天哪，我的脚都快炸裂了！
Oh my God, my feet are bursting!
¡Ay, Dios mío, se me revientan los pieses!
乔利在哪里？
Where is the Jolly?
¿Dónde está la Jolly?
¡ 快乐！
¡Jolly!
哦，我多么讨厌迟到。
Oh, how I hate tardiness.
Ay, cómo odio los impuntuales.
还有那些迟到的人。
And those who arrive late too.
Y los que llegan tarde también.
我也是，苏珊娜。
Me too, Susana.
Yo también, Susana.
当时你在哪里？
Where were you?
¿Dónde estabas?
我很抱歉，我刚刚在车里迷路了，我跟着电话里的西班牙女士，她告诉我......
I apologize, I just got lost in the car, I followed the Spanish woman I have on the phone who told me...
Te pido perdón, es que me perdí con el auto, seguí por la española que tengo en el teléfono que me decía...
右转！
Turn right!
¡Gira a la derecha!
旋转到达目的地！
Spin reaching its destination!
¡Gira llegando a su destino!
您确定他想向您推荐这份工作吗？
Are you sure he wants to present this job to you?
¿Estás segura que te quiere presentar este trabajo?
如果是我呢？
What if me?
¿Y si yo?
你知道我现在是寡妇吗？
And do you know that I am now a widow?
¿Y vos sabes que ahora soy viuda?
我必须工作。
I have to work.
Tengo que trabajar.
另外，选拔通知要求聘请按摩师。
In addition, the selection notice asking for a masseuse.
Además, el aviso de la selección pidiendo masajista.
美丽！
¡Beauty!
但它确实一直在滚动。
But it does roll all the time.
Pero si una rueda todo el tiempo.
如果你没有车。
If you don't have a car.
Si no tenés auto.
我怎么知道你有车？
And how will I know that you have a car?
¿Y cómo voy a saber que vos tenés auto?
但你必须知道。
But you have to know.
Pero tenés que saber.
阿尔托！
¡Alto!
表明你自己的身份。
Identify yourself.
Identifíquese.
我是苏珊娜·埃斯帕达·福奇莱。
I am Susana Espada Fuchile.
Soy Susana Espada Fuchile.
我来是为了通知...
I come for the notice of...
Vengo por el aviso de...
女按摩师。
Masseuse.
Masajista.
我是乔林，朋友，因为我很有用，所以我来作为一个道具。
And I am Jolín, friend, and since I am very useful, I come as a prop.
Y yo soy Jolín, amiga, y como soy muy útil, vengo de utilero.
他们将必须向我提供已完成中学学习的分析证书。
They are going to have to present me with an analytical certificate of completed secondary studies.
Me van a tener que presentar documento certificado analítico de estudios secundarios completos.
尿液样本、无债、税、疫苗手册。
urine sample, debt free, tax, vaccine booklet.
muestra de orina, libre deuda, impositivo, libreta de vacunas.
和一些用于安全的克雷蒙斯。
and some cremones for security.
y unas cremonas para el de seguridad.
我们什么都不知道，我们对这一切一无所知，但他们什么也没告诉我们。
We didn't know anything, we don't have anything about all that, but they didn't tell us anything.
Nosotros no sabíamos nada, no tenemos nada de todo eso, pero no nos dijeron nada.
他们将无法进入。
They will not be able to enter.
No van a poder ingresar.
今天你还没停下来！
You haven't stopped today!
¡Tú no has parado hoy!
罗莎不会让我们过去的！
Rosa is not going to let us pass!
¡Rosa no nos va a dejar pasar!
维吉兰特先生，我想问你一件事，因为我们现在不知道如何离开这里。
Mr. Vigilante, I want to ask you something, because we don't know how to get out of here now.
Señor vigilante, le quiero preguntar una cosa, porque nosotros no sabemos ahora cómo salir de acá.
我们能有什么邦迪？
What bondi can we have?
¿Qué bondi le podemos tomar?
妈妈你看，我会解释的。
Look mommy, I'll explain.
Mira mami, te explico.
你看到你进来的地方了吗？
Did you see where you came in?
¿Viste por donde entraste?
你来到这里，你在那里看到那条路。
You come here, you see that path, there.
Te venís hasta acá, ves el camino aquel, allá.
看到那座淡蓝色的建筑了吗？
Do you see the light blue building?
¿Ves el edificio celeste?
嗯，入口处就是选拔小组。
Well, there, at the entrance, is the selection group.
Bueno, ahí, en la entrada, está el colectivo de selección.
那里，如果你愿意的话。
There, if you want.
Ahí, si querés.
距离您有半个街区，198、293，您还有 Belgrano Sur 车站，如果没有，请穿过高速公路……
You have half a block away, 198, 293, you also have the Belgrano Sur station, and if not, cross the highway and...
Tenés a media cuadra, el 198, el 293, tenés la estación del Belgrano Sur también, y si no, cruza la autopista y...
他们进入了我的内心。
They got into me.
Se me metieron.
他们进入了我的内心。
They got into me.
Se me metieron.
安全？
Security?
¿Seguridad?
他们进入了我的内心。
They got into me.
Se me metieron.
安全？
Security?
¿Seguridad?
他们在哪里？
Where are they?
¿Dónde están?
他们正在西方。
They are having the West.
Están teniendo a la Oeste.
他们有两个！
There are two of them!
¡Son dos!
他们有两个！
There are two of them!
¡Son dos!
它们塞满了！
They are stuffed!
¡Están metidas de peluche!
Anda pa' allá，好，anda pa' allá。
Anda pa' allá, good, anda pa' allá.
Anda pa' allá, bueno, anda pa' allá.
是的，这是一座重要的建筑！
Yes, it is an important building!
¡Sí, es un edificio importante!
看看papurro 和pucurucho 都是来自天堂的奶油！
Look at the papurro and the pucurucho that comes all cream from heaven!
¡Mira el papurro y el pucurucho que viene todo de crema del cielo!
嗯，非常感谢。
Well, thank you very much.
Bueno, muchísimas gracias.
他们还好吗？
How are they still doing?
¿Cómo les va todavía?
你也很漂亮。
You are also very beautiful.
Ustedes también son muy hermosas.
我自我介绍一下，我叫Tolosa，我负责AFA项目。
I introduce myself, my name is Tolosa, I am in charge of the AFA project.
Me presento, mi nombre es Tolosa, soy el encargado del proyecto de la AFA.
好吧，我实际上是主人。
Well, I'm practically the owner.
Bueno, prácticamente soy el dueño.
我猜你们是来工作的，对吗？
I imagine you guys come for work, is that correct?
Me imagino que ustedes vienen por el trabajo, ¿es así?
是的，我是一名按摩师，她是一名道具师。
Yes, I am a masseuse and she is a prop artist.
Sí, yo soy masajista y ella, utilerista.
好吧，让我们从最基本的开始。
Ok, let's start with the most basic.
Ok, vamos a empezar por lo más básico.
我需要你给我你的简历。
I need you to give me your resume.
Necesito que me entreguen su currículum.
我的意思是我需要查看一份证书，知道你们是合格的人。
I mean I need to see a credential, know that you are the qualified people.
Me refiero al necesito ver una credencial, saber que son ustedes las personas capacitadas.
因为我们手头有简历。
Because we have the resume at hand.
Porque el currículum lo tenemos a mano.
没关系，你不理解我，因为我已经独自度过了很多时间。
It's okay, you don't understand me, because I've spent a lot of time alone.
No pasa nada, no me entiendes, porque yo lo he pasado mucho tiempo solo.
但这是卡吗？
But is that the card?
¿Pero ese es el carnet?
卡。
The card.
El carnet.
我有，但是过期了。
I had it, but it expired.
Yo tenía, pero se me venció.
我要派他们去和两个我非常爱的人谈谈。
I'm going to send them to talk to two people I love very much.
Voy a mandarlas hablar con dos personas que quiero muchísimo.
爸爸和马里托。
The Daddy and Marito.
El Daddy y Marito.
我还想告诉你……等一下，梅西的电话响了。
And I also want to tell you... Wait a second, Leo Messi's phone is ringing.
Y además quiero decirles... Un segundo, que está sonando el teléfono a Leo Messi.
不！
¡No!
梅西！
¡Messi!
告诉他我会给他一个吻！
Tell him I'll send him a kiss!
¡Decídele que le mando un beso!
一个吻。
A kiss.
Un beso.
你好，队长。
Hello, captain.
Hola, capitán.
不，我的一些女孩朋友。
No, some girls friends of mine.
No, unas chicas amigas mías.
我给你订的香水你做了什么？
What did you do with the perfume I ordered you?
¿Qué hiciste con el perfume que yo te encargué?
就像马特奥正在使用它一样。
Like Mateo is using it.
Como que lo está usando Mateo.
等一下。
Give me a second.
Dame un segundo.
马特奥如何使用他？
How does Mateo use him?
¿Cómo que le usa Mateo?
去年西罗也发生了同样的事情。
Last year the same thing happened with Ciro.
El año pasado le pasó lo mismo con Ciro.
任务中。
intramission.
la intramisión.
对于工作通知。
For the job notice.
Por el aviso del trabajo.
哦，是的，为了工作。
Oh yes, for work.
Ah, sí, para el trabajo.
我们正在寻找马里托和大卫。
We are looking for Marito and David.
Estamos buscando a Marito y a David.
我没有结婚，我是他的chiquitapia。
I am not marital, I am his chiquitapia.
No soy marital, soy su chiquitapia.
哦，琪琪！
Oh, chiqui!
¡Ay, chiqui!
幼稚少女的亲戚！
Relative of the childish girl!
¡Pariente de la chiquilera!
哦，他们同名，亲戚！
Oh, they have the same name, relative!
¡Ay, es que se llaman igual, pariente!
但我不认为它很小，我认为它很大。
But I don't see it as very small, I see it as quite big.
Pero yo no lo veo muy chiquito, lo veo bastante grande.
那个身体就在我的背上。
With that body on my back.
Con ese cuerpo por mi espalda.
不，我是 AFA 主席。
No, I am the president of the AFA.
No, soy el presidente de la AFA.
你想让我念一下脖子上的放松按摩吗？
Do you want me to read a relaxing massage here on the neck that would leave it?
¿Quiere que leo una masaja relajante acá en el cuello que lo dejaría?
不，我不需要任何东西。
No, I don't need anything.
No, no necesito nada.
去见马里托和达迪。
Go see Marito and Dadi.
Vayan a ver a Marito y a Dadi.
你也不需要雕塑吗？
You don't need a sculpture either?
¿Una esculpidas tampoco necesitas?
我不需要任何东西。
I don't need anything.
No necesito nada.
去更衣室。
Go to the locker room.
Vayan al vestuario.
如果您不想按摩，请。
Please, if you didn't want the massage.
Por favor, si no quiso el masaje.
再见，总统。
See you later, president.
Hasta luego, presidente.
祝你好运，是吗？
Good luck, huh?
Que le vaya bien, ¿eh?
让我们赢得所有奖杯。
Let's win all the cups.
Le ganemos todas las copas.
你是永久的吗？
Have you been permanent?
¿Habéis estado permanente?
没什么，没什么。
Nothing, nothing.
Nada, nada.
正如在马尔维纳斯群岛为战争做准备一样
As in Malvinas prepared for war
Como en Malvinas preparado pa' la guerra
谢谢，梅西。
Thanks, Messi.
Gracias, Messi.
谢谢，巴尔巴。
Thanks, Barba.
Gracias, Barba.
谢谢，奇奇。
Thanks, Chiqui.
Gracias, Chiqui.
你在这里做什么？
What are you doing here?
¿Qué hacen ustedes acá?
你在这里做什么？
What are you doing here?
¿Qué hacen ustedes acá?
我们正在等待大卫和马里托
We are waiting for David and Marito
Estamos esperando a David y a Marito
更衣室不能在这里，因为我是导演
the locker room can't be here because I'm the director
el vestuario no pueden estar acá ustedes porque no porque yo soy el director
阿根廷足球集团、阿根廷足协、阿根廷足协，我向每一位球员……
of Argentine football cabals, of the AFA, of the Argentine Football Association, I offer each player...
de cábalas del fútbol argentino, de la AFA, de la Asociación del Fútbol Argentino, le ofrezco a cada jugador...
一系列目录供他们选择，因此我们赢得了决赛、美洲杯和世界杯。
a series of catalogs for them to choose from and thanks to that we won the final, the Copa América and the World Cup.
una serie de catálogos para que ellos puedan elegir y gracias a eso ganamos la finalísima, la Copa América y la Copa del Mundo.
他们不能坐在这里！
They can't be sitting here!
¡No pueden estar sentadas acá!
卡巴拉主任先生，我有自己的卡巴拉。
Mr. Kabbalah Director, I have my own Kabbalah.
Señor director de cábalas, yo tengo mi propia cábala.
你不知道处罚吗？
You don't know the penalties?
¿Vos no sabés los penales?
我交叉手指，触摸我的左乳房。
I crossed my fingers and touched my left breast.
Yo cruzo los dedos y me tocó el seno izquierdo.
如果他抓住了我，另一个人就会抓住我。
And if he got me, the other guy got me.
Y si me copó, me tocó el otro.
帮帮他吧，他好像已经起来了。
Help him, he's like he's up.
Ayúdale que está como alzado.
我做一件事，我...
I do one thing, I...
Yo hago una cosa, yo...
我不相信那些东西。
I don't believe in those things.
No creo en esas cosas.
我更...我简直不敢相信。
I'm more... I can't believe it.
Yo soy más... No estoy de creer.
不，你必须相信。
No, you have to believe.
No, tienes que creer.
之前我还以为是鳟鱼。
Before I thought it was a trout.
Antes pensé que era un trucho.
啊，显示？
Ah, ¿show?
Ah, ¿viste?
现在呢？
And now?
¿Y ahora?
¡道场！
¡Dojo!
你好你好！
Hello hello!
¡Hola, hola!
你好！
Hello!
¡Hola!
向所有认识我的人问好！
Greetings to all who know me!
¡Saludos a todos los que me conocen!
游戏一团糟！
The game is a mess!
¡El partido es un embole!
是的，这确实是一场艰难的比赛，我们做了我们这一周所做的工作。
Yes, it really was a difficult game, we did what we worked on during the week.
Sí, realmente fue un partido difícil, hicimos lo que trabajamos en la semana.
他们在那里做什么？
And what are they doing there?
¿Y éstas qué hacen ahí?
把他们救出来的代价会很大。
It's going to be expensive to get them out.
Que va a ser caro ya a sacarlas.
他们在这里做什么？
What are they doing here?
¿Qué hacen acá?
没什么，小姐。
Nothing, miss.
Nada, señorita.
不，不，没什么。
No, no, nothing.
No, no, nada.
我们正在等马里托和爸爸。
We are waiting for Marito and Daddy.
Estamos esperando a Marito y a Daddy.
啊，我100岁了。
Ah, I am 100.
Ah, yo soy 100.
多少？
How much?
¿Cuánto?
100.
社区经理。
Community manager.
是的，从选择来看。
Yes, from the selection.
Sí, de la selección.
我帮助球员。
I help the players.
Ayudo a los jugadores.
类似于 Facebook、Instagram、TikTok。
Subicás like Facebook, Instagram, TikTok.
Subicás tipo con Facebook, Instagram, TikTok.
然后输入，我是内容创建者。
And type, I'm a content creator.
Y tipo, soy content creator.
他也会以同样的方式挑战她。
He will challenge her the same.
La retará igual.
不，我带着签名。
No, I'm with the autographs.
No, yo estoy con los autógrafos.
谁？
Whose?
¿De quién?
入选者的签名。
The autographs of the selection.
Los autógrafos de la selección.
我的意思是，我的笔迹很好，而且他们也提供给我们，所以我做出了选择。
I mean, I have good handwriting and they have supplied us, so I make the selection.
O sea, tengo buena letra y ellos nos han abasto, así que hago las de la selección.
签名都找到了，除了亚历克西斯·麦卡利斯特的签名，我也没有得到。
The autographs are located, except for Alexis McAllister's, which I don't get too.
ubicados los autógrafos, salvo el de Alexis McAllister que no me sale también.
哪一个效果好呢？
And which one turns out well?
¿Y cuál que sale bien?
玛丽亚的面条。
Maria's Noodle.
El de Fideo de María.
像 Fideo 那样做。
Do it like Fideo.
Hacelo al de Fideo.
他们的名字是什么？
What are their names?
¿Cómo son sus nombres?
安和Xoli。
On and Xoli.
Su y Xoli.
好吧，为你和朱莉，玛丽亚的充满爱的视频。
Well, for you and Jolie, Maria's video with love.
Bien, para tú y Jolie, el video de María con cariño.
阿雷
Arre
Arre.
瞧，那是超级可爱的。
Look, it was super cute.
Mira, quedó supercuta.
让我们看看，让我们看看。
Let's see, let's see.
A ver, a ver.
哦，是一样的！
Oh, it's the same!
¡Ay, es igual!
玛丽亚的面条是什么？
What is Maria's noodle?
¿Cuál es el fideo de María?
什么是面条？
What is the noodle?
¿Cuál es el fideo?
都是一样的 都是一样的
and it's the same it's the same
y es igual es igual
你也代表球员签署支票吗？
Do you also sign checks on behalf of the players?
¿Firmás cheque también de parte de los jugadores?
是的当然。
Yes of course.
Sí, por supuesto.
哦，好吧，他话很多。
Oh well, he talks a lot.
Ah, bueno, habla un montón.
时间到了。
There's the minute.
Ahí está el minuto.
布埃诺。
Bueno.
啊！
¡Ah!
这是谁？
And who is this?
¿Y esta quién es?
比如是谁？
Like who is it?
¿Cómo que quién es?
我是珍妮。
I'm Jenny.
Soy la Jenny.
我是斗篷，恩查尔的老大，第一。
I am the cape, the boss of Enchal, number one.
Soy la capa, la jefa del Enchal, la number one.
我们计划去参加下一届世界杯。
We plan to go to the next World Cup.
Nosotras pensamos ir al próximo mundial.
是的，我们来谈谈吧。
Yes, let's talk to me.
Sí, vamos a hablar conmigo.
是的？
Yeah?
¿Sí?
因为？
Because?
¿Por qué?
是的，你必须跟我说话。
Yes, you have to talk to me.
Sí, tiene que hablar conmigo.
我要把那面写着……的旗帜擦干。
I'm going to dry the flag that says...
Yo voy a secar la bandera que diga...
Susy 礼物，我还要带另一件上面写着 Johnny 的礼物，因为我要陪你
Susy present and I'm going to bring another one that says Johnny too because I'm going to accompany you
Susy presente y yo voy a llevar otra que diga Johnny también porque te voy a acompañar
欧莱，欧莱，欧莱，欧莱！
Olé, olé, olé, olé!
¡Olé, olé, olé, olé!
奥莱，奥莱 奥莱，奥莱
Olé, olé Olé, olé
奥莱，奥莱，奥莱！
Olé, olé, olé!
¡Olé, olé, olé!
奥莱，是的！
Olé, yes!
¡Olé, así sí!
奥莱，奥莱！
Olé, olé!
¡Olé, olé!
你必须更新。
You have to update.
Hay que actualizar.
晚安。
Good night.
Buenas noches.
晚安。
Good night.
Buenas noches.
现在我们再次被声波所感染，因为他们同时出发。
Now we are insonated again, since they are going at the same time.
Ahora nos volvemos a insonar, ya que lo van a la par.
哦，看看谁帅。
Oh, look who's cool.
Ay, mire quién está men papo.
我简直不敢相信。
I can't believe it.
No lo puedo creer.
我简直不敢相信，我发誓。
I can't believe it, I swear.
No lo puedo creer, te juro.
你怎么样，小家伙？
How are you doing, little guy?
¿Cómo anda, cochote?
卡波拉！
¡Cápola!
第一！
Number one!
¡El número uno!
不，我是吉乔特·科波拉。
No, I'm Guijote Coppola.
No, soy Guijote Coppola.
不，土狼卡波拉。
No, Coyote Capola.
啊，好吧，但是变调夹来自变调夹，这是变调夹。
Ah, well, but capo comes from capo, this is a capo.
Ah, bueno, pero capo la viene de capo, esto es un capo.
这是真的。
It's true.
Es verdad.
你在干什么？
What are you doing?
¿Qué haces?
你在干什么？
What are you doing?
¿Qué haces?
你在干什么？
What are you doing?
¿Qué haces?
起来吧！
Getting up!
¡El levantarse!
我的，做对了！
My, do it right!
¡Mis, hazlo bien!
哎呀，我不再抬举你的痛苦了！
My, I no longer lift up your suffering!
¡Mis, a tu sufrir ya no levanto!
如今我有一家代理机构，科波拉集团，专门为足球运动员提供代理服务。
Today I have an agency, Copola Group, which is dedicated to representing soccer players.
Yo hoy tengo una agencia, Copola Group, que se dedica a representar futbolistas.
举办活动。
Make events.
Hacer eventos.
正是我们所需要的。
Just what we need.
Justo lo que necesitamos.
我们需要一个经理。
We need a manager.
Nosotras necesitamos manager.
你打球吗？
Do you play ball?
¿Ustedes juegan a la pelota?
不，不，但是好吧，但是我们是来工作的，如果我们见面，我们需要一个了解这个数字的人，我们理解。
No, no, but well, but we came for a job and if we meet, we need someone who understands the number, we understand.
No, no, pero bueno, pero vinimos por un trabajo y si quedamos, necesitamos a alguien que entienda el número, nosotros entendemos.
但更了解他是一名经理。
But someone who understands more that he was a manager.
Pero alguien que entienda más que era manager.
但我的收费很高。
But my fees are high.
Pero mis honorarios son elevados.
利润各占50%。
of the profits, 50% each.
de las ganancias, el 50% cada uno.
而损失中，100%是你的。
And of the losses, 100% is for you.
Y de las pérdidas, el 100% es para ustedes.
100%为我们，更多为损失
100% for us, more for the loss
100% para nosotros, más para la pérdida
交易完成。
Deal done.
Trato hecho.
我会给你留一张小卡片，很快再见。
I'll leave you a little card and see you soon.
Le dejo una tarjetita y nos vemos próximamente.
哦，是的，再见。
Oh yes, see you.
Ay, sí, nos vemos.
再见，老板。
Goodbye, boss.
Adiós, capo.
多么华丽啊。
How gorgeous.
Qué hermoso.
你怎么把它搞砸了？
How do you screw it up?
¿Cómo lo cagas?
这是萨拉米香肠。
It's a salami.
Es un salame.
这是T和M！
This is the T and the M!
¡Esto es la T y la M!
噢，请问这里的苏，玩家随时都会出现。
Oh, let's ask Sue here that the players appear at any moment.
Ay, pedímonos acá a Sue que en cualquier momento aparecen los jugadores.
哦，你也这么认为吗？
Oh, do you think so?
Ay, ¿te parece?
我的胡子能翻译吗？
Do my mustaches translate?
¿Se me traducen los bigotes?
发生了什么？
What happened?
¿Qué pasó?
我们在做什么？
What are we doing?
¿Qué estamos haciendo?
当你说去更衣室时，你就踩在草地上了。
When you say go to the locker room, you are stepping on the grass.
Cuando se dice vayan al vestuario, está pisando el pasto.
谁在踩草地？
Who is stepping on the grass?
¿Quién está pisando el pasto?
他们踩着草地小姐
they are stepping on the grass miss
están pisando el pasto señorita
这是一种特殊的草。
This is a special grass.
Este es un pasto especial.
当我们成为冠军时，我们从卡塔尔引进了他。
We brought him from Qatar when we became champions.
Lo trajimos de Qatar cuando salimos campeones.
我不应该告诉这件事，但奇基塔皮亚在公文包里掉了三块面包。
I shouldn't have told this, but Chiquitapia dropped three loaves of bread inside a briefcase.
Esto no tenía que haberlo contado, pero a Chiquitapia se le cayeron tres panes adentro de un portafolio.
我们用我们种植的canchero和友好的水让它生长
and with the canchero we were planting and with friendly water we made it grow
y con el canchero estuvimos sembrando y con agua amigable hicimos crecer
是的，我们用三个panis完成了这一切。
Yes, with three panis we did all this.
Sí, con tres panis hicimos todo esto.
我请求你，不要踩草地。
I ask you please, do not step on the grass.
Les pido por favor, no pisen el pasto.
请离开。
Please leave.
Retírense, por favor.
我们不踩它。
We don't step on it.
Nosotros no lo pisamos.
我们正在踩它。
We are stepping on it.
Lo estamos pisando.
好的，我去点酒吧。
Ok, I'll order the bar.
Ok, voy a pedir el bar.
让我们看看，让我们看看，让我们看看。
Let's see, let's see, let's see.
A ver, a ver, a ver.
VAR 吹罚。
The VAR calls.
El VAR llama.
我们无法准确地看到他们是否踏上比赛场地，但是......
We don't get to see precisely if they stepped on the playing field or not but...
No llegamos a ver con precisión si pisaron o no el campo de juego pero...
我需要你给我你的意见，胡安·巴勃罗。
I need you to give me your opinion, Juan Pablo.
Necesito que me de su opinión, Juan Pablo.
都是你的。
All yours.
Todo tuyo.
你说什么，伙计？
What do you say, mate?
¿Qué dice, compañero?
我认为脚底对果岭表面有轻微的介入
I think there is a slight intervention of the sole of the foot on the surface of the green
Creo que hay una leve intervención de la planta del pie sobre la superficie del verde
这可能是非自愿的，但我们会看看他们的决定。
It could be involuntary, but we'll see what they decide.
Podría ser involuntaria, pero veremos qué deciden.
我们想想那把铲子所走的线！
We think about the line that that shovel takes!
¡Pensamos nosotros la línea que se le pone esa pala!
我这里有图像，慢动作可能会扭曲，但这里毫无疑问。
I have the image here, slow motion can distort, but there is no doubt here.
Tengo la imagen acá, la cámara lenta puede distorsionar, pero acá no hay ninguna duda.
但毫无疑问过去了。
But no doubt passed.
Pero ninguna duda pasado.
确认的！
Confirmed!
¡Confirmado!
确认了，酒吧确认了，他们走上了比赛场。
Confirmed, the bar confirms it, they stepped onto the playing field.
Confirmado, lo confirma el bar, pisaron el campo de juego.
和？
And?
¿Y qué?
和？
And?
¿Y qué?
和？
And?
¿Y qué?
和？
And?
¿Y qué?
和？
And?
¿Y qué?
和？
And?
¿Y qué?
和？
And?
¿Y qué?
和？
And?
¿Y qué?
和？
And?
¿Y qué?
来吧，来吧。
Go ahead, go ahead.
Adelante, adelante.
你是来看通知的吗？
Are you coming for the notice?
¿Ustedes vienen por el aviso?
我是一个丈夫。
I am a husband.
Yo soy marito.
我感受到了选择的信息。
I feel the message of the selection.
Siento el mensaje de la selección.
你说得对。
You're right.
Tienes razón.
这是一次意外，是无意的。
It was an accident, it was unintentional.
Fue un accidente, fue sin querer.
那是因为胜利的喜悦。
It was because of the joy of victory.
Fue por la alegría del triunfo.
我是一个道具人。
I am a prop man.
Yo soy utilero.
现在我的助理来了。
Now my assistant is coming.
Ahora va a venir mi asistente.
卡鲁查！
¡Carucha!
啊，卡鲁查！
Ah, Carucha!
¡Ah, Carucha!
你好，卡鲁查！
Hello, Carucha!
¡Hola, Carucha!
哦，我也给了你一个吻！
Oh, I gave you a kiss too!
¡Ay, te di un beso también!
谁来找通知的？
Who came for the notice?
¿Quién vino por el aviso?
我们俩。
Both of us.
Nosotras dos.
我是一名女按摩师。
I am a masseuse.
Yo es yo masajista.
好吧，我们对你有什么看法？
Well, what do we think about you?
Bueno, ¿qué nos pensamos con vos?
好，好，好。
Good, good, good.
Bien, bien, bien.
这就是产品。
This is the product.
Es este el producto.
你的头发是什么做的？
What's making your hair?
¿Qué está poniendo el pelo?
一点奶油。
A little cream.
Un poquito de crema.
好的。
GOOD.
Bien.
从玻璃上看永远不会坏。
Never bad from the glass.
Nunca malo de la copa.
但这并不愚蠢。
But it's not stupid.
Pero no es coba.
你看到模因了吗？
Did you see the memes?
¿Viste los memes?
我看到了一切。
I saw everything.
Vi todo.
很强吧？
Strong, huh?
Fuerte, ¿eh?
我不喜欢它，这就是为什么... 和理发师谈谈。
I didn't like it, that's why... Talk to the hairdressers.
No me gustó, por eso... Habla con los peruqueros.
我下次去试试。
I took a trial next time.
Yo tomé un juicio la próxima vez.
我谈到过。
I talked about it.
Lo hablé.
完美的。
Perfect.
Perfecto.
我们来时，请带上糖果。
Take candy, as we come.
Toma caramelo, como venimos.
我不能对你撒谎。
I can't lie to you.
No te puedo mentir.
你吃多少？
How much are you eating?
¿Cuánto estás comiendo?
我们走吧。
Let's go.
Vamos.
32.
32个很多了。
32 is a lot.
32 es muchísimo.
糖又上升了一个档次。
Sugar is up a notch.
La azúcar está un pico arriba.
允许！
Permission!
¡Permiso!
¡哎呀哎呀！
¡Ey, ey, ey!
¡啊！
¡Ahh!
我死定了！
I'm dead dead!
¡Me muero muerto!
当然！
Of course!
¡Claro!
我的天啊。
Oh my God.
Ay, Dios mío.
他是一位伟大的专业人士，他非常出色。
He is a great professional, he is excellent.
Es un gran profesional, es excelente.
妈的，你能面对吗？
Damn, can you face it?
Carucha, ¿te podés encarar?
多谢。
Thanks a lot.
Muchísimas gracias.
我来了，嗯？
I'm coming, huh?
Ya vengo, ¿eh?
记住我告诉你的话。
Remember what I told you.
Acordate lo que te dije.
我的丈夫儿子，你在叫我吗？
My husband son, were you calling me?
Mi hijo marito, ¿me llamabas?
唐·波尔！
¡Don Pol!
我要死了。
I'm dying.
Yo me muero.
我以味道发誓，我……不，不。
I swear by the taste, I... No, no.
Te juro por el gusto, yo... No, no.
由波尔.
By Pol.
De Pol.
我差点认不出你了。
I almost don't recognize you.
Yo casi no te reconozco.
你在这里做什么？
What are you doing here?
¿Qué hace acá?
你继续玩了吗？
Did you continue playing?
¿Seguió jugando vos?
这位被征召了，他是选拔的小引擎。
This one is called up, he is the little engine of the selection.
Este está convocado, es el motorcito de la selección.
小马达？
The little motor?
¿El motorcito?
如果我看到它，它是一个马达，就像一只兔子。
And if I see it, it's a motor, like a rabbit.
Y si yo lo veo, es un motor, como un conejo.
我没能认出你是因为你的头发，因为它总是在改变颜色。
I didn't recognize you because of your hair, because it always changed color.
Yo no te reconocía por el pelo, porque siempre cambiaba de color.
是的，这是真的。
Yes it's true.
Sí, es verdad.
而且现在我看到他，他很安静。
And also now that I see him, he is very quiet.
Y además ahora que lo veo que es muy calladito.
整天在球场上说话、说话。
And on the court all day talking, talking.
Y en la cancha todo el día hablando, hablando.
你在法庭上说什么？
What do you say on the court?
¿Qué dices en la cancha?
它们是游戏的东西。
They are game things.
Son cosas del juego.
他们是两个不同的人。
They are two different.
Son dos diferentes.
啊，外面很安静。
Ah, it's quiet outside.
Ah, afuera se va tranquilo.
啊，外面很安静。
Ah, it's quiet outside.
Ah, afuera se va tranquilo.
啊，外面很安静。
Ah, it's quiet outside.
Ah, afuera se va tranquilo.
啊，外面很安静。
Ah, it's quiet outside.
Ah, afuera se va tranquilo.
是的，看，她正在作为道具奔跑。
Yes, look, she is running as a prop.
Sí, mira, ella está postulante como utilera.
是的，上面有给你的道具。
Yes, props on top for you.
Sí, utilera encima para vos.
我是一名女按摩师。
And I am a masseuse.
Y yo soy masajista.
来吧，来吧，来吧。
Come, come, come.
Vení, vení, vení.
坐下
sit down
Sentate.
阿科斯塔，阿科斯塔。
Acostate, acostate.
小心点，这需要几个小时。
Be careful, it's worth hours.
Cuidado que valen horas.
身上有多少涂鸦。
How much graffiti the body has.
Cuánto grafiti que tiene el cuerpo.
看看这腿有多重。
Look how heavy these legs are.
Mira lo que pesa de estas piernas.
以及它的价值。
And what it's worth.
Y lo que vale.
是的，我参加了急救课程。
Yes, I took the first aid course.
Sí, hice el curso de los primeros auxilios.
是的，第一个，然后第二个，他们把他踢了出去。
Yes, the first ones, then the second one they kicked him out.
Sí, los primeros, después la segunda le echaron.
嗯，好的。
Well, the good.
Bueno, lo bueno.
我们来试试吧。
Let's try it.
Vamos a probarlo.
我卖掉它吗？
Do I sell it?
¿Lo vendo?
是的，是的。
Yes, yes.
Sí, sí.
卖了，卖给大家了……
Sell ​​it, sell it to everyone...
Vendalo, vendalo a todos los...
如果你卖掉它，我就买它。
and if you sell it, I'll buy it.
y si lo vendes, yo lo compro.
哦，对不起，对不起。
Oh, sorry, sorry.
Ay, perdón, perdón.
不，不，不。
No, no, no.
对不起，对不起。
Sorry, sorry.
Perdón, perdón.
小心！
Careful!
¡Cuidado!
我不想那样！
I don't want that!
¡No quiero eso!
好强啊！
Okay strong!
¡Vale fuerte!
既然我买了！
Now that I buy it!
¡Ahora que lo compro!
不不不，很强。
No, no, it's very strong.
No, no, está muy fuerte.
它非常强大。
It's very strong.
Está muy fuerte.
是的，是的，是的。
Yes, yes, yes.
Sí, sí, sí.
这对腹部有好处，但是看。
And this is good for the bellies, but look.
Y esto es bueno para las barris, pero fíjense.
那么，看看这是什么。
So, look what this is.
Entonces, mirá lo que es esto.
好吧，好吧，好吧。
Well, well, well.
Bueno, bueno, bueno.
衣服，我们为您折叠
the clothes and we fold them for you
la ropa y nosotros te la doblamos
好吧，她叠好你的衣服。
Well, she folds your clothes.
Bueno, ella te la dobla la ropa.
Ahí va，宁静，宁静，宁静，你，你，你，你。
Ahí va, tranquilo, tranquilo, tranquilo, you, you, you, you.
Ahí va, tranquilo, tranquilo, tranquilo, anda, anda, anda, anda.
小心，他拿走了蜡烛！
Be careful, he took the candle!
¡Cuidado, se llevó la vela!
听着，现在我要告诉你一件事！
Look, now I'll tell you something!
¡Mira, ahora te digo algo!
我
i
你好。
Hello.
Hola.
我是来参加按摩测试的。
I come for the massage test.
Vengo a la prueba de masajismo.
进来之前擦脚了吗？
Did you wipe your feet before coming in?
¿Te limpiaste los pies antes de entrar?
是的，很干净。
Yes, it's clean.
Sí, está limpio.
请降低它。
Lower it please.
Bájalo, por favor.
你是谁？
Who are you?
¿Vos quién sos?
我是厨师。
I am the cook.
El cocinero soy.
哦，多好啊！
Oh, how good!
¡Ay, qué bien!
我会成为谁？
Who am I going to be?
¿Quién voy a ser?
清洁的那个？
The cleaning one?
¿El de limpieza?
哪里说你是清洁工？
And where does it say you're the cleaning guy?
¿Y por dónde dice que sos el de limpieza?
AFA 说，我以为你是一名退役球员。
The AFA says there, I thought you were a retired player.
Ahí dice la AFA, pensé que eras un jugador retirado.
你在做什么？
And what are you doing?
¿Y qué estás haciendo?
因为？
Because?
¿Por qué?
鸡蛋清洗还是打蛋？
Cleaning or beating eggs?
¿Limpiando o batiendo huevos?
我正在打扫卫生，因为这些孩子简直就是猪圈。
I'm cleaning, because these kids are a pigsty.
Estoy limpiando, porque estos chicos son un chiquero.
我增加辞职。
I increase my resignation.
Yo me aumento el renuncio.
你会怎么办？
What would you do?
¿Qué harías?
厨师。
Chef.
Cocinero.
富西奥内罗？
Fucionero?
¿Fucionero?
是的。
Yeah.
Sí.
一年前我用它做了一个蛋糕。
I made a cake from it a year ago.
Hice un bizcocho de él hace un año.
你的结果如何？
And how did it turn out for you?
¿Y cómo te salió?
而且有点难，我还剪不了。
And it's a little hard, I can't cut it yet.
Y está un poco duro, no lo puedo cortar todavía.
我什至不需要在家里把它写在纸上。
I don't even have to put it on paper at home.
Lo tengo que pisar papel ni en casa.
一年后。
After a year.
Después de un año.
好吧，祝其他人好运，我要离开，因为我要去观看一部名为 Beykoz 的电视节目。
Well, good luck with the others, I'm leaving because I'm going to watch a TV show called Beykoz.
Bueno, escúchame suerte con los demás, que me voy porque voy a ver un programa de tele que se llama Beykoz.
让我们看看我是否学到了一些东西
Let's see if I learn something
a ver si aprendo algo
我想问你一个谜语。
I want to ask you a riddle.
Te quiero hacer una adivinanza.
电影的名字是什么？
What is the name of the movie?
¿Cómo se llama la película?
一个做蛋糕的人转而做choripanes。
that a man who made cakes switched to making choripanes.
que un señor que hacía tortas se pasó a hacer choripanes.
它叫什么？
What's it called?
¿Cómo se llama?
勒索者！
Extortist!
¡Extortista!
他没有爱，那个男人也没有爱，多么奇怪。
He has no love, that man has no love, how strange.
No tiene amor, no tiene amor ese hombre, que raro.
我个人很喜欢它。
Personally I liked it.
Personalmente me gustó.
我不知道我是否听懂了，但我还是笑了。
I don't know if I understood it very much, but I laughed anyway.
No sé si lo entendí mucho, pero me reí igual.
你笑了吗？
Did you laugh?
¿Te reíste?
这才是最重要的，快乐。
That's what counts, the joy.
Eso es lo que cuenta, la alegría.
你好吗？
How are you?
¿Qué tal?
很高兴见到你。
Nice to meet you.
Mucho gusto.
你做什么？
And what do you do?
¿Y vos qué hacés?
我是公交车司机。
I'm the bus driver.
Soy el chofer del micro.
哦，我多么希望有一天能去坐公共汽车。
Oh, how I would like to go to the bus one day.
Ay, cómo me gustaría ir un día al micro.
您想去哪里？
Where would you like to go?
¿A dónde te gustaría ir?
哦，不，不，我只是开车或带他们从酒店到体育场。
Oh, no, no, I just drive them or take them from the property to the stadium.
Ah, no, no, yo solo los manejo o los llevo del predio al estadio.
我是沿海航行。
I am cabotage.
Soy de cabotaje.
啊，我不知道那个地方，不过没关系。
Ah, I don't know that place, but it doesn't matter.
Ah, no conozco ese lugar, pero no importa.
你叫我按摩师吗？
Did you call me a masseuse?
¿Me dijiste masajista?
按摩师的按摩真是太棒了。
It's amazing with the masseuses, the massage.
Es increíble con los masajistas, el masaje.
它起源于中国，比基督早 2700 年。
It arose in China, 2700 years before Christ.
Surge en China, 2700 años antes de Cristo.
他们进入现场，他们创造反射疗法，但当然，我们不必排除它。
They enter the scene, they create reflexology, but of course, we do not have to rule it out.
entran en la escena, crean la reflexología, pero claro, no tenemos que descartar.
当然，对希腊人来说，有所有的文化、体育文化、精神，但真正的现代按摩是在19世纪。
to the Greeks, of course, with all the culture, the physical culture, the mind, but the true modern massage, 19th century.
a los griegos, claro, con toda la cultura, la cultura física, la mente, pero el verdadero masaje moderno, siglo XIX.
格里特·林德，瑞典人。
Gerrit Lind, the Swede.
Gerrit Lind, el sueco.
你看过关于按摩的那一篇吗？
Did you see the one about the massages?
¿Viste el de los masajes?
是的，爸爸。
Yes, dad.
Sí, papá.
壮观，巨大。
Spectacular, tremendous.
Espectacular, tremendo.
非常好。
Very good.
Buenísimo.
我不敢相信你怎么知道这一切。
I can't believe how you know all that.
Yo no puedo creer cómo sabes todo eso.
结果是我惹了很多麻烦。
What happens is that I make a lot of trouble.
Lo que pasa es que lío mucho.
这更...
It's more...
Es más...
事实上，对不起，我给自己留了一点空间。
In fact, excuse me, but I made a little space for myself.
De hecho, disculpame, pero me hice un huequito.
我要去公交车上读一点关于篮子虫的变态的知识。
I'm going to the bus to read a little about the metamorphosis of the basket bug.
Me voy al micro a leer un poquito sobre la metamorfosis del bicho canasto.
你有事吗？
Do you anything?
¿Vos cualquier cosa?
有人问我的情况吗？
Is anyone asking about me?
¿Alguien pregunta por mí?
你没看到我吗？
Didn't you see me?
¿No me viste?
这是一次完美的逃离。
This is a perfect escape.
Esto que sea un escape perfecto.
嗨，事情怎么样？
Hi how are things?
Hola, ¿qué tal?
大豆爸爸。
Soy Daddy.
¡爸爸！
¡Daddy!
你是来应聘按摩师工作的吗？
Are you coming for the masseuse job?
¿Viene por el trabajo de masajista?
是的，要提供证据。
Yes, to give proof.
Sí, para dar la prueba.
我是一名有执照的按摩治疗师。
I am a licensed massage therapist.
Soy masajista matriculada.
嗯，他要去参加考试。
Well, he's going to take a test.
Bueno, se va a tomar una prueba.
哦真的吗？
Oh really?
¿En serio?
噢，美丽，谢谢。
Oh, beautiful, thank you.
Ay, hermoso, gracias.
我把你想要的东西带到了这里。
I brought you here what you asked for.
Te traje acá lo que me pediste.
你不是马里托的助手吗？
Weren't you Marito's assistant?
¿Vos no eras el ayudante de Marito?
是的，还有达迪亚的助理，他有工作……
Yes, and dadia's assistant, who with a job...
Sí, y asistente de dadia, que con un trabajo...
从事这方面的两份工作还是什么？
Two jobs in this or something?
¿Dos laburos en este o algo?
参加测试。
Take the test.
Haz la prueba.
谢谢。
Gracias.
是的，我接受。
Yes, I take it.
Sí, me la toma.
我们感觉。
We feel.
Sentimosnos.
很好，完美。
Good, perfect.
Bien, perfecto.
让我们看看，这是肌肉受伤后给球员穿的第一件事。
Let's see, it's the first thing you put on a player after a muscle injury.
A ver, es lo primero que se le pone a un jugador después de una lesión muscular.
替补。
A substitute.
Un suplente.
巧妙。
Ingenious.
Ingeniosa.
真的。
Really.
De verdad.
这非常好，非常聪明。
It's very good, very clever.
Es muy bien, muy ingeniosa.
最好的事情就是让我们练习一下。
The best thing is let's practice.
Lo mejor vamos a la práctica.
你知道我在骗你，对吗？
You know I'm lying to you, right?
Sabes que yo te miento, ¿eh?
我的意思是，波尔长得很漂亮，但你却超级懒。
I mean, Pol has a good look, but you are super lazy.
O sea, de Pol tiene facha, pero tú sos súper lativo.
永远不要把自己奉献给演艺事业...
Never dedicate yourself to acting...
Nunca te dediques a actuar...
我没有开始，再次做同样的事情。
I didn't start, again with the same thing.
No empecé, otra vez con lo mismo.
买糖...
Buy candy...
Comprar caramelo...
就是这样，我要去买一条石斑鱼，对不起！
There it is, I'm going to buy a grouper, excuse me!
¡Ahí está, voy a comprar una mero, permiso!
试试石斑鱼，你说怎么样！
Try the grouper, what do you say!
¡Pruétele a la mero, qué me dice!
你为什么打电话给我？
Why did you call me?
¿Por qué me llamaste?
我刚一看，一个男人要抓住我。
I just checked it out, a man is about to grab me.
Es que lo puse a ver, me está por agarrar un surmenaz.
公主？
The princess?
¿La princesa?
莱安德罗·帕雷德斯！
Leandro Paredes!
¡Leandro Paredes!
莱安德罗，莱安德罗！
Leandro, Leandro!
¡Leandro, Leandro!
好吧，莱安德罗，莱安德罗，事实是……我们带她来当按摩师，我们希望她和……
Well, Leandro, Leandro, the truth is that... We brought her as a masseuse, we want her with...
Bueno, Leandro, Leandro, la verdad es que... La trajimos como masajista, la queremos con...
我已经在进行测试了。
I'm already giving a test.
Estoy ya dando una prueba.
是的？
Yeah?
¿Sí?
它可以工作。
It can work.
Puede funcionar.
它可以工作。
It can work.
Puede funcionar.
我慢慢地做你。
I do you slowly.
Te hago despacito.
我从这里开始。
I start here.
Empiezo por acá.
如果你不想让洛佩兹碰你。
If you don't want the lópez to touch you.
Si no querés que te toque el lópez.
不，不，不。
No, no, no.
他碰过你的脖子吗？
Did he touch your neck?
¿Te tocó el cuello?
不，是腿，是腿。
No, the leg, the leg.
No, la pierna, la pierna.
噢，腿？
Oh, the leg?
Ah, ¿la pierna?
这是一个测试。
It's a test.
Es una prueba.
对于洛佩斯来说，他们是半个狂热分子。
This with López they are half fanatics.
Esto con el López son medio fanáticos.
你必须等待，你正在等待。
You have to wait, you are waiting.
Vos tenés que esperar, vos estás esperando.
告诉他，告诉他，请告诉他。
Tell him, tell him, please tell him.
Decíle, decíle, por favor, decíle.
好吧，没关系。
OK that's fine.
Bueno, está bien.
但我喜欢他们为你描绘的方式，我喜欢它。
But I liked how they illustrated you, I like it.
Pero me gustaba como te ilusaron, me gusta.
很美丽。
It's beautiful.
Es hermosa.
赫莫萨。
Hermosa.
我会解释一下。
I'll explain a little.
Voy a explicar un poquito.
我把它放在哪里？
Where do I put it?
¿Dónde le pongo?
在腿上。
On the legs.
En las piernas.
在腿上。
On the legs.
En las piernas.
这个会去吗？
Will this one go?
¿Esta irá?
但首先是在腿上
on the legs but first
en las piernas pero primero
活着的双胞胎要花多少钱或多或少？
How much will the living twin cost more or less?
¿Cuánto costará más o menos el gemelo que vive?
要知道。
To know.
Para saber.
我们阻止了它，是的。
We stopped it, yes.
Lo paramos, sí.
哦，帕拉拉，帕拉拉。
Oh, parala, parala.
Ay, parala, parala.
不，这并不奇怪。
No, it's not weird.
No, no está rara.
这是什么，我的爱人？
And what is this, my love?
¿Y esto qué es, mi amor?
谁对你做的？
Who did it to you?
¿Quién te lo hizo?
一脚。
A kick.
Una patada.
谁给你的？
Who gave it to you?
¿Quién te la dio?
这种接触水泥...
This contact cement...
Este cemento de contacto...
您将如何放置接触水泥？
How are you going to put the contact cement?
¿Cómo te va a poner el cemento de contacto?
不能接触水泥，会很硬。
There can be no contact cement, it will be hard.
No puede haber cemento de contacto, se la va a dejar dura.
是的，基本上是的。
yes, basically yes.
que sí, básicamente sí.
我有什么感觉，莱安德罗？
What did I feel, Leandro?
¿Qué sentí, Leandro?
我有什么感觉？
What did I feel?
¿Qué sentí?
事情稳定了一点，我们走吧。
It settles a little and let's go.
Se cala un poco y vamos.
是的，是的。
Yes, yes.
Está, está.
走吧，走吧。
Let's go, let's go.
Vámonos, vámonos.
这是一个考验。
It was a test.
Era una prueba.
不，这不是测试。
No, it wasn't a test.
No, no era una prueba.
我确信现在还没有轮到我。
I'm sure it's not my turn.
Seguro que no me toca.
就是这样，就是这样。
That's it, that's it.
Ya está, ya está.
请跟我来。
Please come with me.
Por favor, acompáñame.
我们走吧，我们走吧，我们走吧。
Let's go, let's go, let's go.
Vámonos, vámonos, vámonos.
¡Chaisu!
¡  Chaisu!
进展如何？
How did it go?
¿Cómo te fue?
好吧，但是我涂在脸上的霜有点问题......
Well, fine, but I had a little problem with the cream I put on the...
Bueno, bien, pero tuve un problemita con la crema que le puse en la...
哦！
Oh!
¡Ay!
哦！
Oh!
¡Ay!
哦！
Oh!
¡Ay!
哦！
Oh!
¡Ay!
哦！
Oh!
¡Ay!
哦！
Oh!
¡Ay!
哦！
Oh!
¡Ay!
哦！
Oh!
¡Ay!
首先，他们对我所做的事情非常丑陋。
First, what they did to me is very ugly.
Primero, es muy feo lo que me hicieron.
我们对你做了什么？
What did we do to you?
¿Qué te hicimos?
第二个是法国。
And second, France.
Y segundo, Francia.
他们对我做的最透明的事情。
The most transparent thing they did to me.
Lo más transparente que me hicieron.
那不好，我把他们介绍给球员了，我不喜欢他们的做法，丑陋。
That's not good, I introduced them to the players, I don't like what they did, ugly.
No está bueno eso, les presenté a los jugadores, no me gusta lo que hicieron, feo.
我们必须工作，我是寡妇，我必须工作
We have to work, I am a widow, I have to work
Nosotros tenemos que trabajar, yo soy viuda, tengo que trabajar
我要付房租，还有很多事情。
I have to pay rent, a lot of things.
Tengo que pagar las rentas, un montón de cosas.
而且我会一无所有地离开，而且看不到梅西。
And also I'm leaving with nothing and on top of that without seeing Messi.
Y además me voy sin nada y encima sin ver a Messi.
再见。
Bye bye.
Adiós.
他们说的话让我很受触动。
It kind of hits me what they're saying.
medio que me pega lo que están diciendo.
我们做什么？
What do we do?
¿Qué hacemos?
我已经疯了。
I'm already crazy.
Ya me loco.
哦，她爱，她很好。
Oh, she loves, she is good.
Ay, que ama, es buena.
哈喽，你呢？
Hello, you?
Hola, ¿tú?
嗯，这不可能，因为一切都是...
Well, it can't be, because everything is...
Bueno, no puede estar, porque está todo...
当我母亲还小的时候，你看着自己和她……
You looked at yourself with my mother when she was...
te mirabas usted con mi mamá cuando era...
当我还小的时候，现在他们这样做了，我就不能在场了。
When I was little and now that they do this, I can't be present.
Cuando era chiquito y ahora que hacen esto, yo no puedo estar presente.
但是，嘿，我很高兴孩子们参加了那里并且他们玩得很开心。
But hey, I'm very happy that the kids participated there and that they had a good time.
Pero bueno, me alegro mucho que hayan participado los chicos ahí y que les hayan pasado bien uno.
做这一切的一小会儿，然后给你一个大大的吻
a little while doing all that and give you a big kiss
un ratito haciendo todo eso y darte un beso grande
下一位可能会出现。
The next one may be present.
La próxima puede estar presente.
再见，一个吻。
Bye, a kiss.
Chau, un beso.
非常好，G！
Very good, G!
¡Muy bien, G!
谢谢你们，谢谢你们如此令人难以置信的欢迎。
Thank you, thank you for this incredible welcome.
Gracias, gracias por este recibimiento increíble.
爱与神圣。
of love and divine.
de amor y divino.
我喜欢它。
I love it.
Me encanta.
伊里皮诺把它放回去...
Iripino put it back...
Volvió Iripino a poner...
男孩，他有爪子吗？
Boy, did he have a claw.
Chico, tenía una garra.
我站在那里就感觉到了。
I felt it from standing there.
Yo lo sentía desde ahí parada.
但实际上，我感觉到了，我看到了，这就是能量的来源，你也感觉到了。
But really, I felt it, I saw it, that's where the energy came from, you felt it too.
Pero de verdad, yo la sentía, la veía así de ahí la energía, ustedes la sentían también.
哇！
Wow!
¡Guau!
我有点紧张，因为实际上...
I was kind of nervous because, actually...
Yo estaba medio nerviosa porque, en realidad...
那？
That?
¿Qué?
但不，这一切都是在一起的。
But no, it all went together.
Pero no, iba todo juntos.
春天的费利西亚？
Felicia in the spring?
¿Felicia en la primavera?
不，我不明白。
No, I don't understand.
No, no entiendo.
可能是这样，好吧。
It could be, well.
Podría ser, bueno.
昨天就是昨天，昨天就是昨天，没关系。
It was yesterday, it was yesterday, it was yesterday, it's okay.
Fue ayer, fue ayer, fue ayer, está bien.
春天快乐，野蛮人！
Happy spring day, barbarian!
¡Feliz día de la primavera, bárbaro!
我不知道你是否告诉过我，我明白，但是...
I don't know if you told me that, I understood that, but...
Yo no sé si me dijiste eso, yo entendí eso, pero...
我告诉你...我是。
I tell you... I was.
Les digo que... Estaba.
我也是，我的爱人。
Me too, my love.
Yo también, amor mío.
但预计这会花费您一分钟的时间。
But expect it to take you a minute.
Pero esperen que les cuelte un minuto.
你看到我有多瘦了吧？
You saw how skinny I am, right?
¿Vieron que flaca estoy, no?
这是我想让你看到的第一件事。
That's the first thing I want you to see.
Eso es lo primero que quiero que vean.
等等，等等，我告诉你，我们已经四年半没见面了。
Wait, wait, I'll tell you, we haven't seen each other in four and a half years.
Espera, espera que te cuento Hace cuatro años y medio que no nos vemos
我不敢相信时间过得这么快，天啊。
I can't believe time goes by so quickly, my God.
Yo no puedo creer que se pase tan rápido el tiempo, Dios mío.
但不可思议的是，我什至不告诉你我转了多少次，也不告诉你。
But it's incredible, I don't even tell you how many I turned, nor do I tell you.
Pero es increíble, ni les digo cuántos cumplí, ni les digo.
我不想让任何人知道任何地方。
I don't want anyone to know anywhere.
No quiero que se sepa ningún lado.
没有人知道。
Nobody knows.
Nadie lo sabe.
我举办了一场盛大的派对，所以……我只说一次，然后再见。
I threw a giant party so that... I'll just say it once and bye.
Hice una fiesta gigante para que... Ya lo digo de una vez y chao.
我不介意。
I don't mind.
No me importa.
我知道他们永远爱我，他们也永远同样爱我。
I know that they always love me, they will always love me the same.
Yo sé que me quieren siempre, me van a querer siempre igual.
他们多可爱啊！
How cute they are!
¡Qué lindos que son!
今天我们有一个节目。
And today we have a program.
Y hoy tenemos un programón.
你看到草图是什么了吧？
You saw what the sketch was, right?
¿Vieron lo que fue el sketch, no?
与A.
With the A.
Con la A.
我从未加入过 AFA。
I had never joined the AFA.
Yo nunca había entrado a la AFA.
就像迪士尼、AFA。
It's like Disney, the AFA.
Es como Disney, la AFA.
这是一件令人印象深刻的事情。
It's an impressive thing.
Es una cosa impresionante.
你好，达尼托。
Hello, Danito.
Hola, Danito.
你好吗？
How are you?
¿Cómo estás?
新！
¡Nuevo!
你剪了头发
and you cut your hair
y el pelo te lo cortaste
它或多或少会走多远？
And how far does it go more or less?
¿Y hasta dónde te llega más o menos?
哇，多么野蛮啊。
Wow, how barbaric.
Uy, pero qué bárbaro.
非常非常长。
Very, very long.
Muy, muy largo.
距离你剪掉它已经有多久了？
How long has it been since you cut it?
¿Hace cuánto que no te lo cortas?
四年了。
Four years.
Cuatro años.
哦，四年后我还剩下多少。
Oh, how much I left in four years.
Ay, lo que yo me fui en cuatro años.
四年来我什么也没种。
I didn't grow anything in four years.
A mí no me creció nada en cuatro años.
但你很美丽。
But you are beautiful.
Pero estás hermosa.
噢，谢谢你，我的爱人。
Oh, thank you, my love.
Ay, gracias, mi amor.
他们已经见过面了。
They already met.
Se conocieron ya.
好吧，现在我必须这样做。
Well, now I have to do this.
Bueno, ahora tengo que hacer esto.
这些文件意味着一些山羊。
These papers mean some goat.
Estos papeles significan algún chivito.
¡啊，不！
¡Ah, no!
不！
¡No!
首先我们要感谢所有参与素描的明星们。
First of all we have to thank all the stars who were in the sketch.
Primero de todo hay que agradecerles a todas las estrellas que tuvieron en el sketch.
请！
Please!
¡Por favor!
好吧，让我们开始吧。
Well, let's get started.
Bueno, vamos a empezar.
Chiquitapia，借给我们一切的人，今天生日。
Chiquitapia, who lent us everything, today's birthday.
Chiquitapia, que nos prestó todo, que hoy cumpleaños.
恭喜你，生日快乐，小宝贝。
Congratulations, happy birthday, little one.
Felicidades, feliz cumpleaños, chiqui.
乔吉尼娜·鲁齐、尼科·巴斯克斯、彼得·兰扎尼、索莱达·帕斯托鲁蒂。
Jorginina Ruzzi, Nico Vázquez, Peter Lanzani, Soledad Pastoruti.
吉列尔莫·科波拉、伊万·德·皮内达、卡罗·帕尔迪亚科、塞巴……
Guillermo Coppola, Iván de Pineda, Caro Pardíaco, Seba...
塞巴斯蒂安·斯蒂芬斯、Yayo、约翰·保罗·巴尔斯基、保罗·吉拉尔特、贝图拉、
Sebastian Stephens, Yayo, John Paul Barsky, Paul Giralt, Betular,
Sebastián Estebanís, Yayo, Juan Pablo Barsky, Pablo Giralt, Betular,
塔迪和马里托，是名副其实的世界冠军球员的助手。
Tadi and Marito, who are really the assistants of the World Champions players.
Tadi y Marito, que son de verdad los asistentes de los jugadores de Campeones del Mundo.
罗德里戈·德·保罗和莱安德罗·帕雷德斯。
Rodrigo de Paul and Leandro Paredes.
Rodrigo de Paul y Leandro Paredes.
老实说，我...
Honestly, I...
A verdad, yo...
我是一个足球迷，尤其是世界杯。
And I am a soccer fan, especially the World Cup.
Y soy fanática del fútbol, sobre todo de los mundiales.
所有的世界杯，无论我在路上死了多少，因为人们到达了在车里很棒的地步，然后他们就离开了你
all the World Cups, no matter how much I die walking because one gets to the point where it's great in the car and they leave you
todos los mundiales por más que me muera caminando porque uno llega a bárbaro en el auto y te dejan a
他们告诉你，是的，连续八个街区。
They tell you, yes, eight blocks straight.
Te dicen, sí, ocho cuadras derecho.
他用右手看到那八个人，那是他的位置。
And the eight, he saw with his right, there is his place.
Y lo ocho, vio con la derecha, ahí es su lugar.
八个街区，不会有人。
Eight blocks, there won't be anyone.
Ocho cuadras, no habrá quien.
出租车什么的。
A taxi, something.
Un taxi, algo.
不不。
No no.
No, no.
你必须疯狂地行走。
You have to walk like crazy.
Tienes que caminar como loca.
来这里拜访公众是因为他们被告知......
visiting the public here because they are told...
de visita acá al público porque se le digan...
但有些令人难以置信的访问使我们高举心中的旗帜。
but some visits that cannot be believed, that make us raise the flag of our hearts.
pero unas visitas que no se pueden creer, que nos hacen salir la bandera del corazón.
一切。
Everything.
Todo.
他们是世界冠军和两届美国冠军。
They are world champions and two-time champions of America.
Son campeones del mundo y bicampeones de América.
莱安德罗·帕雷德斯·罗德里戈·德波尔！
Leandro Paredes Rodrigo de Pol!
¡Leandro Paredes Rodrigo de Pol!
那！
That!
Eso!
他们怎么知道的？
How did they know?
¿Cómo sabían?
你好我的爱人。
Hello my love.
Hola mi amor.
非常好，非常好，非常好，非常好，非常好，非常好。
Very good, very good, very good, very good, very good, very good.
Muy bien, muy bien, muy bien, muy bien, muy bien, muy bien.
他们怎么知道的？
How did they know?
¿Cómo sabían?
他们怎么知道拥有整件阿根廷球衣？
How did they know to have the entire Argentine shirt?
¿Cómo sabían tener toda la camiseta argentina?
等待！
Wait!
¡Esperen!
等待！
Wait!
¡Esperen!
等等，我一会儿再跟他说！
Wait, I'll talk to him later!
¡Espera, después le hablo!
等一下！
Wait a minute!
¡Esperen un minuto!
但你知道，不，他们不会让我说话。
But you know, no, they're not going to let me talk.
Pero vos sabés, no, no me van a dejar hablar.
嗯，我们坐下了。
Well, we sat down.
Bueno, nos sentamos.
于是，我们坐下了。
So, we sat down.
Entonces, nos sentamos.
我们坐在这里，来了。
We sit here, coming.
Nos sentamos acá, venilando.
我不知道这些地方，我不知道。
I don't know the places, I don't know.
No sé los lugares, no sé.
我有，我的在这里，你的也在这里，无论你想要谁。
I have it, mine is here, yours is here, whoever you want.
Yo tengo, yo el mío está acá, el de ustedes acá, el que quieran.
就在那里。
There it is.
Ahí está.
这是多么优雅啊。
How elegant it is.
Que elegante que está.
他们必须让我问他们问题，因为我想知道一些事情。
They have to let me ask them things because I want to know things.
Me tienen que dejar que les pregunte cosas porque yo quiero saber cosas.
我们了解关于足球的一切。
We know everything about football.
Sabemos todo lo del fútbol.
我不明白他们。
I don't understand them.
No les entiendo.
好吧，事实是我想了解关于你的事情。
Well, the truth is that I want to know things about you.
Bueno, la verdad que yo quiero saber cosas de ustedes.
因为每个人都知道足球的一部分，他们是冠军，他们是国家。
because everyone knows the football part, they are champions, they are the country.
porque todo el mundo conoce la parte de fútbol, son campeones, son la patria.
祖国，因为我相信没有一个国家像这个国家一样热爱足球。
The homeland, because I believe that there is no country as passionate about football as this one.
La patria, porque yo creo que no existe un país tan futbolero como este.
我不这么认为，你们在欧洲踢球的人看不到这一点。
I don't think so, you who play in Europe don't see this.
Yo creo que no, ustedes que juegan en Europa, no ven esto.
这里充满激情，不，不。
The passion that is lived here, no, no.
La pasión de que se vive acá, no, no.
这是...发生在我们身上的事情是已经...
It's a thing of... What happens to us is that already...
Es una cosa de... Lo que nos pasa a nosotros es que ya...
四五年了。
four or five years.
cuatro o cinco años.
我不知道，你不能……你能不能安心去餐馆吃饭？
I don't know, you can't... Can you go eat in a restaurant in peace or not?
No sé, no se puede... ¿Pueden ir a comer en un restaurante ustedes tranquilos o no?
在我们必须生活的一切、我们必须实现的目标之后，这是非常困难的
It is very difficult after everything we had to live, what we had to achieve
Es muy difícil después de todo lo que nos tocó vivir, lo que nos tocó conseguir
这是非常困难的，但同时也是非常愉快的，因为一个人也梦想着这一点并且能够实现它
It is very difficult but well it is also very enjoyable because one also dreamed of this and being able to live it
es muy difícil pero bueno también se disfruta mucho porque uno también soñaba con esto y poder vivirlo
他们做到了，伙计们。
And they did it, guys.
Y lo lograron, chicos.
给我印象最深的是两人...
What impressed me most is that the two...
A mí lo que más me impresionó es que los dos...
他们三岁时就进入俱乐部踢球。
They entered the club to play when they were three years old.
entraron al club a jugar a los tres años.
你曾经是弓箭手，对吧？
You were an archer, right?
Vos eras arquero, ¿no?
守门员。
Goalkeeper.
Arquero.
他们不让我上场，因为我太小了，所以他们把我送到了球门。
They didn't let me play because I was very little and so they sent me to the goal.
A mí no me dejaban jugar porque era muy chiquito y entonces me mandaron al arco.
但是，嘿，有人挺身而出，我得以采取行动。
But hey, someone stepped up and I was able to make a move.
Pero bueno, alguien se avivó y me pude apantar una jugada.
他们停止了比赛，让他可以撒尿，可怜的家伙，因为他没有尿布。
They stopped the game so he could pee, poor guy, because he didn't have diapers.
que paraban el partido para que haga pipí, pobrecito, porque pañales no tenía.
不，我没有。
No, I didn't have one.
No, no tenía.
我在拱门里睡着了。
I fell asleep in the arch.
Me quedaba dormido en el arco.
我真是个有性格的人。
I was quite a character.
Yo era bastante personaje.
但是，嘿，作为一个孩子，我更不感到羞耻。
But hey, as a kid I was even less ashamed.
Pero bueno, de chico tenía menos vergüenza todavía.
显然，3年并不是一个很长的时间。
3 years is not a long time, obviously.
3 años no es de un tiempo, obvio.
你母亲所做的事业鼓励了你。
encouraged your career that your mother has done.
incentivó tu carrera que lo ha hecho tu mamá.
是的，妈妈陪了我很多。
Yes, my mom accompanied me a lot.
Sí, mi mamá me acompañó un montón.
那要了我的命。
That kills me.
Eso me mata.
直到今天都还好。
Good until today.
Bueno hasta el día de hoy.
事实上，我妈妈喜欢它......好吧，我现在住在西班牙，她经常去马德里，但是......
The truth is that my mother loves it... Well, I now live in Spain, she goes to Madrid a lot, but...
La verdad es que a mi vieja le encanta... Bueno, yo ahora vivo en España, va mucho a Madrid, pero...
卡塔尔，现在是美国，我的意思是，她无处不在。
Qatar, now the United States, I mean, she goes everywhere.
Catar, ahora Estados Unidos, digo, ella va a todos lados.
它无处不在，它跟着你。
It goes everywhere, it follows you.
Va a todos lados, te sigue.
她到处走，不会错过任何人。
She goes everywhere, she doesn't miss anyone.
Ella a todos lados, no se pierde ninguno.
哦，我的爱人，我的爱人。
Oh, my love, my love.
Ay, mi amor, mi amor.
显然，他经常和他的母亲在一起。
a lot with his mother, obviously.
mucho con la mamá de él, obvio.
你妈妈也去吗？
Is your mom going too?
¿También va su mamá?
你的驱动力是你的祖父奥斯瓦尔多。
And your drive was your grandfather Osvaldo.
Y a vos el empuje tuyo fue tu abuelo Osvaldo.
不，相反。
No, the other way around.
No, al revés.
哦，抱歉。
Oh, sorry.
Ah, perdón.
爷爷陪伴了我很长时间。
My grandfather accompanied me for a long time.
Mi abuelo me acompañó mucho tiempo.
我以为我对他的看法是错误的。
I thought I was wrong about his.
Yo pensé que el de él me equivoqué.
所以你的祖父，因为你有你的祖父纹身，我有我的祖父纹身，我有他在这里，当他进入球场时，我总是给他一个吻
So your grandfather, because you have your grandfather tattooed I have my grandfather tattooed, I have him here I always give him a kiss when he enters the field
Entonces tu abuelo, porque vos lo tenés tatuado a tu abuelo Yo tengo tatuado a mi abuelo, lo tengo acá Siempre le doy un beso cuando entra a la cancha
哦，我的爱人。
Oh, my love.
Ay, mi amor.
是的，我只剩下这个了……我们不能展示它，闭嘴。
Yes, I'm left with that... We can't show it, shut up.
Sí, a mí me queda eso de que... No lo podemos mostrar, cállense la voz.
是的！
Yeah!
¡Sí!
有很多人。
There are many people.
Hay mucha gente.
他们很疯狂，很多女孩都想脱掉他们的衣服。
They are crazy, many girls want to undress them.
Están locas, muchas chicas quieren desnudarlos.
你的母亲莫妮卡呢？
And your mother, Monica?
¿Y vos tu mamá, Mónica?
不，莫妮卡是他的。
No, Monica was his.
No, Mónica era de él.
来吧，上来吧。
Come on, come up.
Dale, sube.
看来你过得很不好。
It seems like you had a bad time.
Parece que te pasaron mal.
等一下。
Hang on a minute.
Espera un momento.
不可能是我第一天就犯了错误。
It can't be that I made a mistake on the first day.
No puede ser que el primer día yo me equivoque.
不可能，他们会杀了我。
It can't be, they're going to kill me.
No puede ser, me van a matar.
但我读了再见，因为我看不到。
But I read the bye because I can't.
Pero yo leo el chao porque no puedo.
莫妮卡让他加入了俱乐部。
Monica enrolled him in the club.
Mónica lo inscribió en el club.
来自萨兰迪亚的贝尔格拉诺三年了，这就是我说的完美，他们叫他生菜
the belgrano from zarandía for three years, that's what I said perfectly, they called him lettuce
el belgrano de zarandía los tres años eso lo dije perfecto le decían lechuga
现在他们叫他...为什么他们叫你生菜？
Now they called him... Why did they call you lettuce?
Ahora le decían... ¿Por qué te decían lechuga?
一位在阿根廷电视台工作的弓箭手，名叫“生菜罗阿”。
By an archer who worked on Argentine television and called lettuce roa.
Por un arquero que trabajaba en la televisión argentina y llamaba lechuga roa.
哦，你喜欢吗？
Oh, did you like it?
Ah, ¿te gustaba?
当然，我看了一下，是的。
Of course, I looked at it, yes.
Claro, yo lo miraba, sí.
啊，我的爱人。
Ah, my love.
Ah, mi amor.
现在他们叫你小马达。
And now they call you little motor.
Y ahora te dicen motorcito.
现在他们给了我小马达，是的。
And now they gave me the little motor, yes.
Y ahora me pusieron el motorcito, sí.
因为你跑得像兔子一样。
Because you run like a rabbit.
Porque corres como un conejo.
我想这就是原因，是的。
I think that's why, yes.
Creo que es por eso, sí.
对我来说，兔子与小马达无关。
For me the rabbit has nothing to do with the little motor.
Para mí el conejo no tiene nada que ver con el motorcito.
哦，告诉我为什么他称它为小马达。
Oh, tell me why he calls it a little motor.
Ay, decime por qué le dice motorcito.
因为汽车的发动机，这使得...
Because of the car's engine, which is what makes...
Por el motor del auto, que es el que hace que...
你觉得吗？
Seem to you?
¿Te parece?
他在撒谎。
He's lying.
Está mintiendo.
它是楼梯的引擎。
It is the engine of the staircase.
Es el motor de la escaloneta.
我发誓吗？
Do I swear?
¿Te juro?
当然。
Of course.
Claro.
他们告诉我一些有关此事的信息。
And they tell me a little about that.
Y me dicen un poco por eso.
您有一台专门用于糖果的相机。
You have a camera that is the one for candy.
Ustedes tienen una cámara que es la de los caramelos.
我不知道，我发誓我看了所有的比赛，我参加了所有的世界杯。
And I didn't know that, I swear I watch all the games, I go to all the World Cups.
Y yo esa no lo sabía, te juro que veo todos los partidos, voy a todos los mundiales.
我做了一切，但是...我们在卡塔尔见到了你。
I did everything, but... We saw you in Qatar.
Hice todo, pero... Te vimos en Catar.
是的。
Yeah.
Sí.
因为我们总是让你伴着国歌。
Because we always had you there with the anthem.
Porque siempre con el himno te teníamos ahí.
哦真的吗？
Oh really?
¿En serio?
是的。
Yeah.
Sí.
我喜欢它，我喜欢它，我喜欢它，我喜欢它，这太令人兴奋了，上帝我......
I loved it, I loved it, I loved it, I loved it, it was exciting, God I...
Me encantó, me encantó, me encantó, me encantó, fue emocionante, Dios me...
糖果怎么样？
How was the candy?
¿Cómo fue lo de los caramelos?
是怎么开始的？
How did it start?
¿Cómo empezó?
我认为它是在 2019 年美洲杯之后开始的。
I think it started after the 2019 Copa América.
Arrancó creo que después de la Copa América 2019.
我们从那只山羊开始，保罗也和迪巴拉一起，然后好吧，在 2021 年杯赛中他无法参加，但是......
We started with that goat with Paulo too, with Dibala, then well, in the 2021 Cup he couldn't be there, but...
que arrancamos con esa cabra con Paulo también, con Dibala, después bueno, en la Copa de 2021 él no pudo estar, pero...
但我们从那一刻开始，一直延续到今天。
But we started at that moment and we follow it to this day.
Pero nosotros arrancamos en ese momento y hasta el día de hoy la seguimos.
我们到达，我们去更衣室。
We arrive, we go to the locker room.
Llegamos, vamos al vestuario.
这取决于天气是热还是冷。
It depends if it's hot or cold.
Depende si hace calor o frío.
我们换了衬衫等等，然后我们两个人拿着糖果单独进去了。
We changed our shirts and so on and then the two of us went in alone with the candy.
nos cambiamos la remera y demás y ahí entramos los dos solos con los caramelos.
你已经从家里带来它们了吗？
Do you already bring them from home?
¿Ustedes ya los traen de su casa?
不，糖果就在那里。
No, the candy is there.
No, están ahí los caramelos.
每个人都选择自己吃的糖果。
Each one chooses the candy they eat.
Cada uno elige los caramelos que come.
我们前往球场中央。
We make the journey to the middle of the court.
Hacemos el recorrido hasta la mitad de la cancha.
我们总是用同一只脚进入。
We always enter with the same foot.
Entramos siempre con el mismo pie.
它叫什么？
What's it called?
¿Cómo se llama?
关于这个领域、关于这个人的一些特别的事情，让我们看看天气怎么样。
something in particular about the field, about the people, let's see what the weather is like.
alguna cosa en particular de la cancha, de la gente, a ver cómo está el clima.
是的。
Yeah.
Sí.
我们寻找家人在哪里。
We look for where the family is.
Buscamos a dónde está la familia.
是的。
Yeah.
Sí.
他们会在附近吃它们。
And they eat them near them.
Y se los comen cerca de ellos.
是的，我们总是在那里吃。
Yes, we always eat them there.
Sí, los comemos siempre ahí.
好吧，一旦我们完成了它们，我们就转身。
And well, once we finish them, we turn around.
Y bueno, una vez que los terminamos, damos la vuelta.
你吃几个？
How many do you eat?
¿Cuántos te comes vos?
我吃14个
I eat 14.
Yo me como 14.
哇！
Wow!
¡Guau!
多么令人印象深刻啊！
How impressive!
¡Qué impresionante!
它不会伤害你，对吧？
It doesn't hurt you, right?
No te hace mal, ¿no?
不，这不明显。
No, it's not noticeable.
No, no se nota.
我七。
I seven.
Yo siete.
而他七。
And he seven.
Y él siete.
你七岁吗？
Are you seven?
¿Vos siete?
除了颜色相同之外，它们都很棒。
Apart from the same colors, they are awesome.
Aparte los mismos colores, son cabaladas.
相同颜色的。
of the same colors.
de los mismos colores.
他跟我说，他们太可怕了，现在更可怕了
With me he told me, they are terrible, now it is terrible
Conmigo me dijo, son terribles, ahora es terrible
女性公众的问题是因为你不能走在街上。
the problem with the female public because you can't walk down the street.
el problema con el público femenino porque ustedes no pueden caminar por la calle.
他们太可怕了，太可怕了，太可怕了，太可怕了。
They are terrible, they are terrible, terrible, terrible.
Son terribles, son terribles, terribles, terribles.
国旗、国家，都浮现在我的面前。
The flag, the country, comes out to me.
A mí me sale la bandera, la patria.
你这人怎么回事？
What's wrong with you?
¿A ustedes qué les pasa?
我知道他们很可爱，我知道他们很可爱，但是……
I know they're cute, I know they're cute, but...
Yo sé que son lindos, yo sé que son lindos, pero...
你在说什么？
What are you saying?
¿Qué dices?
我想要一个放在我的床头柜上。
I want one for my nightstand.
Yo quiero uno para mi mesa de luz.
不不。
No no.
No, no.
¿只有一个？
¿Only one?
¿Uno solo?
听着，不，不，还有颜色，因为糖果必须是彩色的，例如，你的......
Listen, no, no, and the colors, because the candies have to be colored, for example, yours are...
oíme no no y los colores porque tienen que ser de colores los caramelos por ejemplo los tuyos son que
有四个蓝色和三个黄色。
There are four blue and three yellow.
Son cuatro azules y tres amarillos.
你的和我的都有不同的颜色，以免四处乱立
and yours, mine are of various varied colors so as not to go around erecting
y los tuyos los míos son de varios colores variados para no andar erigiendo
不不，我总是选择同样的事情，但他们总是……
No, no, I always choose the same thing, but they are always...
No, no, elijo siempre lo mismo, pero son siempre...
完美的。
Perfect.
Perfecto.
我不知道，我发誓。
I didn't know that, I swear.
Eso no lo sabía, te juro.
好吧，防故障，对吧？
Well, failsafe, right?
Bueno, mecanismo de seguridad, ¿no?
当然，阴谋集团。
Of course, cabals.
Por supuesto, cábalas.
是的，我们感觉更多......这并不意味着我们会通过这样做来获胜，但是我们...... 14 队给我带来了压力，因为这就像......
Yes, we feel more... It doesn't mean that we're going to win by doing that, but we... The 14 put pressure on me because it's like a...
Sí, nosotros nos sentimos más... No quiere decir que vamos a ganar haciendo eso, pero nosotros... Los 14 me presionan porque es como un...
不，但是走……不，一一走。
No, but go... No, one by one.
No, pero anda... No, de a uno.
但有十四个相同。
But there are fourteen the same.
Pero son catorce igual.
有时我还没吃完。
Sometimes I don't finish eating them.
A veces no los termino de comer.
事实是，我把这三个都留在口袋里了，我要把它们抛在身后。
The truth is, I have all three left in my pocket and I'm leaving them behind.
La verdad, me quedan todos tres en el bolsillo y ya los dejo.
后来，当我们进入更衣室时，我们就走路了。
Later, when we entered the locker room, we walked.
Después, cuando entramos al vestuario, nos caminamos.
我们很快就到了。
We are soon.
Estamos pronto.
在那里你会感到安全。
And there you feel safe.
Y ahí te sentís seguro.
当然，莱安德罗，你已经结婚了，正在生孩子
of course leandro you are married expecting a baby
por supuesto leandro vos estás casado esperando un bebé
是的，不，我还没告诉过，但是……哦，抱歉。
Yes, no, I hadn't told it yet, but... Oh, sorry.
Sí, no, no lo había contado todavía, pero... Ay, perdón.
看，他们告诉我的，所以他知道。
Look, they told me, so he knows.
Mira, a mí me lo dijeron, o sea que sabe.
亲爱的！
My love!
¡Mi amor!
摆脱布布苏埃拉！
Get rid of the bubusuela!
¡Sáquenle el de la bubusuela!
请。
Please.
Por favor.
布布塞拉，沉默。
Bubucela, silence.
好吧，听我说，我喜欢它。
Well, listen to me, I loved it.
Bueno, escúchame, me encantó.
当卡米拉还是你的时候你就爱上了她
You fell in love with Camila when she was...
Vos te enamoraste de Camila cuando tenia...
当我八岁的时候，我爱上了她。
I was eight years old when I fell in love with her.
Yo tenía ocho años cuando me enamoré de ella.
亲爱的。
My love.
Mi amor.
你把它纹在脖子上了。
You tattooed it on your neck.
Vos te la tatuaste en el cuello.
而她却没有给你任何想法。
And she didn't give you any thought.
Y ella no te daba bolilla.
在她成为我女朋友之前我给她纹身了，是的。
I got her tattooed before she was my girlfriend, yes.
Me la tatué antes de que sea mi novia, sí.
这就是原因。
That's why.
Por eso.
换句话说，你感觉你要打败他。
In other words, you felt like you were going to beat him.
O sea, te sentías que le ibas a ganar.
我感觉她将成为我生命中的女人。
I felt like she was going to be the woman of my life.
Yo sentía que iba a ser la mujer de mi vida.
哦，我的爱人！
Oh, my love!
¡Ay, mi amor!
多么神圣，它让我温柔。
How divine, it makes me tender.
Qué divino, me da ternura.
好吧，那我就和她一起生活，纹身。
Well, then I live it with her, the tattoo.
Bueno, entonces con ella lo vivo, el tatuaje.
他开始哭了吗？
Did he start crying?
¿Se puso a llorar?
他开始哭泣，是的。
He started crying, yes.
Se puso a llorar, sí.
他开始给我更多的球。
He started to give me a little more ball.
Me empezó a dar un poquito más de bola.
哦，当然。
Oh, of course.
Ay, claro.
而那个具体的，他可以展示它，因为他把它挂在脖子上。
And that specific one, he can show it because he has it on his neck.
Y ese concreto, ese lo puede mostrar porque lo tiene en el cuello.
然后他展示了它。
Then he shows it.
Después lo muestra.
但后来他们结婚了，他们结婚的时候你16岁
But then they got married, when they got married, you were 16
Pero después se casaron, cuando se pusieron de novios, vos tenés 16
那年我14岁，她16岁。
I was 14, she was 16.
Yo tenía 14, ella 16.
16岁，她和你14岁。
16, she and you 14.
16, ella y vos 14.
哦，我的爱人。
Oh, my love.
Ay, mi amor.
从那时起直到今天我们都在一起。
And from then until today we are together.
Y de ahí hasta el día de hoy estamos juntos.
多好啊！
How nice!
¡Qué lindo!
这是第一个孩子吗？
And is it the first baby?
¿Y es el primer bebé?
不，这是第三个。
No, it's the third.
No, es el tercero.
啊，第三个。
Ah, the third.
Ah, el tercero.
是的，我有两个女儿。
Yes, I have two girls.
Sí, tengo dos nenas.
一个10岁的女孩，一个7岁的男孩。
A 10-year-old girl, a 7-year-old boy.
Una nena de 10 años, un nene de 7.
现在我们正在等待。
And now we are waiting.
Y ahora estamos esperando.
哦，我的爱人，很高兴。
Oh, my love, well delighted.
Ay, mi amor, pues encantado.
他们都有大家庭吧？
They all have big families, huh?
Todos tienen familias grandes, ¿eh?
我们喜欢它，我们喜欢它。
We like it, we like it.
Nos gusta, nos gusta.
当然，疯狂。
Sure, crazy.
Claro, loco.
我们仍然不知道这是男孩还是女孩。
We still don't know if it's a boy or a girl.
No sabemos todavía si es varón o nena.
他们什么都不知道。
They don't know anything.
No saben nada.
你是或者你将成为叔叔和教父吗？
Are you or are you going to be the uncle and the godfather?
¿Vos o vas a ser el tío y el padrino?
而教父，在我看来，我要留给别人了。
And the godfather, it seems to me, I'm going to leave to someone else.
Y el padrino, me parece, se lo voy a dejar a otro.
因为，完全...
Because, totally...
Porque, total...
以我拥有的能量，宝宝会相信他和我在一起，所以......
With the energy I have, the baby is going to believe that he is with me, so...
Con la energía que tengo el nene va a creer o nena va a creer que está conmigo, así que...
我死了。
I die.
Yo muero.
你有两个。
You have two.
Vos tenés dos.
我有两个。
I have two.
Yo tengo dos.
作为父母，他们是多么深情、非常善良、充满爱心。
And as parents, how they are affectionate, very good, loving.
Y como padres, como son cariñosos, buenísimos, amorosos.
我很热情，事实是。
I am very affectionate, the truth is.
Yo soy muy cariñoso, la verdad.
嗯，还有一点我的生活经历。
Well, also a bit of the experience that I lived.
Bueno, también un poco la experiencia que yo viví.
再见，我试着...
Bye bye, I try like...
Bye bye, intento como...
那个版本改进很多，对吧？
Improve that version a lot, right?
Mejorar mucho esa versión, ¿no?
是的。
Yeah.
Sí.
所以，是的，实际上非常深情，我们有一种纽带。
So yes, very affectionate, actually, and we have a bond.
Así que sí, muy cariñas, a la verdad, y tenemos un vínculo.
哦，我的爱人。
Oh, my love.
Ay, mi amor.
我们俩都令人难以置信，而且我们玩得很开心
incredible with both of us and well we enjoyed ourselves a lot
increíble con los dos y bueno nos disfrutamos mucho
但是，例如，您在西班牙比赛。
But live, for example, you play in Spain.
Pero vive, por ejemplo, vos jugás en España.
我住在西班牙马德里。
I live in Spain, in Madrid.
Yo vivo en España, en Madrid.
好吧，他们在阿根廷。
And well, they are here in Argentina.
Y bueno, ellos están acá en Argentina.
他们旅行来看你。
They travel to see you.
Viajan a verte.
他们经常旅行，几乎总是和我母亲一起。
They travel a lot, almost always with my mother.
Viajan un montón, casi siempre con mi mamá.
当然。
Of course.
Claro.
当布宜诺斯艾利斯、马德里...
When Buenos Aires, Madrid...
A la hora de que Buenos Aires, Madrid...
很远啊
It's far.
Es lejos.
是的，很远，但因为这是一次独自旅行，而且……不间断。
Yes, it's far, but since it's a solo trip and... Non-stop.
Sí, es lejos, pero como es un viaje solo y... Sin escalas.
精确的。
Exact.
Exacto.
这相当复杂。
That's pretty complicated.
Eso es bastante complicado.
嗯，他们喜欢来马德里，所以他们经常来。
Well, and they love coming to Madrid, so they come a lot.
Bueno, y ellos aman venir para Madrid, entonces vienen mucho.
他们说话有点像那样，然后...不，不，他们问我，他们告诉我，看看如何用西班牙语说这个。
And they talk a little like that, then... No, no, they ask me, they tell me, to see how to say this in Spanish.
Y hablan un poco así, después... No, no, ellos me piden, me dicen, a ver cómo se dice esto en español.
然后我们也经常随国家队出场。
And then we come a lot with the national team too.
Y después venimos mucho con la selección también.
当然，感谢上帝。
Sure, thank God.
Claro, gracias a Dios.
我们几乎一直在一起，他们来到这里。
And there we are practically together all the time, they come to the property.
Y ahí prácticamente estamos todo el tiempo juntos, ellos se vienen al predio.
他们喜欢球场上的所有人。
They adore them all on the court.
a ellos, a todos ellos los adoran en la cancha.
他们一定非常自豪，非常自豪。
They must be so proud, so proud.
Tienen que estar tan orgullosos, tan orgullosos.
是的，至少对我来说，嗯。
Yes, at least for me, well.
Sí, a mí por lo menos sí, bueno.
是的，对吧？
And yes, right?
Y sí, ¿no?
是的，我真的这么做。
Yes, I really do.
Sí, de verdad que sí.
你看起来更严肃了。
You seem more serious.
Vos parecés más serio.
不不。
No no.
No, no.
我比较害羞。
I'm more shy.
Soy más tímido.
停下来，你害羞了吗？
Stop, are you shy?
Para, ¿sos tímido?
你是认真的还是不认真的？
Are you serious or not?
¿Serio o no?
你是认真的还是不认真的？
Are you serious or not?
¿Serio o no?
嗯，不过好像，好像。
Well, but it seems, it seems.
Bueno, pero parece, parece.
另一方面，你更善于交际，对吧？
You, on the other hand, are more sociable, let's say, right?
vos, en cambio, sos más sociable, digamos, ¿no?
硬面具。
Hard mask.
Máscara dura.
硬质面膜，不错。
Hard mask, good.
Máscara dura, bueno.
但我喜欢这样，一切看起来都是这样。
But I love that, that it all seems like that.
Pero me encanta eso, que parezca todo así.
我们一起演了一个小品。
We did a skit together.
Hicimos un sketch juntos.
这就是作为演员的感受。
That is, as actors, how they felt.
O sea, como actores, cómo se sintieron.
很舒服，事实是我以为情况会更糟，但我们玩得很开心。
Quite comfortable, the truth is that I thought it was going to be worse and we had a great time.
Bastante cómoda, la verdad que pensé que iba a ser peor y la pasamos muy bien.
但事实是他们给了我们很多帮助。
But the reality is that they helped us a lot.
Pero la realidad es que nos ayudaron mucho.
当然，还有我……演员们。
Of course, and I... The actors.
Claro, y yo... Los actores.
是的。
Yeah.
Sí.
他们帮助了我们很多。
They helped us a lot.
Nos ayudaron un montón.
不，但你们都很棒。
No, but you guys were great.
No, pero ustedes estuvieron geniales.
是的，但不，这是一个……你可以掌控自己的地方。
Yes, but no, it's a place where... Where you can handle yourself.
Sí, pero no, es un lugar en el que... En el que ustedes se puedan manejar.
一切就这样出来了，嘭，嘭。
It all came out like that, bam, bam.
salía todo así, pim, pam.
是的，好吧，但是对虾进行按摩是一种乐趣，他们有......
Yes, well, but there was the pleasure of doing a massage on the shrimp, which they have...
Sí, bueno, pero estuvo el placer de hacer un masaje en la gamba, que la tienen...
看，腿，就像一瞬间。
Look, the legs, it's like a moment.
Mira, las piernas, es como a momento.
双腿就像拥抱着大教堂的柱子。
The legs are like hugging the column of the cathedral.
Las piernas es como abrazar la columna de la catedral.
他们没有脂肪，但无处可去。
They have no fat, but nowhere.
No tienen grasa, pero por ningún lado.
女孩们，我们必须奔跑。
Girls, we have to run.
Chicas, hay que correr.
你必须像这样跑步，你必须锻炼，因为它令人印象深刻。
You have to run like these, you have to exercise because it is impressive.
Hay que correr como estos, hay que hacer ejercicio porque es impresionante.
当然，他们很年轻，但仍然。
Of course, they are very young, but still.
Por supuesto, son muy jóvenes, pero igual.
他们歌唱自己头发的外观变化。
They sing about the changes in looks they make with their hair.
cantan los cambios de looks que hacen en el pelo.
野蛮？
¿Brutal?
你改变更多，对吗？
You change more, right?
Vos cambias más, ¿no?
但你却像时尚一样强加。
but you impose like a fashion.
pero ustedes imponen como una moda.
我在街上看到像你一样的人。
I see people on the street who are like you.
Yo veo gente por la calle que está como ustedes.
好吧，我认为这也是我们所处的时刻，阿根廷队正在产生很大的影响。
And well, I think it's also a bit of the moment we're in, where the squad is, the Argentine team is having a lot of impact.
Y bueno, yo creo que también es un poco del momento en el que estamos, en el que está la escaloneta, la selección argentina, está impactando mucho.
很多，但是我真的很喜欢
a lot but yes I really like it
un montón pero sí a mí me gusta la verdad que
我很开心，我玩得很长，也很短。
I have fun, I had it long, short.
Me divierto, lo tuve largo, corto.
这对你来说看起来很残酷。
That's how it looks brutal on you.
Así te queda brutal.
这片空地对你来说看起来很残酷，他也是如此。
The clearing looks brutal on you and so does he.
El claro te queda brutal y él también.
是的，还有那双小眼睛。
Yes, with those little eyes.
Sí, con esos ojitos.
不，用眼睛看可能会更黑。
No, with the eyes it could look darker.
No, con los ojos le puede quedar bien más oscuro.
我们这样做也是出于无聊，有时是集中精力，就像我们不知道该做什么，我们就去染色。
We also do it out of boredom, sometimes in concentrations, like loads that we don't know what to do, we go and get dyed.
Lo hacemos también de aburrido, a veces en las concentraciones, como cargas que no sabemos qué hacer, vamos y nos teñimos.
谁给它们染色？
And who dyes them?
¿Y quién los teñe?
问题是什么？
What is the problem?
¿ Cuál es el problema?
因为他们总是表现得无可挑剔，这里的一切都是赤裸裸的，有些事情和谈论狮子座。
because they always come out as impeccable, here everything is bare and some things and talking about Leo.
porque siempre salen como impecables, acá todo peladito y unas cosas y hablando de Leo.
他们想念他，他们将会想念他，我不知道那是什么感觉。
They missed him, they are going to miss him, I don't know what it was like.
Lo extrañaron, lo van a extrañar, no sé cómo fue.
你们是朋友，非常朋友。
You are friends, very friends.
Ustedes son amigos, muy amigos.
事实是，是的，我们想念他。
The truth is, yes, we miss him.
La verdad que sí, lo extrañamos.
没有它很奇怪，没有国际棋联也很奇怪，这是......
It was strange not having it, it was strange not having FIDE too, which was...
Fue raro no tenerlo, fue raro no tener a FIDE también, que era...
对于我们来说，在团队中，尤其是在我们团队中，有一个人非常重要，他是团队中的一员。
For us, someone is very important in the group, especially in ours, who is one of
para nosotros alguien muy importante en el grupo más en el nuestro que es uno de
最重要的，没有它们很奇怪。
of the most important and it was strange not having them.
de los más importantes y fue raro no tenerlos.
但当他出场时，他们在决赛中给了他一脚。
But it was when he came out that they gave him the kick in the final.
Pero sí fue cuando salió que le dieron la patada esa en la final.
是的，在决赛中他出来哭了，你拥抱他并安慰他，我们都哭了。
Yes, in the final he came out and was crying and you hugged him and consoled him and we all cried.
Sí, en la final salió y lloraba y vos lo abrazaste y lo consolaste y todos llorábamos.
那一刻我什至不想看她。
I didn't even want to look at her at that moment.
No la quería ni mirar en ese momento.
我知道，因为显然这对他来说一定是这样的。
I know, because what it must have been like for him, obviously.
Ya sé, porque lo que debe haber sido para él, obvio.
非常强。
Very strong.
Muy fuerte.
而且，利奥，从这个意义上来说……
Besides, Leo, in that sense...
Aparte, Leo, en ese sentido...
他不那么外向，他更多地用...
He is not so demonstrative, he demonstrates more with...
no es tan demostrativo, él demuestra más con...
采取一些行动，而不是采取太多行动……当然。
with some action and not so much with... Of course.
con alguna acción y no tanto con... Por supuesto.
它哭起来一定是太热了。
For it to cry it must have been really hot.
Para que llore tiene que haber estado re caliente.
不，但我喜欢这种温柔，你看，就好像他们愿意一样，没有人与任何人竞争。
No, but I liked the tenderness, you see, that as if they wanted, no one competes with anyone.
No, pero me gustó la ternura, viste, de que como si quieren, nadie compite con nadie.
有一种东西是纯洁的，你可以看到这一点。
There is a thing of purity, you can see that.
Hay una cosa de pureza, se ve eso.
我们一直都明白...
We always understood that...
Nosotros entendimos siempre que...
他是洛阿科队的队长。
He is the captain of Loarco.
Él es el capitán de Loarco.
更重要的是，我们很高兴这样做，我们希望他永远成为所有报纸的封面人物，我们在后面推动。
What's more, we do it with pleasure, we want him to always be the cover of all the newspapers and we push from behind.
Es más, lo hacemos con gusto, queremos que él siempre sea la tapa de todos los diarios y nosotros empujando desde atrás.
太棒了。
It's wonderful.
Es maravilla.
那不存在。
That doesn't exist.
Eso no existe.
不，它不存在。
No, it doesn't exist.
No, no existe.
至少在我们这个行业是这样。
At least in our profession.
Por lo menos en nuestra profesión.
在足球中也存在很多自我问题，事实是这支球队，我不知道，就像一个谜题，
In football there are also many ego issues and the truth is that this team, I don't know, was like a puzzle that
en el fútbol también hay muchos temas de egos y la verdad que esta selección no sé fue como un rompecabezas que
每件作品都完美地组合在一起，今天你一个人去。
each piece fit together perfectly, today you go alone.
cada pieza encajó a la perfección, hoy vas solo.
有很多努力，但是我们都非常互补，每个人都有很好的作用。
There are many efforts, but we all complement each other very well and each one has a very good role.
Hay muchos esfuerzos, pero nos complementamos todos muy bien y cada uno tiene un rol muy bueno.
很好，很好，显示出来，穿过屏幕，显示出来，显示出来。
That's good, that's good, that shows and goes through the screen, it shows, it shows.
que bueno, que bueno, eso se nota y traspasa la pantalla, se nota, se nota.
它非常引人注目，而且非常棒。
It is very noticeable and it is fabulous.
Se nota muchísimo y es fabuloso.
我认为也许斯卡罗尼也与此有很大关系。
And I think that maybe Scaloni had a lot to do with that too.
Y yo pienso que a lo mejor Scaloni tuvo mucho que ver en eso también.
它是如此严肃、如此完美、如此……
It's so serious and so perfect and so...
es tan serio y tan perfecto y tan...
当他拥抱儿子哭泣时，我也感到温柔，明白吗？
And I also feel tender when he hugs his son and cries, see?
Y también me da ternura cuando abraza al hijo y llora, ¿viste?
那天他杀了我们所有人。
That day he killed us all.
Ese día nos mató a todos.
不知道你记不记得，我不记得那是什么游戏了。
I don't know if you remember, I don't remember what game it was.
no sé si ustedes se acuerdan, no me acuerdo el partido que fue.
决赛结束后他还给了他一个非常有力的拥抱
He also had a very strong hug with him after the final that came out all over
Él también tuvo un abrazo muy fuerte con él después de la final que salió en todo
在世界上。
in the world.
en el mundo.
这也是我们与他、与教练之间的纽带。
That's the bond we have with him too, with the coach.
Eso es el vínculo que tenemos con él también, con el entrenador.
他们凡事都听他的，绝对是凡事。
They listen to him in everything, in absolutely everything.
le hacen caso en todo, en absolutamente todo.
但他也是一个非常乐于对话的人。
but he is also a person very open to dialogue.
pero también es una persona muy abierta al diálogo.
我们从领域内部看到了一些东西。
There are things that we see from inside the field.
Hay cosas que nosotros vemos desde dentro de la cancha.
你在比赛中感受到了这一点，而他在外面，他可能没有意识到这一点。
that you felt it in the game, that he being outside, he may not realize it.
que vos la sentiste en el juego, que él estando afuera, por ahí puede ser que no se dé cuenta.
他对我们中的一个人去说，利奥，看，这正在发生，那正在发生。
and he is very open to one of us going and saying, Leo, look, this is happening, that is happening.
y él es muy abierto a que uno de nosotros vaya y le digan, Leo, fíjate que está pasando esto, está sucediendo lo otro.
一切都是在信任的基础上产生的，对吗？
and everything is generated very much in trust, right?
y todo se va generando muy en confianza, ¿no?
显然他总是拥有最后的发言权。
Obviously he always has the last word.
Obviamente que él tiene la última palabra siempre.
不，不，但这太棒了，太棒了。
No, no, but it's fabulous, it's fabulous.
No, no, pero es fabuloso, es fabuloso.
因为一定有外星人。
Because there has to be an alien.
Porque tiene que haber un alien.
不，你也必须勇敢。
No, you must be brave too.
No, ustedes deben ser bravitos también.
当他们集中注意力时，他们会玩一些小游戏，一些事情……让我们去打牌吧。
When they are concentrated they have little games, things... Let's go to cards.
Cuando están concentrados que tienen jueguitos, cositas... Vamos a las cartas.
去打卡？
To cards?
¿A las cartas?
到了窍门。
To the trick.
Al truco.
到了窍门？
To the trick?
¿Al truco?
一整天都在耍花招，胡安。
All day on the trick, Juan.
Todo el día al truco, Juan.
当有一点空闲的时候...哦，他们昨天告诉我，你...你一直都是冠军吗？
When there is a little free time... Oh, they told me yesterday that you... Are you the champions all the time?
Cuando hay un tiempito libre... Ay, me dijeron ayer que ustedes... ¿Todo el tiempo que son los campeones ustedes?
我们从未失去过它。
We never lost it.
Lo perdimos nunca.
是的，他们告诉我，不，罗德里戈撒了很多谎，这是真的。
Yes, they told me, no, that Rodrigo lies a lot, it's true.
Si me dijeron, no, que Rodrigo miente mucho, es verdad.
嗯，这是一个有时你也必须撒谎的游戏。
Well, it's a game in which sometimes you have to lie too.
Bueno, es un juego en el que a veces hay que mentir también.
是的，有时是的。
Yes, sometimes yes.
Sí, a veces sí.
有时是的，但如果他们抓住你，如果你撒谎……是的，嗯，这是……
Sometimes yes, but if they catch you, if you lie... Yes, well, it's...
A veces sí, pero si te agarran, si mentís... Sí, bueno, está...
存在它会吸引你的风险，对吗？
There is a risk, right?, that it will hook you.
Está en riesgo, ¿no?, que te enganche.
他们是否玩得很肮脏？
And do they play dirty or not?
¿Y juegan porquita o no?
是的。
Yeah.
Sí.
当然，这对我来说没问题，但是……
That's fine with me, of course, but...
Me parece bien, por supuesto, pero...
显然，如果有他们不需要的东西，就停下来，给予激励。
to stop, to give an incentive, obviously, if there is something they don't need.
para parar, para dar un incentivo, obviamente, si hay algo que no necesitan.
因为我想和你玩游戏，因为我也是特技冠军。
Because I would like to play a game with you, because I am also a trick champion.
Porque a mí me gustaría jugar un partido con ustedes, porque yo también soy campeona del truco.
谢谢，谢谢。
Thank you, thank you.
Gracias, gracias.
有卡吗？
Are there cards?
¿Hay cartas?
一会儿我们就去玩。
In a while we will play.
En un rato vamos a jugar.
准备好一切。
Prepare everything.
Preparad todo.
谁是我的伙伴？
Who is my partner?
¿Quién es mi compañero?
因为通常我的搭档里卡多·达林（我疯狂地称呼他）在西班牙，再见。
Because usually my partner Ricardo Darín, who I called like crazy, is in Spain, bye.
Porque por lo general mi compañero Ricardo Darín, que lo llamé como loco, está en España, chau.
嗯，所以...
Well, so...
Bueno, así que...
他们为我找到了一个很棒的合作伙伴。
They found me a wonderful partner.
Me buscaron un compañero maravilloso.
让它好起来，因为看，这些一定很糟糕。
Let it be good, because look, these must be terrible.
Que sea bueno, porque mira que estos deben ser terribles.
但那些来自……的信有符号吗？
But the letters that are from... Do they make signs?
Pero las cartas que son de... ¿Hacen señas?
我带了我的卡。
I brought my cards.
Yo traje mis cartas.
我可以玩我的卡吗？
Can I play with my cards?
¿Puedo jugar con mis cartas?
不，不，不。
No, no, no.
我有麦当劳寄给他们的信，是……
I have the letters that McDonald sent them, which is...
Tengo las cartas que les mandó McDonald que es...
他们对你神圣的面孔很野蛮，但让我们和其他人一起玩吧，因为如果我犯了错误......
They are barbaric with your faces that are divine, but let's play with the others because if I make a mistake...
son bárbaras con las caras de ustedes que están divinos, pero vamos a jugar con las otras porque si yo me equivoco...
想象一下你自己有这张脸。
Imagine yourself with that face.
Imagínate con esa cara.
不，我不能。
No, I can't.
No, no puedo.
不能。
Can't.
No puedo.
梅斯蒂也玩这个把戏吗？
Does Mesti play the trick too?
¿Mesti juega el truco también?
当然，我们三个人是一个团队。
Of course, the three of us are the team.
Claro, nosotros tres somos el equipo.
我们赢得了美洲杯冠军，在世界杯上我们赢得了锦标赛冠军。
that we won the Copa América and in the World Cup that we made a tournament.
que ganamos la Copa América y en el Mundial que hicimos torneo.
啊，三个，但他们玩...
Ah, three, but they play...
Ah, de tres, pero juegan...
但当 Leo 不在的时候，我们就玩。
But when Leo is not there, we play.
Pero cuando no está Leo, jugamos nosotros.
结果是狮子座让我们有点沮丧。
What happens is that Leo is the one who brings us down a bit.
Lo que pasa es que Leo es el que a nosotros nos baja un poco.
而且他不太喜欢这样。
And he doesn't like it that much.
Y a él no le gusta tanto.
他不喜欢这样，所以...我们，好吧。
And he doesn't like it, so... And we, ok.
Y a él no le gusta, entonces... Y nosotros, ok.
我喜欢这样，我喜欢这种尊重，我喜欢它。
I love that, I love that respect, I love it.
Me encanta eso, me encanta ese respeto, me encanta.
我喜欢一切，我喜欢告别面条，我们都喜欢面条，这是一回事......
I love everything, I loved the farewell to the noodle, we all love noodle, it's one thing...
Me encanta todo, me encantó la despedida del fideo, que todos lo amamos al fideo, es una cosa...
太好了，我不知道，但看起来太好了，太可爱了。
It's so good, I don't know, but it seems so good, so cute.
es tan bueno, no sé, pero parece tan bueno, tan tierno.
我不知道，亲爱的，人们会想念他的。
I don't know, adorable, he's going to be missed.
No sé, adorable, lo van a extrañar.
除了与国家队的故事......
Apart from a story with the national team...
Aparte una historia con la selección...
实力也很强，决赛输了。
very strong too, to lose finals.
muy fuerte también, de perder finales.
一如既往，由于伤病的原因，他无法……
not being able, as always due to the injuries that prevented him, from being...
no poder, como siempre por las lesiones que le impedían, ser...
他们阻止了他成为什么样的人，从而最终让他和他的妻子、女儿们在一起。
They prevented him from being who and thus ending up next to his wife, his daughters.
lo impedían ser quienes y terminar así al lado de su mujer, de sus hijas.
稍后你一定会怀念这一切，那种肾上腺素，那种成功。
You must miss all this later, that adrenaline, that success.
Se debe extrañar después toda esta cosa, esa adrenalina, ese éxito.
那种疯狂，训练课程很艰难，他们每天都训练。
and that madness, the training sessions are tough and they train every day.
y esa locura, los entrenamientos son bravos y se entrenan todos los días.
嗯，是的，在俱乐部，是的，在国家队。
Well, yes, in the clubs yes, here in the national teams.
Bueno, sí, en los clubes sí, acá en las selecciones.
当我们来的时候，我们有几天的时间来准备比赛
When we come we do have a few days to prepare for the games
cuando venimos sí tenemos poquitos días para preparar los partidos
你看足球也没有太多记忆。
You saw that football doesn't have much memory either.
Viste que el fútbol tampoco tiene mucha memoria.
当然，但是当然，当然。
Sure, but of course, of course.
Claro, pero por supuesto, por supuesto.
你在罗马踢球，对吗？
And you play in Rome, right?
Y vos juegas en Roma, ¿no?
是的，我在罗马踢球。
I play in Rome, yes.
Yo juego en Roma, sí.
去罗马。
To Rome.
A la Roma.
香气中。
In the aroma.
En el aroma.
很多年前，我曾经...
I once, many years ago...
Yo una vez, hace muchísimos años...
我说，我想让罗马对阵拉齐奥，你看到了他们是什么......但我不敢相信......
And I said, I want to give Rome a match to Lazio, you saw what they are... But I couldn't believe...
Y dije, yo quiero dar un partido de Roma a Lazio, viste que son... Pero no pude creer...
好吧，我会在罗马等你，这样你就可以去……我要去，当我去的时候，我肯定会见到你，还有你。
Well, I'll wait for you then in Rome so you can go to the... I'm going, when I go I'll see you, for sure, and you too.
Bueno, te espero yo entonces en Roma para que vayas al... Voy, cuando vaya te voy a ver, seguro, y a vos también.
是的，我要去见他们。
Yes, I'm going to see them.
Sí, los voy a ver.
任何。
Whatever.
Me lo que sea.
另外，我……我喜欢足球，我喜欢它。
Besides, I am... I like football, I like it.
Además, yo soy... Me gusta el fútbol, me gusta.
在您为许多意大利俱乐部效力之前。
Before you played for many Italian clubs.
Antes jugaste en muchos clubes italianos.
是的，我在巴黎踢球，我在尤文图斯踢球。
Yes, I played in Paris, I was at Juventus.
Sí, jugué en París, estuve en la Juventus.
哦，在巴黎圣日耳曼，是的。
Oh, in Paris-Saint-Germain, yes.
Ah, en París-Saint-Germain, sí.
我在巴黎度过了四年半。
I spent four and a half years in Paris.
Estuve cuatro años y medio en París.
你也讨厌巴黎，因为梅西不喜欢它。
And you also hated in Paris because Messi didn't like it.
Y odiaste también en París porque a Messi no le gustó.
不，我一开始就很好，我在巴黎很开心
No, I was very good at the beginning, I was very happy in Paris
No, yo estuve al principio muy bien, fui muy feliz en París
好吧，后来，当利奥到来时，我们度过了艰难的一年。
And well, later, when Leo arrived, we had a difficult year.
Y bueno, después, cuando llegó Leo, tuvimos un año medio difícil.
你说的语言是意大利语还是法语？
And the language you speak, Italian, French?
¿Y el idioma que hablas, italiano, francés?
我会说意大利语、法语，我的意思是让别人明白我的意思。
I speak Italian, French I make myself understood.
Hablo italiano, francés me hago entender.
意大利语比较容易，对吧？
Italian is easier, right?
El italiano es más fácil, ¿no?
当然。
Of course.
Por supuesto.
我在意大利待了很长时间，差不多六年了。
I had a long time to have Italy, almost six years.
Tuve mucho tiempo por tener Italia, casi seis años.
啊，他真的说得很好，非常好。
Ah, he really speaks it well, it goes very well.
Ah, realmente lo habla bien, va bienísimo.
用意大利语说一些话。
Say something in Italian.
Que diga algo en italiano.
你想让我用意大利语说什么？
What do you want me to say in Italian?
¿Qué querés que diga en italiano?
意大利对她说了一句话。
Italy says one sentence to her.
Le dice Italia una frase.
我不会说意大利语。
I don't speak Italian.
Yo no hablo italiano.
他还会说意大利语。
He also speaks Italian.
Él también habla italiano.
你也是？
You too?
¿Vos también?
我意大利语说得很好。
I speak Italian very well.
Yo parlo muy bien el italiano.
太感谢了！
Thank you so much!
¡Muchas gracias!
我已经在那里四年了。
I have been there four years.
Yo he estado cuatro años.
四年在哪里？
Four years where?
¿Cuatro años donde?
去罗马？
To Rome?
¿A la Roma?
北。
North.
Al norte.
是的，我买了。
Yes, I bought it.
Sí, lo compré.
让我们面对吧！
Let's face!
¡Me mata!
让我们面对吧！
Let's face!
¡Me mata!
至少，事实如此。
At least, the truth.
Por lo menos, la verdad.
当然，在北方则不然。
Not, of course, in the north.
No, claro, en el norte.
¿在什么他身上？
¿In what Him?
¿En que Lui?
在那个Lui，你却发现他比你还害羞。
In that Lui, but you see that he is more shy than you.
En que Lui, pero ves que es más tímido de usted.
有点可惜，不是吗？
A bit of a shame, isn't it?
Un poco de vergonya, ¿no?
有点尴尬，不知道为什么。
A little embarrassing, I don't know why.
Un poco de vergonya, no sé por qué.
因为我...
Because I...
Porque yo...
我们回来了。
We return.
Volvemos.
好吧，但比如说，你很害羞，但你浪漫吗？
Well, but for example, you are shy, but are you romantic?
Bueno, pero por ejemplo, sos tímido, pero ¿sos romántico?
是的。
Yeah.
Sí.
是的，也是。
Yes, too.
Sí, también.
在我看来，他对卡米拉所做的事......
It seems to me that what he did with Camila...
A mí me parece que lo que hizo con lo de Camila...
如果不给你带来困难，那就没有比这更伟大的爱的表现了。
There is no greater demonstration of love, if it doesn't give you a hard time.
No hay una demostración más grande de amor, si no te daba bolilla encima.
是的，我很浪漫，我很浪漫，我很感伤，对我的朋友也是如此。
Yes, I am very romantic, I am very romantic, I am very sentimental, with my friends too.
Sí, soy muy romántico, soy muy romántico, soy muy sentimental, con mis amigos también.
哦，我的爱人。
Oh, my love.
Ay, mi amor.
是的。
Yeah.
Sí.
和你的朋友在一起，他们是好朋友。
With your friends, they are good friends.
Con tus amigos, son buen amigos.
是的，他们是好朋友，是的。
Yes, they are good friends, yes.
Sí, son buen amigos, sí.
多么美妙啊！
How wonderful!
¡Qué genial!
我喜欢它。
I love it.
Me encanta.
比如说，给你一个浪漫的夜晚，就是一张摆着蜡烛的桌子……
And, for example, a romantic night for you, which is a table with candles...
Y, por ejemplo, una noche romántica para vos, que es mesa con velas...
蜡烛，鲜花，是的，是的。
Candle, flowers, yes, yes.
Vela, flores, sí, sí.
他喜欢浪漫，是的，他喜欢浪漫。
He likes the romantic, yes, he likes the romantic.
Le gusta lo romántico, sí, le gusta lo romántico.
我喜欢它，我喜欢它。
I like it, I like it.
Me gusta, me gustan.
塔米拉也被咬了。
And Tamila is bitten too.
Y a Tamila también les muerde.
她也喜欢它，是的。
She loves it too, yes.
A ella también le encanta, sí.
就这样吧，为爱而死。
That's it, die of love.
Es eso, muere de amor.
他喜欢它。
He loves it.
Le encanta.
多么美妙啊！
How wonderful!
¡Qué genial!
而你很浪漫吗？
And you are romantic?
¿Y vos sos romántico?
我也很浪漫。
I am very romantic too.
Yo soy muy romántico también.
你让我笑得太厉害了。
You made me laugh too much.
Me has reído demasiado.
我真的很喜欢写作。
I really like to write.
A mí me gusta mucho escribir.
你写吗？
Do you write?
¿Escribís?
是的，我写了很多信。
Yes, I have written many letters.
Sí, he escrito muchas cartas.
情书？
Love letters?
¿Cartas de amor?
情书？
Love letters?
¿Cartas de amor?
啊，好吧，但我以为这是一本书，而不是一封信。
Ah well, but I thought it was a book, not a letter.
Ah bueno, pero yo creí que un libro, no una carta.
情书更容易！
Love letters are easier!
¡Cartas de amor es más fácil!
是的，好吧，但这很浪漫。
Yes, well, but it's romantic.
Sí, bueno, pero es romántico.
但是，例如，你放什么？
But what do you put, for example?
¿Pero qué pones, por ejemplo?
你如何开始呢？
How do you start it?
¿Cómo lo empezás?
不不不，但是我已经写信了……
No, no, but I have written letters...
No, no, pero he escrito cartas...
非常好，非常衷心，但是非常喜欢晚餐，鲜花，我非常喜欢......
very good, very heartfelt but very much about the dinner, the flowers, I like it a lot...
muy buenas, muy sentidas pero mucho si de la cena, de las flores, me gusta mucho...
聊天，很多对话，保护，一杯酒，蜡烛。
chatting, a lot of dialogue, protection, glass of wine, candles.
charlar, mucho diálogo, protección, copa de vino, velas.
你有趣吗？
Are you funny?
¿Vos sos gracioso?
总是，因为他的眼睛在笑。
Always, because his eyes laugh.
Siempre, porque se le ríen los ojos.
太好了，一直这样吗？
It's great, is it always like this?
Es genial, ¿es siempre así?
一整天。
All day.
Todo el día.
你拥有令人难以置信的能量。
You have incredible energy.
Tú tienes una energía increíble.
他拥有的能量令人难以置信，他拥有的能量非常美丽。
The energy he has is incredible, the energy he has is very beautiful.
Es increíble la energía que tiene, muy linda la energía que tiene.
事实是，除此之外，好吧，磁场，小马达，如果它像兔子一样运行......磁场是难以忍受的。
The truth is, and aside, well, the field, the little motor, if it runs like a rabbit... The field is unbearable.
La verdad, y aparte, bueno, la cancha, el motorcito, si corre como un conejo... La cancha es insoportable.
我从来没有见过。
I never saw.
Yo nunca vi.
为何难以忍受？
Why is it unbearable?
¿Por qué es insoportable?
和大家谈谈。
Talk to everyone.
Habla con todo el mundo.
说话，对，说话。
Speak, yes, speak.
Habla, sí, habla.
这是真的。
It's true.
Es verdad.
你对人或人说什么？
What do you say to people or people?
¿Qué le decís a la gente o a la gente?
对所有人。
To all.
A todos.
总的来说，是的，嗯，我不知道，并不是它改变了我，但我得到了一个方面......
In general, yes, well, I don't know, it's not that it transforms me, but I get a facet that...
En general, sí, bueno, no sé, no es que me transforme, pero me sale ahí una faceta que...
在球场上我唯一遇到的就是烦恼，而且这一年我和我的对手经常打架。
The only thing that happens to me on the field is annoyance and well, and I fight a lot with my rivals throughout the year.
solo me sucede dentro de la cancha fastidio y bueno y me peleo mucho con los con los rivales con el año
他根本不爱我。
He doesn't love me at all.
A mí no me quiere nada.
当有一小公里时，它就会立即消失。
When there is a small kilometer, it goes right away.
cuando haya un pequeño kilómetro, enseguida va.
一阵风袭来。
A gust comes to this one.
Una ráfaga llega a este.
好吧，我们就这么说吧。
Well, let's just say.
Bueno, digamos yo solo.
你也是。
You too.
Vos también.
他也比我差。
He's worse than me too.
Él es peor que yo también.
是的。
Yeah.
Sí.
我也在球场上。
Me on the court too.
Yo en la cancha también.
啊，你在球场上变了，他们告诉我的。
Ah, you changed on the court, they told me.
Ah, cambiaste en la cancha, me dijeron.
和荷兰一起，他在替补席上扔了一个球，对吗？
with Holland, who threw a ball at the substitute bench, right?
con Holanda, que le tiró un pelotazo al banco de suplentes, ¿no?
搞得一团糟，我们几乎把所有的soques都拿走了。
It made a mess, we almost took all the soques.
Hizo un desastre, casi tomamos todos los soques.
你为什么把它扔掉？
Why did you throw it away?
¿Por qué lo tiraste?
你为什么把它扔掉？
Why did you throw it away?
¿Por qué lo tiraste?
哦，好吧。
Oh ok.
Ah, bueno.
非常好，非常好。
Very good, very good.
Muy bien, muy bien.
现在已经过去很多时间了，我们可以这么说。
Now that a lot of time has passed we can say it.
Ahora que pasó mucho tiempo lo podemos decir.
但当然，这是事实。
But of course, it is the truth.
Pero por supuesto, si es la verdad.
此外，那一刻站在你的立场上一定令人印象深刻。
Besides, it must be so impressive to be in your shoes at that moment.
Aparte, debe ser tan impresionante estar en el lugar de ustedes en ese momento.
我们都明白这一点。
that we all understand it.
que todos lo entendemos.
是的，是的，这比什么都重要，因为，嗯，比赛前的气氛非常紧张，所有的言论都......
Yes, yes, it was more than anything because, well, the atmosphere before the game was very tense, all the statements that had...
Sí, sí, fue más que nada porque, bueno, el clima ya antes del partido estaba muy tenso, todas las declaraciones que habían...
他们造就了球员和教练组。
They had made the players, their coaching staff.
Habían hecho los jugadores, el cuerpo técnico de ellos.
天气已经...
The weather was already...
Ya el clima era...
荷兰人，然后当银行采取行动，钱留在那儿时，你就可以了
the Dutch and then when the bank's move happened that the money was left there, you could already
los holandeses y entonces cuando pasó la jugada del banco que la plata me quedó ahí ya pudiste
还有你打过人吗？
And did you hit someone?
¿Y le pegaste a alguien?
不。
No.
啊，真可惜，我的爱人。
Ah, what a pity, my love.
Ah, qué lástima, mi amor.
很久以前我曾经去鹿特丹看过一场荷兰队的比赛。
I once went to see a Dutch game a long time ago in Rotterdam.
Yo una vez fui a ver un partido de Holanda hace muchísimo tiempo en Rotterdam.
阿根廷、荷兰，然后当时也出售瓶装啤酒。
Argentina, Holland, and then at that time beer was sold but in bottles.
Argentina, Holanda, y entonces es que en ese momento se vendía cerveza pero en botella.
阿根廷守门员出来，他们用瓶子打他，打开他的头，只是为了逃脱。
and the Argentine goalkeeper came out and they hit him with a bottle, they opened his head, just to get out.
y salió el arquero argentino y le dieron un botellaz, le abrieron la cabeza, solamente el salir.
我不知道为什么，我不这么认为，因为现在马克西玛是女王，这是在马克西玛之前，但无论如何我们还是这样。
I don't know why, I don't think because now Máxima is the queen, this was before Máxima, but we stayed like this anyway.
No sé por qué, no creo porque ahora Máxima es la reina, esto fue antes de Máxima, pero igual nos quedamos así.
当时我和一位名叫 Ante Garmasi 的模特在一起，他是克罗地亚人。
I was with a model from that time called Ante Garmasi and he was Croatian.
Yo estaba con un modelo de esa época que se llamaba Ante Garmasi y que era croata.
我说，我们不要用西班牙语说话。
I say, let's not speak in Spanish.
Yo digo, no hablemos en español.
他是你的男朋友吗？
Was he your boyfriend?
¿Era tu novio?
不，不，不。
No, no, no.
我告诉他们，我们不要说西班牙语，我发誓。
I tell them, let's not speak in Spanish, I swear.
Les digo, no hablemos en español, te lo juro.
我向上帝发誓不。
I swear to God no.
Te juro por Dios que no.
不不，他以前是同性恋。
No, no, he was gay before.
No, no, antes era gay.
但我们是朋友，非常朋友，我发誓。
but we were friends, very friends, I swear.
pero éramos amigos, muy amigos, te juro.
不不。
No no.
No, no.
他一直支持我，如果我爱上他，他也会支持我。
He always supported me, if I fell in love he supported me.
Él siempre me bancaba, si yo me enamoraba él me bancaba.
我告诉他，跟我来吧，不要丢下我一个人。
I told him, come with me, don't leave me alone.
Yo le decía, acompáñame, no me dejes sola.
他就去了，好吧，他想，是的。
And he went and well, he thought, yes.
Y iba y bueno, él pensaba, sí.
不，他曾经陪过我。
And no, he once accompanied me.
Y no, una vez me acompañó.
我说，哦，多么可爱啊！
I said, oh, how cute it is!
Yo dije, ¡ay, qué lindo es!
你看，它来了，它来了。
Look, it's coming here, it's coming here.
Mirá, viene para acá, viene para acá.
他邀请他跳舞。
And he asked him to dance.
Y lo sacó a bailar a él.
我发誓，我发誓。
I swear, I swear.
Te juro, te juro.
他离开了另一个朋友。
He left that other friend.
Dejó a ese otro amigo.
不，不是！
No, it's not!
¡No, es que no!
他拿出来，它飞起来了。
He took it out, it's flying.
Lo sacó, va volando.
他们很调情。
They are flirtatious.
Son coquetos.
例如，香水。
For example, perfume.
Por ejemplo, el perfume.
在那里他们告诉我梅西的香水很美味，你喜欢它。
There they told me that Messi's perfume is delicious, that you like it.
Ahí me dijeron que el perfume de Messi es riquísimo, que a ustedes les gusta.
国家的。
of the nation.
de la nación.
我喜欢我的香水。
I like my perfume.
A mi me gusta mi perfume.
谁写信给我有关这款香水的信息？
Who wrote me about the perfume?
¿Quién me escribió lo del perfume?
也不是因为他是梅西。
Nor because it's Messi.
Tampoco que porque sea Messi.
嗯，但是他们告诉我他们最喜欢的香水是梅西的。
Well, but they told me that the perfume they like the most is Messi's.
Bueno, pero me dijeron que el que perfume que más les gusta es el de Messi.
事实上，男孩子的气味一般都很好。
The truth is that boys smell good in general.
La verdad es que los muchachos huelen bien en general.
但我当然不是，但我会在赛后与销售人员交谈。
But I'm not of course, but I talk to the sales after the game.
Pero yo no soy por supuesto, pero yo hablo con los sales después del partido.
哦，是的，我说，利奥的香水很好闻。
Oh yeah, well, Leo has a good perfume, I say.
Ah, sí, bueno, Leo tiene un buen perfume, digo.
但不，不，不。
But no, no, no.
Pero no, no, no.
你不使用东西。
You don't use things.
Ustedes no usan cosas.
拥有那些发型和东西，那些神圣的服装，一切。
by having those hairstyles and things, those divine outfits, everything.
al tener esos peinados y esas cosas, esos trajes tan divinos, todo.
他们很调情。
They are flirtatious.
Son coquetos.
我们把所有东西都扔掉了，明白吗？
We threw everything away, see?
La tiramos todo, ¿viste?
您在 AFA 已经有这些套装了吗？还是……？
Did you already have these suits there at the AFA or...?
Estos trajes, ¿los tenías ya ustedes ahí en la AFA o...?
不。
No.
在家里，在家里。
At home, at home.
En casa, en casa.
他们是否让这里的河流变得神圣？
Did they make a river to be divine here?
¿Hicieron río para estar divinos acá?
是的，我们来自庄园，我们去了一个地方，我们去了另一个地方。
Yes, we came from the property, we went to one place, we went to another.
Sí, nosotros venimos del predio, fuimos a un lado, fuimos a otro.
贴上标签我感觉很甜蜜。
I feel sweet with the label on.
Me siento cantojante con la etiqueta puesta.
你只要贴上标签就可以了。
You just have the label on.
Es que tenés la etiqueta puesta.
好吧，但是打开它，没关系，对吧？
Well, but open it, it doesn't matter, right?
Bueno, pero abrítelo, no importa, ¿no?
它仍然是残酷的。
It remains brutal the same.
Se queda brutal igual.
你还想让我展示一下程序。
You also want me to show the program.
Usted vos también querés que muestre el programa.
他们发生什么事？
What happens to them for?
¿Para qué les pasa?
你为什么问？
Why do you ask?
¿Por qué se pregunta?
好吧，你看起来这套衣服很适合你，这对你来说有什么关系呢？
Well, you look like the suit fits you, what does it matter to you?
Bueno, vos traes como que te queda el traje, ¿qué te importa?
这对你来说是神圣的。
It's divine for you.
Divino te queda.
还有罗德里格斯，让我看看。
And Rodríguez, show me.
Y Rodríguez, mostrame.
我该怎么办？
What do I do?
¿Yo qué hago?
是的，给我看看。
Yes, show me.
Sí, mostrame.
物祭依然存在。
The bussai remains.
Le queda el bussai.
今天你买这个了吗？
Did you buy this today?
¿Este te lo compraste hoy?
不，不，我有过。
No, no, I had it.
No, no, lo tenía.
我已经拥有了。
I already had it.
Ya lo tenía.
你穿起来很好看，是吧？
It looks great on you, huh?
Te queda bárbaro, ¿eh?
你呢...
And you...
Y vos...
我不会因为你单身而问你任何事，对吧？
I'm not asking you anything because you're single, right?
No te pregunto nada porque estás soltero, ¿no?
我改变。
I change.
Yo muda.
我单身。
I'm single.
Yo soltero.
单身的。
Single.
Soltero.
没有什么。
Nothing.
Nada.
呃，是的。
Uh, yeah.
Eh, sí.
是的，是的。
Yes, yes.
Sí, sí.
但我很好，我很平静。
But I'm fine, I'm calm.
Pero estoy bien, estoy tranquilo.
安静的。
Quiet.
Tranquilo.
是的。
Yeah.
Sí.
我不想乱来，所以不。
I don't want to mess around, so no.
Yo no quiero meter la gamba, así que no.
女孩，女孩
Girl, Girl
Moza, Moza.
但我想要的是...
But what I would like is that...
Pero yo lo que me gustaría es que...
测试一下您是否真的是技巧冠军。
Test if it's true that you are trick champions.
probar si es verdad que ustedes son campeones de truco.
这是一个挑战。
Which is a challenge.
Que es un desafío.
是的，我们玩吧。
Yes, let's play.
Sí, juguemos.
好吧，让我们开始吧。
Well, let's get to the trick.
Bueno, vamos al truco.
让我们开始吧。
Let's get to the trick.
Vamos al truco.
我们走吧。
Let's go.
Vamos.
让我们开始吧。
Let's get to the trick.
Vamos al truco.
我们开了一个圆桌会议。
We had a round table.
Mesa redonda hicimos.
理应如此。
As it should be.
Como debe ser.
你也玩圆桌吗？
Do you also play with a round table?
¿Juegan con mesa redonda ustedes también?
瞧，我不知道，这太棒了！
Look, I didn't know, that's great!
Mirá, no sabía, ¡qué bien!
好吧，现在就让我们来揭开谜底吧。
Well, now let's reveal the mystery.
Bueno, ahora vamos a revelar el misterio.
谁是我的绝技搭档？
Who is my trick partner?
¿Quién es mi compañero de truco?
我的好朋友吉列尔莫
my great friend Guillermo
mi gran amigo Guillermo
非常好！
Very good!
¡Muy bien!
如果你相信我，你总是和我一起走，我和我一起走，我和我一起走
If you believe me that you always go with me I go with me, I go with me
Si me crees que siempre vas conmigo Yo me voy conmigo, yo me voy conmigo
亲爱的
my love
mi amor
我的生活，欢迎。
My life, welcome.
Mi vida, bienvenido.
我问你，这些不再是冠军了。
And no longer, please I ask you, these are the champions.
Y ya no, por favor te lo pido que estos son los campeones.
看看卡片。
Look at the cards.
Miren las cartas.
这些是麦当劳的卡片，上面有你的脸。
These are the McDonald's cards, with your faces.
Estas son las cartas de McDonald's, con las caras de ustedes.
我们正在展示它。
We are showing it.
La estamos mostrando.
这是你的，你多可爱啊。
This is yours, how cute you are.
Esta es la tuya, qué lindo que estás.
这是莱安德罗的。
This is Leandro's.
Esta es la de Leandro.
这是对...的打击
This is the hit to...
Este es el pelotazo a...
荷兰！
Netherlands!
¡Holanda!
哦，多好啊！
Oh, how good!
¡Ay, qué bueno!
看看还剩下什么。
Look what's left.
Mira qué quedó.
看看他说得多么好。
Look how well what he says.
Mira qué bien lo que dice.
它说什么？
What does it say?
¿Qué dice?
我不会堕落，我们是永恒的。
I don't fall, we are eternal.
No caigo, somos eternos.
我们一生都将属于赢得世界杯的那支精选球队。
All our lives we will belong to that select group that won the World Cup.
Toda la vida vamos a pertenecer a ese grupo selecto que levantó la Copa del Mundo.
我喜欢它。
I love it.
Me encanta.
塔卡有一个木槌，另一个木槌，另一个木槌。
A taca has a mallet, another mallet, another mallet.
Una taca tiene un mazo, otro mazo, otro mazo.
他已经数完了牌和所有的东西，是吧？
And he already counted the cards and everything, huh?
Y él ya contó las cartas y todo, ¿eh?
不，不，不。
No, no, no.
我们抢糖果。
We grab the candies.
Agarramos los caramelos.
但这些是给别人的吗？
But are these for others?
¿Pero por otros son estos?
是的。
Yeah.
Sí.
我以为他们会指望糖果。
I thought they were going to count on the candy.
Pensé que iban a contar con los caramelos.
不不。
No no.
No, no.
不不。
No no.
No, no.
车头灯，你看，车头灯多别致。
The headlights, look how chic, the headlights.
Los farotos, mira que chic, los farotos.
他们并不令人难以置信，非常好
They are not incredible, very good
no son increíbles, muy bien
但对我们来说，并不是要慢慢来，因为这是程序。
But for us, it's not that we are going to go slowly, because it is the program.
Pero para nosotros, no es que vamos a ir despacio, porque es el programa.
我们是为了胜利而来。
We come to win.
Nosotros venimos a ganar.
不喜欢输给我们
don't like to lose to us
no le gusta perder a nosotros
信号很多。
Lots of signal.
Mucha señal.
不，因为这些对我来说有点困难。
No, because these are a bit difficult for me here.
No, porque estos se me enteran un bajo acá.
不，不，算了，Memo 是众所周知的。
No, no, forget it, Memo's is known.
No, no, olvídate, se conoce el de Memo.
这就是原因。
That's why.
Por eso.
就像手杖一样，忘记它吧。
Like the cane, forget it.
Como la caña, olvídate.
布埃诺。
Bueno.
我们是否应该为吉他演奏？
Should we play for Guita or not?
¿Jugamos por Guita o no?
是的，是的。
Yes, yes.
Sí, sí.
无论他们想要什么，我们仍然会捐赠。
Whatever they want, we'll still donate it.
Por lo que quieran, igual la donamos.
有什么好处。
Something of benefit.
Algo de beneficio.
好吧，来吧。
Well, come on.
Bueno, dale.
儿童医院的金额。
Amount of money for the children's hospital.
Cantidad de dinero para el hospital de niños.
儿童医院？
Children's hospital?
¿Hospital de niños?
儿童医院？
Children's hospital?
¿Hospital de niños?
¿A 15，不是吗？
¿A 15, no?
一个15。
A 15.
好的。
Ok.
弗吉尼亚州。
Va.
多于。
Above.
Arriba.
一肘。
One cubit.
Una cubita.
哦，多快啊，但是那是什么？
Oh, how fast, but what is that?
Ay, qué rapidez, pero qué es eso?
格鲁皮尔拉斯维加斯。
Grupier Las Vegas.
我被刺伤了。
I got punctured.
Me pinché.
我害怕相机，明白吗？
I'm afraid of cameras, see?
Me da miedo las cámaras, ¿viste?
看来我有一把剑。
It seems I have the one of sword.
Parece que tengo el uno de espada.
¿Ves？
¿Ves?
不用担心。
Don't worry.
No te preocupes.
好吧。
Alright.
Está bien.
你在这里看不到摄像头，对吧？
You can't see the cameras here, right?
Acá no se me ven las cámaras, ¿no?
他们不会向您展示它们。
They are not going to show them to you.
No te las van a mostrar.
不，不，他们不会。
No, no, they won't be.
No, no, no van a ser.
但展示给他们看，嗯？
But show them, eh?
Pero les muestren, ¿eh?
不，不，不，不。
No, no, no, no.
是的。
Yeah.
Sí.
你告诉我，你想让我玩吗？
You tell me, do you want me to play?
Decime vos, ¿querés que juegue?
朱加，朱加，朱加。
Jugá, jugá, jugá.
你没有那样的东西，伙计。
You don't have anything like that, dude.
No tienes nada eso, güey.
布埃诺。
Bueno.
哎呀！
¡Ey!
这是怎么回事！
What's up!
¡Qué va!
两个都？
Both?
¿Tanto?
他至少有 27 岁。
And 27, minimum, he has.
Y 27, mínimo, tiene.
船运。
Shipping.
Envido.
船运。
Shipping.
Envido.
不。
No.
不，不，不。
No, no, no.
尊重。
Respect.
Respeta.
等待。
Wait.
Espera.
我什么都没有
I don't have anything.
Yo no tengo nada.
我27岁了。
I am 27.
Yo tengo 27.
21.
说谎者。
Liar.
Mentiroso.
他们不再知道我是否在撒谎。
They no longer know if I'm lying or not.
Ya no saben si miento o no.
哦，我已经说过了！
Oh, I already said it!
¡Ah, lo dije ya!
不，不，不。
No, no, no.
它说什么？
What does it say?
¿Qué es lo que dice?
我们做什么？
What do we do?
¿Qué hacemos?
你更了解他吗？
Do you know him more?
¿Vos lo conocés más?
不，他们打冠军，他们是冠军。
No, they play championships, they are champions.
No, ellos juegan campeonatos, son campeones.
你今年多大？
How old are you?
¿Cuántos años tienes?
多少？
How many?
¿Cuántos?
四。
Four.
Cuatro.
29.
为了互相认识。
To get to know each other.
Para conocernos.
27、你明白吗？
27, do you understand?
27, ¿entendés?
我喜欢他们，我喜欢他们。
I like them, I like them.
Me gustan, me gustan.
你喜欢就去吧
You like it, go for it.
Te gusta, dale.
想要。
Wanna.
Quiero.
我告诉过你我什么都没有。
I told you I didn't have anything.
Te dije que yo no tenía nada.
安静，但首先是为了另一个。
Quiet, but first for another.
Tranquila, pero primero por otro.
这不好。
It's not good.
No está bien.
什么，贝司上有 11 吗？
What, do you have the 11 on the bass?
¿Qué, tenés el 11 del bajo?
我不知道
i don't know
No sé.
塞范。
Se van.
我不能玩。
I can't play.
No puedo jugar.
你不能吗？
Can't you?
¿No podés?
好吧，如果你做不到，就尖叫吧。
Well, scream if you can't.
Bueno, gritar si no podés.
诡计。
Trick.
Truco.
哦，是的，但是不……你好。
Oh, yes, but no... Hello.
Ah, sí, pero no... Hola.
是的。
Yeah.
Sí.
雷伊.
Rey.
我不这么认为。
I don't suppose so.
No lo supongo.
我以为是他。
I thought it was him.
Yo pensé que era él.
当然，他们知道这一点，他们互相看着对方，他们就已经知道了。
Of course, they know this, they look at each other and they already know.
Claro, esto saben, se miran y ya saben.
不，四比一。
No, four to one.
No, cuatro a uno.
我不知道...
I didn't know that...
Yo no sabía que...
我从一开始就打算撒谎……但我没有撒谎，因为他已经31岁了。
I was going to lie from the first... But I didn't lie, because he was 31.
que ya iba a mentir desde el primero... Pero no mentí, por su 31.
当然可以，但我以为是他。
Sure, but I thought it was him.
Claro, pero yo creí que era él.
我确实撒谎了。
I did lie.
Yo sí mentí.
当然，当然。
Of course, of course.
Claro, claro.
哦，大家都知道，我知道我已经31岁了。
Oh, everyone knows it, I knew I was already 31.
Ay, lo saben todos, sabía que ya tenía 31.
冷静，冷静。
Calm, calm.
Tranquila, tranquila.
好吧，好吧，一点点。
Okay, okay a little bit.
Está bien, está bien un poco.
多少钱？
How much is it?
¿A cuánto es?
抱歉，15，对吗？
Sorry, 15, right?
Perdón, ¿a 15, no?
15岁，如果我们没有时间的话。
At 15, if we don't have time.
A 15, si no tenemos tiempo.
啊！
¡Ah!
让我们看看，我？
Let's see, me?
A ver, ¿yo?
国王我有这个想法。
A king I have the idea.
Un rey tengo la idea.
如果他是国王，就来吧。
If he is king, come.
Si es rey, vení.
最大限度。
Maximum.
Máximo.
如果是国王，我就玩。
If it's king, I play.
Si es rey, juego.
布埃诺。
Bueno.
来吧，来吧，如果你愿意的话。
Come, come, if you want.
Vení, vení, si querés.
我可以走了吗？
Can I go?
¿Puedo ir?
嘿，我来了，那你冷静点。
Hey, I'm coming, then calm down.
Eh, voy, entonces tranqui.
这次不点了。
Point not this time.
Punto no esta vez.
26岁，但我不喜欢。
26, but I don't like it.
26, pero no me gusta.
因为？
Because?
¿Por qué?
因为它有代码。
Because it has a code.
Porque tiene un código.
我升得不多。
I don't go up much.
No subo mucho.
别留下来。
Don't stay.
No se quede.
瞧，这花费你很少。
Look, it costs you little.
Mira, te cuesta poco.
准备工作需要我花钱吗？
Does the ready cost me?
¿Me cuesta el ready?
你有信吗？
Do you have a letter?
¿Vos tenés una cartita?
我已经告诉过你了……是的。
I have for that, what I told you... Yes.
Yo tengo para eso, lo que te dije... Sí.
我杀了然后走。
I kill and I go.
Mato y voy.
好，好，好。
Good, good, good.
Bien, bien, bien.
我对他大喊，我不会玩。
I yell at him, I can't play.
Yo le grito, no puedo jugar.
我邀请你。
I invite you.
Te invito.
我的意思是，诡计，诡计。
I mean, trick, trick.
Digo, truco, truco.
抱歉，我错了，骗子。
Sorry, I was wrong, trick.
Perdón, me equivoqué, truco.
我又给了他一分，让他了解我们。
I gave him one more point to get to know us.
Le di un punto más para conocernos.
像这样，像这样。
Like this, like this.
Así, así.
不，还有一点。
No, a little more.
No, un poco más.
想要。
Wanna.
Quiero.
你有什么！
What do you have!
¡Qué tenés!
哦，七个！
Oh, seven!
¡Ay, papito!
我爱你，科波林！
I love you, Copolín!
¡Te quiero, Copolín!
好的。
GOOD.
Bien.
我们三个吗？
Did we three?
¿Tres hicimos?
但？
But?
Sí, ¿no?
四对四。
Four to four.
Cuatro a cuatro.
四对四。
Four to four.
A cuatro a cuatro.
爸爸冷静点！
Calm down daddy!
¡Tranquilo papu!
他们多可爱啊。
How cute they are.
Qué lindos son.
他们让一个需要它的国家感到幸福。
They made a country that needed it happy.
Hicieron feliz a un país que lo necesitaba.
我不会对你做任何事，因为……你什么都没有。
I don't do anything to you because... You don't have anything.
No te hago nada porque... No tenés nada.
不，不是因为这个，不是因为那个。
No, it's not because of that, it's not because of that.
No, no es por eso, no es por eso.
我也是，我也是。
Me too, me too.
Yo también, yo también.
是的？
Yeah?
¿Sí?
我可以来吗？
Can I come?
¿Puedo venir?
我可以走了吗？
Can I go?
¿Puedo ir?
我可以走了。
I can go.
Puedo ir.
是的，我告诉过你你在做什么。
Yes, I told you what you were doing.
Sí, yo te dije que hacías.
只有你吗？
Just you?
¿Sola vos?
索拉。
Sola.
杀掉小家伙吧
Kill little one, huh.
Mata chiquitito, eh.
发生什么事了？
What's happening?
¿Qué pasa?
我可以最大限度地发挥。
I can max out.
Yo puedo empardar máximo.
你没那么爱自己。
You don't love yourself that much.
No te quieres tanto.
你还告诉了我一些别的事。
You told me something else.
Me dijiste otra cosa.
我以为你可能会被困住，抱歉。
I thought you might get stuck, sorry.
Pensé que te podías empardar, perdón.
看，我那里有一封非常重要的信。
Look, I have a very important letter there.
guarda ahí tengo una carta muy importante
你必须玩。
You have to play.
Tienes que jugar.
第 27 点。
Point 27.
Punto 27.
船运。
Shipping.
Envido.
我29岁我什么都没有，我没有，我没有，我发誓我没有最好的
I'm 29 I don't have anything, I don't have, I don't have, I swear I don't have The best
Yo tengo 29 No tengo nada, no tengo, no tengo, te juro que no tengo La mejor
停下来。
Stopping.
A parar.
诡计。
Trick.
Truco.
逐个。
One by one.
Uno por uno.
不？
¿No?
逐个。
One by one.
Uno por uno.
很难吧？
It's difficult, huh?
Está difícil el cheto, ¿eh?
打败他们！
Beat them!
¡Ganarles!
我要跑去卢汉！
I'm running to Luján!
¡Me voy corriendo a Luján!
我们下去吧。
Let's go down.
Vamos a ir abajo.
允许。
Permission.
Permiso.
是的。
Yeah.
Sí.
不。
No.
啊！
¡Ah!
那还不错！
That's not bad!
¡Eso no es malo!
他是一名扑克玩家，你明白吗？
He's a poker player, you see?
Es un jugador de póker, ¿viste?
那些放进去的...你要剪掉吗？
Those that are put in... Are you cutting that?
Esos que se ponen en... ¿Estás corteando eso?
小心。
Careful.
Cuidado.
我们很紧张。
We are nervous.
Estamos nerviosos.
不，我没有指甲。
No, I don't have nails.
No, no tengo uñas miradas.
我多么喜欢这首歌，这首精选的新歌。
How I like the song, this new one from the selection.
Como me gusta la canción esta nueva de la selección.
我喜欢这个选择
I like this selection
esta que me gusta esta selección
我们来看你，我们是来给你加油的。
We came to see you, we came to cheer you up.
Te vinimos a ver, te vinimos a alegrar.
我喜欢它，我喜欢它。
I like it, I like it.
Me gusta, me gusta.
戴上它真是要了我的命。
It kills me to put it on.
Me mata ponerla yo.
我是……是的。
I'm... Yes.
Estoy... Sí.
但很小。
But very small.
Pero muy chiquita.
两个人？
For two?
¿Por dos?
是的。
Yeah.
Sí.
布埃诺。
Bueno.
积分。
Points.
Puntos.
积分是多少？
How much is points?
¿Cuánto es puntos?
我27岁了，我很害怕。
I'm 27 and I'm scared.
Yo tengo 27 y tengo miedo.
我也27岁了，我很害怕。
I'm also 27 and I'm scared.
Yo también tengo 27 y tengo miedo.
所以我不告诉他。
So I don't tell him.
Entonces no le digo.
你不知道他不应该是20岁。
You don't know that he shouldn't be 20.
No sabes que no debe tener 20.
不，因为你有2号。
No, because you have number 2.
No, porque vos tenés el 2.
好吧，他赢了。
Well, he's winning.
Bueno, va ganando.
去你的吧！
Go yours!
¡Va tuya!
这取决于你，让我们说不！
It's up to you, let's say no!
¡Va tuya, digamos que no!
他们没有唱歌。
They didn't sing.
No cantaron.
我有真相。  22.
I have the truth.  22.
Yo tengo la verdad. 22.
让我们看看，什么，什么，什么？
Let's see, what, what, what?
A ver, ¿qué, qué, qué?
事实是……不，这个人肯定已经超过27岁了。
The truth is... No, this one must be over 27.
Es que la verdad... No, este debe tener más de 27.
瞧，在我看来……
Look, it seems to me that...
Mirá, me parece que...
有，有，对吧？
It has, it has, right?
Tiene, tiene, ¿no?
是的，是的，是的。
Yes, yes, yes.
Sí, sí, sí.
我有多少个？
How many do I have?
¿Cuántas tengo?
30.
再也没有那个样子了。
There is no more the look.
No hay más la pinta.
再也没有那个样子了。
There is no more the look.
No hay más la pinta.
不，我没有。
No, I don't have one.
No, no tengo.
哦，骗子。
Oh, liar.
Ay, mentiroso.
我要去。
I'm going.
Voy yo.
来吧，来吧。
Come, come.
Vení, vení.
你已经赢了，呵呵。
You already won, huh.
Ya ganaste, eh.
好的！
GOOD!
¡Bien!
不，因为怀疑而沉默。
No, silent because of doubt.
No, callado por la duda.
是的？
Yeah?
¿Sí?
他已经说过了。
He already said.
Ya dijo.
你已经说过了吗？
Did you already say?
¿Ya dijo?
不不。
No no.
No, no.
我不会帮你任何事。
I won't help you with anything.
No te ayudo con nada.
不，这不会，不，什么……
No, it's not going, no, what...
No, no va, no, que le...
一点点那一点，现​​在对他要小心
a little point that point and now be careful when to him
un puntito que punta y ahora cuidado cuando a él
不，没什么。
No, it's nothing.
No, no es nada.
他没有能力。
He is incapable.
Es incapaz.
你听到我说话了吗？
Did you hear me?
¿Me oíste?
我只有那封信。
I only have that letter.
Yo tengo nada más esa carta.
我有一个二。
I have a two.
Yo tengo un dos.
哦，不？
Oh, no?
Ah, ¿no?
谁扮演？
Who plays?
¿Quién juega?
你不能吗？
Can't you?
¿No puedes?
航海。
Voy.
是的，来吧，来吧。
Yes, come on, come on.
Sí, dale, vení.
但眼睛，是吧？
But eyes, huh?
Pero mata, ¿eh?
是的，更好。
Yes, better.
Sí, mejor.
你有那么多吗……
Do you have that much...?
¿Tenés tanto...?
不。
No.
是的。
Yeah.
Sí.
不？
¿No?
不。
No.
没有什么。
Nothing.
Nada.
26日。
On the 26th.
Ni 26.
没有什么。
Nothing.
Nada.
嗯，马托。
Well, Marto.
Bueno, Marto.
很好，我喜欢。
Good, I like it.
Bien, me gusta.
我认为第一个是我们一生中唯一可以随身携带的。
I think the first is the only one in life that we can take with us.
Creo que el primero es el único en vida que nos podemos llevar.
第二个我们就输了。
The second we lost.
El segundo perdimos.
我已经没有了，我向上帝发誓，如果我没有一点东西，但是……
I don't have one anymore, I swear to God that if I don't have a little thing, but...
Ya no tengo, te juro por Dios que si no le tengo una minucia, pero...
为了你的，呃！
For yours, eh!
¡Por las tuyas, eh!
并打个招呼。
and say hello.
y saludar.
请犯错误。
Make the mistake, please.
Hacha la falta, por favor.
不不。
No no.
No, no.
26、27。
26, 27.
你不想吗？
Don't you want to?
¿No quieres?
不，我们不想。
No, we don't want to.
No, no queremos.
嗯，你还有什么东西吗？
Well, do you have anything left?
Bueno, ¿te queda algo?
好吧，他必须玩这个游戏。
Well, he's going to have to play it.
Bueno, se la va a tener que jugar.
戴尔.
Dale.
你留在这里吗？
Are you staying here?
¿Vos te quedáis aquí?
是的，是的。
Yes, yes.
Sí, sí.
我杀死并去找我的伙伴。
I kill and go to my partner.
Yo mato y voy a mi compañero.
我根本没有这些技巧。
I don't have those tricks at all.
Yo no tengo para nada esos trucos.
来自安娜。
From Ana.
De Ana.
我不知道
i don't know
No sé.
你知道苏蒂有多少钱吗？
Do you know how much Suti has?
¿Sabés cuánto tiene Suti?
事实是，他有一个杯子。
The truth is, he has one of the cup.
La verdad, tiene el uno de copa.
因为他说，我有一点，他说。
Because he said, I have a little bit, he said.
Porque dijo, yo tengo un poquitito, dijo.
我要告诉他我想要。
I'm going to tell him I want.
Yo le voy a decir quiero.
因为她只有一个杯子，我就听她的。
Because she has one cup, I listened to her.
Porque tiene el uno de copa, yo la escuché.
我不杀人。
I don't kill.
Yo no mato.
没关系。
It doesn't matter.
No importa.
这不会杀死他。
It doesn't kill him.
No lo mata.
嗯，在这里。
Well, here.
Bueno, toma.
现在我想要退出，因为我和我的伴侣在一起。
And now I want a retruction, because I am with my partner.
Y ahora quiero retruco, porque yo estoy con mi compañero.
但我不杀他……我听说我确实有一点……你怎么知道？
But I don't kill him... I heard that I do have a little bit... And how do you know?
Pero yo no mato el... Yo escuché que si yo tengo un poquitito... ¿Y cómo sabes?
但不，你不能那样做。
But no, you can't do that.
Pero no, no podés hacer eso.
你说，我有一点。
And you said, I have a little bit.
Y dijiste, yo tengo un poquitito.
一杯应该是什么样的？
What should one cup be like?
¿Cómo tiene que ser el uno de copa?
它可能是金色的。
It could be the golden one.
Podría ser el uno de oro.
这些都是专业人士。
These are professionals.
Estos son profesionales.
你更了解他们。
You know them better.
Ustedes los conocen más.
对我来说，确实如此。
For me, it has.
Para mí, tiene.
我们不想。
We don't want to.
No queremos.
给我们三个。
Three for us.
Tres para nosotros.
朝九晚五。
Nine to five.
Nueve a cinco.
三块玉米饼，三块玉米饼。
Three tacos, three tacos.
Tres tacos, tres tacos.
我们以六比五获胜。
We won six to five.
Ganábamos seis a cinco.
两个，如果不是三个，他们有六个，那就完美了。
Two, if not three, they had six, that's perfect.
Dos, si no tres, tenían seis, está perfecto.
现在，我们的这只手。
Now, this hand of ours.
Ahora sí, esta mano nuestra.
是的，因为它让我感动。
Yes, because it moves me.
Sí, porque me mueve.
但这给了我思想。
But that gives me the mind.
Pero ese me dé la mente.
就这样！
There it goes!
¡Ahí va!
如果是一个人，就来吧。
If it's alone, come.
Si es sola, vení.
孤独，孤独，孤独。
Alone, alone, alone.
Sola, sola, sola.
独自一人，独自一人
alone, alone
solas, solas.
眼睛！
Eye!
¡Mata!
眼睛！
Eye!
¡Mata!
我没有那么多。
I don't have that much.
Yo tanto no tengo.
不。
No.
这些都是骗局。
These are scams.
Esto son picarones.
马托和你。
Marto and you.
Marto y vos.
好的。
GOOD.
Bien.
我有一个小二。
I have a little two.
Yo tengo un dos chiquitito.
这发生在我身上。
It happened to me.
A mí me pasó.
我也是。
Me too.
A mí también.
你有一个马王。
You have a horse king.
Tienes un rey caballo.
砂砾。
Gritale.
Grítale.
诡计。
Trick.
Truco.
想要。
Wanna.
Quiero.
看起来……它有什么？
It looks... What does it have?
Se ve... ¿Qué tiene?
不，不，不！
No, no, no!
¡No, no, no!
但不是！
But not!
¡Pero no!
米拉！
¡Mira!
还有你为什么不把它放进去？
And why didn't you put it in?
¿Y por qué no la pusiste?
我戴上还是一样的。
I put it on and it was the same.
La pongo y era lo mismo.
你，你怎么不玩呢？
You, why don't you play?
Tú, ¿por qué no juegas?
别告诉他。
Don't tell him.
No le digas.
我不杀国王，你也不杀。
I don't kill a king, neither do you.
Yo no mato un rey, vos tampoco.
不，不，不，不。
No, no, no, no.
我们怎么样？
How are we doing?
¿Cómo vamos?
现在是的，现在是的。
Now yes, now yes.
Ahora sí, ahora sí.
缺少什么！
What was missing!
¡Qué faltaba!
现在是的。
Now yes.
Ahora sí.
唐·福特.
Don Ford.
不。
No.
我不知道你有路易威登。
I didn't know you had Louis Vuitton.
No sabía que tenías Louis Vuitton.
楚！
¡Chu!
那个男人什么？
That man what?
¿Ese hombre qué?
你知道你是豁免的吗？
Do you know that you are exempt?
¿Sabes que estás dispensa?
我向你发誓...
I swear to you...
Te juro que...
你和国王。
You and King.
Vos y Rey.
好的。
OK.
那和国王。
That and King.
Esa y Rey.
是的。
Yeah.
Sí.
这是什么？
What is this?
¿Qué es esto?
有...？
Have...?
¿Tienes...?
有...？
Have...?
¿Tienes...?
来。
Come.
Vení.
航海。
Voy.
但我不能走太多。
But I can't go much.
Pero no puedo mucho ir.
好吧，我走了。
Well, I'm going.
Bueno, voy.
但他们将...
But they are going to...
Pero se van a...
两个都？
Both?
¿Tanto?
如果我们没有，我们就不要说。
If we don't have it, let's not say.
Si no tenemos, no digamos.
祖父母。
Grandparents.
A vos.
在我看来，我赢了 27 分。
With 27 I win, it seems to me.
Con 27 gano, me parece.
¿27 找出来吗？
¿27 find out?
¿27 gano?
是的。
Yeah.
Sí.
我喜欢它。
I like it.
Me gusta.
我先唱 23. 27.
I sing first 23. 27.
Yo canto primero 23. 27.
爸爸！
Daddy!
¡Papito!
苏珊娜对我来说有2把剑和1把剑。
Susana for me has the 2 sword and the 1 sword.
Susana para mí tiene el 2 de espada y el 1 de espada.
为我。
For me.
Para mí.
哦，帕平吉，多好啊。
Oh papingui, how good.
Ay papingui, qué bueno.
加油，三个！
Come on, three!
¡Vamos, tres!
祖父母！
Grandparents!
¡A vos!
你监视牌，你通过摄像机监视牌。
You spy on the cards, you spy on the cards through the camera.
Vos espías las cartas, vos espías las cartas por la cámara.
你怎么知道？
How can you know?
¿Cómo puede saber?
为什么是23年？
And why 23 years?
¿Y por qué 23 años?
但什么？
But what?
¿Pero qué?
我也不会唱歌。
I can't even sing either.
No puedo ni cantar tampoco.
他没有问我。
He didn't ask me.
No me pregó.
有人在做六事。
There is someone who is doing the six.
Hay alguien que le está haciendo las seis.
谁扔了卡片？
Who threw the cards?
¿Quién tiró las cartas?
啊，因为我们有纹身魔术卡。
Ah, because we have tattooed trick cards.
Ah, porque nosotros tenemos tatuadas cartas del truco.
哦真的吗？
Oh really?
¿En serio?
因为在决赛之前我们玩了一场游戏，我们有十次机会猜出一张牌。
because before the final we played a game and we had ten chances to guess the card that one drew.
porque antes de la final hicimos un juego y teníamos diez posibilidades para adivinar la carta que uno sacaba.
他拿出一张卡片。
He took out a card.
Él sacaba una carta.
我们有十种可能来猜。
and we had ten possibilities to guess it.
y nosotros teníamos diez posibilidades para adivinarla.
事实上，因为我们唯一不打牌的一天是比赛日。
Actually because the only day we don't play cards is match day.
En realidad porque nosotros el único día que no jugamos a las cartas es el día de partido.
这一天，就像……当然，然后，我们要和巴西队比赛的那天，决赛，我们吃完午饭，我们说好吧。
This day, like... Of course, then, the day we are going to play with Brazil, the final, we finish having lunch, we say okay.
Este día, como de... Claro, entonces, el día que vamos a jugar con Brasil, la final, terminamos almorzar, decimos bueno.
我们都去睡午觉吧。
Let's all go to sleep for a nap.
Vamos todos a dormir a la siesta.
当然。
Of course.
Claro.
我们聚在一起，谈话安排在下午 6 点，我们在 4:30 聚在一起，自己也有一些伙伴。
We get together, the talk is scheduled at 6 in the afternoon, we get together at 4:30, to have some mates ourselves.
Nos juntamos, la charla a poner a las 6 de la tarde, nos juntamos a las 4 y media, a tomar unos mates nosotros.
我们这些永远在一起的人。
Those of us who are always there together.
Los que estamos siempre ahí juntos.
我们一点钟就吃完了晚饭和午饭。
We finished dinner and lunch at one o'clock.
Terminamos de cenar, de almorzar a la una.
好了，大家到自己的房间去。
Well, everyone to their room.
Bueno, cada uno a su habitación.
戴尔，戴尔。
Dale, Dale.
Dale, dale.
一点二十分，尼科房间里的每个人也是如此，比如说我的房间。
One twenty, everyone in Nico's room too, say mine.
Un y veinte, todos en la habitación de Nico también, di mío.
我们睡不着。
We can't sleep.
No podemos dormir.
距离比赛还有多久？
How long until the game?
¿Cuánto falta para el partido?
但还有七个小时！
But there are seven hours left!
¡Pero faltan siete horas!
然后我们都坐着。
And then we were all sitting.
Y entonces estábamos todos sentados.
有一次我们已经喝了 200 瓶马黛茶。
At one point we had already drunk 200 thermoses of mate.
En un momento ya habíamos tomado 200 termos de mate.
就这样一看，已经是三点了。
Looking at it like that, and it was three o'clock.
Mirándolo así, y eran las tres.
而现在...
And now...
Y ahora...
突然，由于我们不能玩，我们抓起牌并说，好吧，我会抓一张牌......
And suddenly, since we couldn't play, we grabbed the cards and said, well, I'll grab a card...
Y de repente, como no podíamos jugar, agarramos las cartas y dijimos, bueno, yo agarro una carta...
每个人都有，说吧，我从他那里拿一张牌，任何人或者你，你有十种可能性，让我们看看你能不能猜出那是什么牌。
and each one has, put it, I'll take a card from him, anyone or you, you have ten possibilities, let's see if you can guess what card it is.
y cada uno tiene, ponele, le saco una carta a él, cualquiera o a vos, vos tenés diez posibilidades, a ver si adivinas qué carta es.
这是相当困难的，因为四十个中有十个。
It's quite difficult, because there are ten out of forty.
Es bastante difícil, porque son diez entre cuarenta.
如果我们有七个人，如果四个人猜到了，三个没有猜到……
If there were seven of us, if four guessed it and three didn't...
Si la mitad éramos siete, si cuatro la adivinan y tres no...
这意味着我们将成为冠军。
It means that we are going to be champions.
quiere decir que vamos a salir campeones.
好的！
GOOD!
¡Bien!
三个猜对了，三个猜不到，最后剩下一个是狮子座。
Three guess it, three don't, and the last one left was Leo.
Tres la adivinan, tres no, y el último que quedaba era Leo.
我们画一封信。
We draw a letter.
Sacamos una carta.
我拿出信，看了看，然后给孩子们看。
I take out the letter, I look at it, I show it to the kids.
Yo saco la carta, la miro, se la muestro a los pibes.
我们简直不敢相信。
We couldn't believe it.
No lo podíamos creer.
他参加过五届杯赛。
He had played the five cup.
Había tocado el cinco de copa.
他参加了四次决赛并输掉了四次杯赛。
He had played four finals and lost four cups.
Él había jugado cuatro finales y había perdido cuatro copas.
这是第五次。
It was the fifth.
Era la quinta.
确切地说，这是第五次。
It was the fifth, exactly.
Era la quinta, justo.
我有五个。
I got five.
Me tocó el cinco.
利奥，我们请猜猜。
And we, please, Leo, guess it.
Y nosotros, por favor, Leo, adivinala.
一开始是粗糙的，不，七块金子，不，十一块……
and one of coarse begins, no, seven of gold, no, eleven of...
y empieza uno de basto, no, siete de oro, no, once de...
我们，因为对我们来说那是最后的
Us, because for us that was the final
Nosotros, porque para nosotros esa era la final
现在我们确实击败了他们，即使是马拉卡纳，我们也击败了他们。
Now we did beat them, even though the Maracaná was, we beat them.
Ahora sí le ganábamos, por más que sea el Maracaná, le ganábamos.
突然他说一杯五杯，画面很壮观，因为突然我们都停下来了，好像真的
and suddenly he says five for a glass and the image is spectacular because suddenly we all stop and as if really
y de repente dice cinco de copa y la imagen es espectacular porque de repente nos paramos todos y como si de verdad
我们互相拥抱并开始了。
and we hugged each other and started.
y nos abrazamos y empezamos.
加油，冠军。
Come on, champion.
Dale, campeón.
加油，冠军。
Come on, champion.
Dale, campeón.
加油，冠军。
Come on, champion.
Dale, campeón.
加油，冠军。
Come on, champion.
Dale, campeón.
谢谢！
¡Gracias!
好吧，我们为什么要继续？
Well, why do we continue?
Bueno, ¿para qué seguimos?
嘿……你玩吗？
Hey... Do you play?
Eh... ¿Jugas vos?
致王。
To King.
A Rey.
致王。
To King.
A Rey.
并穿上它。
And put it on.
Y ponela.
如果你失业了，戴上它，因为……我可以戴上它吗？
If you have unemployment, put it on because... Shall I put it on?
Si tienes cesa, ponela porque... ¿La pongo?
是的。
Yeah.
Sí.
一点点，一点点
a little, a little
un poco, un poco.
27是嘴。
27 are mouths.
27 son bocas.
第一个是那个走了的。
The first is the one that goes.
La primera es la que va.
27 不是嘴。
27 are not mouths.
27 no son bocas.
布埃诺。
Bueno.
数量不少，告诉他。
There are not few, tell him.
No son pocas, decíle.
他什么都没有，但他会听。
He has nothing, but he listens.
No tiene nada, pero escucha.
你为什么有这个游戏？
Why do you have this game?
¿Por qué tiene este juego?
我对他们俩都没有什么。
I have nothing for either of them.
Tengo nada por ninguno de los dos.
不，亲爱的苏。
No, dear Sue.
No, querida Sue.
好吧，没关系。
OK that's fine.
Bueno, está bien.
已经给我了。
To me already.
A mí ya.
是的，它是你的。
Yes, it's yours.
Sí, va tuya.
我要去玩了。
I'm going to play.
Voy a juego.
玩多少钱？
Play for how much?
¿Jugar por cuánto?
不，他们会为我打破它。
No, they're going to break it for me.
No, me la van a partir.
你保留那封小信。
You keep that little letter.
Vos te quedas esa cartita.
是的，我告诉过你的那个，我告诉过你的那个，但仅此而已。
Yes, the one I told you, the one I told you, but nothing more.
Sí, la que te dije, la que te dije, pero nada más.
这样我们就会赢。
With that we are going to win.
Con esa vamos a ganar.
红润。
Rosy.
这会让他们付出代价，瞧。
This is going to cost them, look.
Esta les va a costar, mira.
这将使他失去他仅有的一张卡。
It's going to cost him the only card he has.
le va a costar la única carta que tiene.
作为？
As?
¿Cómo?
想要
Wanna
Quiero
你把所有东西都放了吗？
Do you put everything?
¿Pone todo?
没有，但是什么也没有。
No, but it has nothing.
No, pero no tiene nada.
那时我已经赢了。
I already won then.
Ya gané entonces.
不不！
No no!
¡No, no!
但我们没有注意到他的迹象。
But we didn't catch his signs.
Pero que no le pillamos las señas.
没关系，冷静，冷静。
It doesn't matter, calm down, calm down.
No importa, tranquila, tranquila.
我什么都没有。
I had nothing.
No tenía nada.
我什么都没有。
I didn't have anything.
Yo no tenía nada.
不，不，不，不。
No, no, no, no.
没问题。
No problem.
No hay problema.
从这只手来看，它是我们的。
From this hand it is ours.
De esta mano es nuestra.
布埃诺，13-9。
Bueno, 13-9.
13-9。
13-9.
那我就走了
I'm going then.
Voy entonces.
孤独。
Lonely.
Solita.
来吧，来吧。
Come, come.
Vení, vení.
他正在订购。
He is ordering.
Está encargando.
我放什么？
What do I put?
¿Qué pongo?
一点点。
A little one.
Una chiquita.
这一定有一个伟大的。
This must have a great one.
Este debe tener una gran.
一点点的代价就让他付出了代价。
A little one costs him.
Un chiquita le cuesta.
小姑娘，真是难为她了。
Little girl, it's hard for her.
Chiquita, le cuesta.
如果是二，我就坚决反对。
If it's a two, I put my foot down.
Si es un dos, pongo pata.
别忘了他。
Don't forget about him.
No te olvides de él.
没人要送还是不送吗？
Can no one have it to send or not?
¿Ninguno lo puede tener para enviar o no?
他为你说的，他说的。
He said it for you, he said it.
Lo dijo para vos, lo dijo.
不，不，但他们问你，他们问你。
No, no, but they ask you, they ask you.
No, no, pero te preguntan, a ti preguntan.
他说的！
He said it!
¡Lo dijo!
我们看看他怎么说？
Let's see, how did he say?
A ver, ¿cómo dijo?
他说的！
He said it!
¡Lo dijo él!
你有没有？
Do you have?
¿Tenés?
嗯，无意中，但是……他不是骗子！
Well, unintentionally, but... He's not a liar!
Pues sin querer, pero... ¡No es un mentiroso!
如果他们要起诉我的话...
If they are going to charge me...
Si me van a cobrar...
这是比赛。
It's the match.
es el partido.
我没有。
I don't have it.
No lo tengo.
他杀人了吗？
Did he kill?
¿El mato?
看看吧，呵呵
Look, huh.
Guarda, eh.
来。
Come.
Vení.
想？
Want?
¿Quieres?
不，不，不。
No, no, no.
我无法发出信号，我可以一起去……好吧，别拍连续剧了。
I can't signal, I can go with... Well, don't do series.
No puedo hacer señal, puedo ir con... Bueno, no haga serie.
带着一个小女孩和一切。
With a little girl and everything.
Con una chiquita y todo.
带着一点点来看看吧。
With a little one, let's see.
Con una chiquita, a ver.
我才21岁，你不会喜欢的。
I was 21, you're not going to like it.
Yo tenía 21, no le va a gustar.
这会让你付出代价，瞧。
This one is going to cost you, look.
Le va a costar esta, mira.
布埃诺。
Bueno.
我们的第一个。
Our first.
La primera nuestra.
马特奥和贝尼。
Mateo and Beni.
Mateo y Beni.
多么令人愤慨啊！
What an outrage!
¡Qué barbaridad!
很重要。
Much point.
我的天啊。
Oh my god.
14 事情还没有结束。
14 and it's not over.
14 y no se acabó.
怎么样？
How is?
¿Cómo es?
¿14 y 10？
¿14 y 10?
14 岁 10 岁。
14 y 10.
这个号码也是婆婆的。
This number is the mother-in-law's too.
Este número es de la suegra también.
第10个！
The 10th!
¡El 10!
哦，你忘了！
Oh, you forgot!
¡Ah, lo olvidaste!
我的上帝！
My God!
¡Dios mío!
好吧，如果你想...
Well, if you want...
Bueno, si vos querés...
和国王国王
and king king
y rey rey
列表？
List?
¿Listo?
不不。
No no.
No, no.
他们会说，这是一颗豆子。
They would have said it, it's a bean.
Lo hubiesen dicho, es un poroto.
当然。
Of course.
Claro.
我有一点，但都没有。
I have a little bit, but neither.
Yo tengo un poquito, pero tampoco.
这里的豆子多么稀有啊。
How rare beans are here.
Qué raros son los porotos acá.
我有，但不是哇，但是哦，好吧
I have it but it's not wow but oh well
yo tengo pero no es guau pero bueno
不，他们会说，他们会扔掉
no, they are going to say, they are going to throw out
no, van a decir, van a echar
不足之处之一。
And the lack is one.
Y la falta es uno.
生活中缺失。
Missing in life.
Falta en vida.
是的，我想要。
Yes I want.
Sí, quiero.
是的，我想要。
Yes I want.
Sí, quiero.
21. 26.
快点！
Come on!
¡Vamos!
快点！
Come on!
¡Vamos!
快点！
Come on!
¡Vamos!
是的！
Yeah!
¡Sí!
是的！
Yeah!
¡Sí!
快点！
Come on!
¡Vamos!
¡21！
¡21!
呃！
¡Uy!
请不要发动攻击！
Don't put the attack on, please!
¡No pones el ataque, por favor!
事实是？
The fact that?
¿El qué?
要我告诉你窍门吗？
Shall I tell you trick?
¿Le digo truco?
是的！
Yeah!
¡Sí!
是的！
Yeah!
¡Sí!
来吧，该死的！
Come on, damn it!
¡Vamos, carajo!
多给点小费。
Tip more.
Punta más.
多给点小费。
Tip more.
Punta más.
不！
¡No!
但你是一个奇迹，约翰！
But you are a miracle, John!
¡Pero vos sos un milagro, John!
为什么你有...？
Why did you have...?
¿Por qué tenías...?
为什么你总是表现得很穷？
Why do you always act poor?
¿Por qué siempre te haces el pobrecito?
让我看看，我已经知道你有什么了。
Let's see, I already knew what you have. Oh, no!
A ver, ya sabía lo que tenés ¡Ah, no!
牛！
Cattle!
¡Ganado!
我的目光注视着她
I had my eyes on her
La tenía mirada
谢谢你所做的一切，宝贝。
Thanks for everything, baby.
Gracias por todo, bebé.
嗯，已经实现了，已经实现了。
Well, it was fulfilled, it was fulfilled.
Bueno, se cumplió, se cumplió.
冠军。
the champions.
los campeones.
谢谢你的到来，谢谢罗德里，很高兴，我们爱你，我们爱你。
Thank you for coming, thank you Rodri, a pleasure, we love you, we love you.
Gracias por venir, gracias Rodri, un placer, los amamos, los amamos.
谢谢，这是一种荣幸。
Thank you, it has been an honor.
Gracias, ha sido un honor.
并在这里赢得他们。
and win them here.
y ganarlos acá.
伙计们，谢谢你们来到这里，这是我的荣幸，这是我的荣幸。
Guys, thank you for coming, it has been an honor, this is an honor, have you here.
Chicos, gracias por venir, ha sido un honor, esto es un honor, tenlos acá.
你让国家、人民幸福，我们非常爱你。
You make the country, the people happy, and we love you very much.
Ustedes alegran al país, al pueblo y los amamos mucho.
我说一件事。
I say one thing.
Yo digo una cosa.
在介绍我的下一位客人之前。
before introducing my next guest.
antes de presentar a mi próxima invitada.
我希望您看到返回到我的程序的这种格式。
I want you to see this format that returns to my program.
Quiero que vean este formato que vuelve a mi programa.
节省几百万，我能说一下具体金额吗？
Save the millions for, can I say the amount?
Salven los millones por, ¿puedo decir la cantidad?
Ciel 百万比索。
Ciel million pesos.
Ciel millones de pesos.
苏珊娜经典回归。
A Susana classic returns.
Vuelve un clásico de Susana.
剧本出来了，有几个。
The scripts come out, a couple.
Salen los guiones, una pareja.
七个问题，一亿比索岌岌可危。
Seven questions, 100 million pesos at stake.
Siete preguntas, 100 millones de pesos en juego.
他们能否应对紧张并避免跌倒？
Will they be able to handle the tension and avoid the fall?
¿Podrán manejar la tensión y evitar la caída?
拯救数百万人。
Save the millions.
Salve los millones.
拯救数百万人。
Save the millions.
Salve los millones.
下周日晚上10点首播。
Premiering next Sunday at 10 pm.
Estreno desde el próximo domingo a las 10 de la noche.
所以我们有两场1亿的比赛。
So we have two games of 100 million.
O sea que tenemos dos juegos de 100 millones.
因为，记住，首先我告诉你，布伦卡·佩德……
Because, remember, first I tell you that Brunca Perder...
Porque, acuérdense, primero les digo que Brunca Perder...
我怎么敢和世界冠军交手？
How dare I play against the world champions?
¿Cómo me atrevo a jugar contra los campeones del mundo?
他们整天都在玩恶作剧！
They spend all day playing tricks!
¡Están todo el día jugando al truco!
我就是杀手！
Killers I am!
¡Mataradas soy!
我的天啊！
Oh my God!
¡Ay, Dios mío!
不，我喜欢他们赢了。
No, I love that they won.
No, me encanta que hayan ganado.
他们是世界冠军。
They are the world champions.
Son los campeones del mundo.
他们必须赢得。
They have to be earned.
Tienen que ganarse.
好吧，我们再次记住这一点，因为有 1 亿。
Well, we remember this again because there are 100 million.
Bueno, volvemos a recordar esto porque son 100 millones.
让我们通过 su 再次操作面板。
Let's play with the panel again via su.
Volemos a jugar con el panel en vía su.
拨打 9,009 或扫描二维码，我们进行抽奖，我会给您打电话
at 9,009 or scan the QR, we will do the draw, I will call you
al 9.009 o escanea el QR vamos a hacer el sorteo yo te llamo
你可以赢得一亿比索。
and you can win 100 million pesos.
y vos podés ganar 100 millones de pesos.
是时候展示它了。
The time has come to present it.
Ha llegado el momento de presentarla.
大家都别喊了！
Don't everyone shout!
¡No briten todos!
我早就知道他们会尖叫，我就知道，呵呵。
I already knew they were going to scream before, I knew, huh.
Ya sabía que iban a gritar antes, sabía, eh.
布埃诺。
Bueno.
她是城市音乐中最重要的艺术家之一。
She is one of the most important artists in urban music.
Es una de las artistas más importantes de la música urbana.
玛丽亚·贝塞拉！
Maria Becerra!
¡María Becerra!
与自动，半狂热，它如何坐在不反弹自动
with an automatic, semi fanatic, how it sits without bouncing the automatic
con un automático, semi fanático, como se sienta sin rebotar el automático
玛丽亚！
¡María!
你好！
Hello!
¡Hola!
很高兴，无论如何我们走吧，谢谢你，你好
a pleasure, let's go anyway, thank you, hello
un placer, sueltas igualmente, gracias, hola
每个人都为你疯狂。
Everyone is crazy about you.
Todos están enloquecidos con vos.
今天我们选择一个程序。
Today we choose a program.
Hoy elegimos un programón.
世界冠军是玛丽亚·贝塞拉。
The world champions in María Becerra.
Los campeones del mundo en María Becerra.
极好的。
Incredible.
Increíble.
惊人的。
Awesome.
Impresionante.
玛丽亚，多么美丽的基地啊。
Maria, what a beautiful base.
María, qué base linda.
他刚刚获得银牌。
He just silvered.
Acaba de platear.
所有的男孩，多么伟大。
All the boys, how great.
Todos los chicos, qué bárbaro.
我四年前离开这里。
I left here four years ago.
Yo hace cuatro años me fui de acá.
不，20号我就离开了。
No, in the 20th I left.
No, en el 20 me fui.
当你回来时，你就是布宜诺斯艾利斯的明星，宝贝。
And you come back and you are the star of Buenos Aires, the baby.
Y vos vuelvo y sos la estrella de Buenos Aires, la nena.
正如他们所说的，来自阿根廷的女孩。
As they call you, the girl from Argentina.
Como te dicen, la nena de Argentina.
谁给了你这个阿根廷女孩？
Who gave you the girl from Argentina?
¿Quién te puso la nena de Argentina?
首先我们用歌曲的形式说出来，就像来自阿根廷的女孩一样。
And first we said it in a song pattern, like the girl from Argentina.
Y primero lo dijimos en una pauta de una canción, como la nena de Argentina.
我们在歌曲结束时所说的话，就在那里，人们开始告诉我他们所看到的
things we said at the end of the song and well, and there it was, people started telling me what they saw as
cosas que decíamos al final de la canción y bueno y ahí quedó me lo empezó a decir la gente viste como
当然是为了犒劳一下自己。
Of course, to pamper yourself.
Claro, como para mimarte.
是的，是的，就在那里。
Yes, yes, and there it was.
Sí, sí, y ahí quedó.
多好啊。
How nice.
Qué lindo.
我喜欢宠着你。
I like pampering you.
Me gusta la mimarte.
是的，它很漂亮。
Yes, it's beautiful.
Sí, es hermosa.
非常好！
Very good!
¡Muy bien!
但我希望你能告诉我你是如何成为这个令人印象深刻的明星的。
But I would love for you to tell me how you came to this impressive stardom.
Pero me encantaría que me cuentes cómo llegaste a este estrellato impresionante.
你的离开怎么样？
How was your departure?
¿Cómo fue tu salida?
你什么时候决定...
When did you decide...
¿Cuándo decidiste...
带上他们所有人，出去……而事实是……
take them all ahead and go out there to... And the truth is...
llevarte por delante a todas y salir ahí al... Y la verdad que...
我从 2019 年开始专业发行音乐。
I started releasing music professionally in 2019.
Yo empecé a sacar música profesionalmente en el 2019.
我发行了我的第一张EP。
I released my first EP.
Saqué mi primer EP.
这是三首歌，而且，我并没有就此停止。
It was three songs together and, well, I didn't stop from there.
que fueron tres canciones juntas y, bueno, y de ahí no paré.
事实是，从一开始……但这些都是在 TikTok 上发布的。
The truth is that from the first... But those came out on TikTok.
La verdad que desde el primer... Pero esas salían por TikTok.
不，通过 YouTube。
No, through YouTube.
No, por YouTube.
哦，对于 YouTube。
Oh, for YouTube.
Ah, por YouTube.
通过 YouTube，还有 Spotify。
Through YouTube and, well, Spotify too.
Por YouTube y, bueno, Spotify también.
好吧，在我也在网络等上制作内容之前，我显然将它们从那里推到了我的歌曲中。
and well, before I also made content on networks etc. and I obviously pushed them from there to my songs.
y bueno yo antes también hacía contenido en redes etcétera y los empujaba desde ahí obviamente a mis canciones
好吧，从第一刻起他们就受到了热烈的欢迎，事实是
And well, from the first moment they had a great reception, the truth is
Y bueno, desde el primer momento tuvieron un gran recibimiento, la verdad
例如，谁发现了您，谁给您打电话并告诉您......
For example, who discovered you, who called you on the phone and told you...
Por ejemplo, ¿quién te descubrió, quién te llamó por teléfono y te dijo...
他告诉你，贝塞拉小姐，我有一份合同给你，诸如此类的东西。
And he told you, Miss Becerra, I have a contract for you, something, something like that.
Y te dijo, señorita Becerra, tengo un contrato para usted, algo, algo así.
事实上，我从很小的时候就开始唱歌了。
And well, the truth is that I have been singing since I was very young.
Y bueno, la verdad es que yo canto desde que soy muy chica.
你一直喜欢他。
You always liked him.
Siempre te gustó.
总是这样，从很小的时候开始。
Always, from a very young age.
Siempre, desde muy chica.
我从很小的时候就开始做音乐喜剧、戏剧、唱歌。
I did musical comedy, theater, singing, from a very young age.
Hice comedia musical, teatro, canto, desde muy chica.
好吧，没什么，我已经唱歌了，并且开始在 YouTube 上制作内容。
And well, nothing, I already sang and I started making content on YouTube.
Y bueno, nada, yo ya cantaba y empecé haciendo contenido en YouTube.
有一次我的一段视频走红了，我就说，好吧，到了适当的时候我就会利用它。
Once I went viral with a video and I said, well, in due time I'm going to take advantage of it.
Una vez me volví viral con un video y dije, bueno, en mi momento lo voy a aprovechar.
当然。
Of course.
Claro.
我想成为明星。
I wanted to be a star.
Quería ser una estrella.
我开始上传视频，制作喜剧视频，博客，一切，时不时我会放一些封面，看到了吗？
And I started uploading videos, I made comedy videos, blogs, everything and from time to time I would put in some covers, see?
Y empecé a subir videos, hacía videos de comedia, blogs, de todo y de vez en cuando metía unos covers, ¿viste?
演唱蕾哈娜、麦莉·赛勒斯、爱莉安娜·格兰德
singing Rihanna, Miley Cyrus, Ariana Grande
cantando Rihanna, Miley Cyrus, Ariana Grande
当然，我向人们展示，好吧，我这样做，但这实际上是我喜欢的。
Sure, and I was showing people, okay, I do this, but this is actually what I like.
Claro, y yo les mostraba a la gente, ok, hago esto, pero esto es en realidad lo que me gusta.
好吧，到了某个时刻，我真的很想全身心投入其中，也就是说，我想以此谋生。
And well, there came a point where I really wanted to dedicate myself to that, that is, I wanted to make a living from it.
Y bueno, llegó un punto en el que realmente me quería dedicar a eso, o sea, quería vivir de eso.
我有很多观众，同样的人告诉我，他们唱歌。
and I had a large audience and the same people told me, they sang.
y tenía una gran audiencia y la misma gente me lo decía, cantaba.
创作歌曲，我们会听你的，我们会听你的，好吧，在我的动画中......
makes songs, we are going to listen to you, we are going to listen to you and well, in my anime...
hace canciones, nosotros te vamos a escuchar, te vamos a bancar y bueno, en mi anime...
这就是一切的结果，我的意思是……天哪！
And that's where it all came out, I mean... Oh my God!
Y ahí salió todo, o sea... ¡Dios mío!
它变得动画化了！
It's getting animated!
¡Se animaste!
是的……但是，听我说……
Yes... But, listen to me...
Sí... Pero, oíme...
玛丽亚。
María.
我爱你们所有人，我爱你们宝贝
I love you all, I love you baby
Ya todo te amo, te amo nena
这是一种爱。
It's a love.
Es un amor.
谢谢，非常感谢。
Thank you, thank you very much.
Gracias, muchas gracias.
现在看来，令人印象深刻...
Now, it's impressive...
Ahora, es impresionante...
谢谢！
¡Gracias!
多么爱啊！
What love!
¡Qué amor!
太感谢了！
Thank you so much!
¡Muchas gracias!
很高兴这一切发生在你身上。
It's very nice that all this happens to you.
Es muy lindo que te pase todo esto.
是的，事实是。
Yes, the truth is.
Sí, la verdad que sí.
但他们告诉我，你填满了两条河。
But they told me, you filled two rivers.
Pero a mí me dijeron, llenaste dos rivers.
是的。
Yeah.
Sí.
那是马上，马上。
That was right away, right away.
Eso fue enseguida, enseguida.
是的，事实是它们就这样卖完了，我的意思是，这是巨大的，是的。
Yes, and the truth is that they sold out just like that, I mean, it was tremendous, yes.
Sí, y la verdad es que se agotaron así nomás, o sea, fue tremendo, sí.
他们问一点，他们问。
They ask a little, they ask.
Peden un poco, peden.
但你知道什么...
but what do you know...
pero que se...
河，又一波来了！
River, another one is coming!
¡River, viene otro!
又一个来了！
Another one is coming!
¡Otro viene!
我不知道，我们还不知道。
I don't know, we don't know yet.
No sé, no lo sabemos todavía.
我们正在等待报价。
We are waiting for the offer.
Estamos esperando la oferta.
我们正在观察。
We are watching.
Estamos viendo.
希望如此。
Hopefully.
Ojalá.
但这令人印象深刻。
But it's impressive.
Pero es impresionante.
当这件事发生在你身上，写满两本书时，你怎么想？
And what did you think when that happened to you, filling two books?
¿Y vos qué pensaste cuando te pasó eso, llenar dos libros?
是的，这太棒了，这太棒了，因为，好吧，事实是，人民，他们给了我这个荣誉。
Yes, it was tremendous, it was tremendous because, well, the people, the truth is, who granted me the honor.
Sí, fue tremendo, fue tremendo porque, bueno, la gente, la verdad que me concedió el honor.
我是第一个创造两条河流的阿根廷人，但如果不是的话，一些非常沉重的东西就消失了
and I was the first Argentine to make two rivers but if not something very heavy went away
y fui la primera argentina en hacer dos river pero si no se fue algo muy heavy
这是真的，令人难以置信。
It's true, it's incredible.
Es verdad, es increíble.
我在那里见过迈克尔·杰克逊和麦当娜。
I had seen Michael Jackson and Madonna there.
Yo ahí había visto a Michael Jackson y a Madonna.
真实是美丽的，没什么，独特的，令人难忘的。
The truth is beautiful, nothing, something unique, unforgettable.
La verdad es hermoso, nada, algo único, inolvidable.
想知道，多么美妙啊。
Wonder, how wonderful.
Maravilla, qué maravilla.
你现在工作很多。
You're working a lot now.
Estás trabajando muchísimo ahora.
你开始游览。
You start a tour.
Empezás una gira.
是的，是的，但是这是穿越欧洲，这次旅行怎么样？
Yes, yes, but it's through Europe, what's the tour like?
Sí, sí, pero es por Europa, ¿cómo es la gira?
因此他们是其他国家。
Hence they were other countries.
De ahí que eran otros países.
你首先是在酷玩乐队唱歌，对吧？
You first sang with Coldplay, right?
Primero cantaste con Coldplay, ¿no?
不，不，不。
No, no, no.
你的信息量很大。
You are a lot of information.
Eres mucha info.
不，停下来。
No, stop.
No, para.
请记住，我住在乡下。
Remember that I lived in the country.
Acuérdense que yo vivía en el campo.
玛丽！
¡Mari!
而且天气很好。
And the weather is good.
Y el tiempo es bueno.
你刚刚和一个美国人唱歌。
You just sang with an American.
Acabas de cantar con un americano.
哦，好吧，我最近和 Michael Bublé 和 Jason Derulo 一起唱歌。
Oh well, I sang with Michael Bublé and Jason Derulo recently.
Ah bueno, cante con Michael Bublé y Jason Derulo hace poco.
我想说的话又说出来了。
what I wanted to say and the other one came out.
lo que yo quería decir y me salió el otro.
迈克尔，迈克尔，让我着迷。
Michael, Michael, fascinates me.
Michael, Michael, me fascina.
这种类型的音乐。
This type of music.
Este tipo de música.
他唱歌令人难以置信。
He sings incredible.
Canta increíble.
不，不，不，不。
No, no, no, no.
很漂亮，真的。
Beautiful, really.
Hermoso, la verdad.
每个人都接受你...是吗？
And everyone accepts you as... Yes?
Y todos te aceptan como... ¿Sí?
也许他们只是互相尊重对方是一位伟大的艺术家。
that maybe they simply respect each other as a great artist.
que igual simplemente se respetan como una gran artista.
事实是，是，不是……
The truth is yes, no...
La verdad sí, que no...
你看，当你和真正优秀的人一起工作时，你会意识到，明白吗？
You see, when you work with really great people, you realize, see?
Viste, cuando trabajas con gente grande de verdad, te das cuenta, ¿viste?
他们不信任你的才华。
They distrust you in your talent.
Te desconfían en tu talento.
他们没有理由羡慕任何事情。
They have no reason to envy anything.
no tienen por qué envidiar nada.
因为他们是非常谦虚的人，非常脚踏实地......
because they are very humble people, very grounded with...
porque son gente muy humilde, muy a tierra con los...
在整个地球上，非常勤奋，你看到了吗？
on the total earth, very hardworking, you see?
sobre la tierra total, muy trabajadora, ¿viste?
首先。
That first of all.
Eso ante todo.
然后你就会意识到并理解他们为什么会在这个位置。
Then you realize and understand why they are where they are too.
Entonces te das cuenta y entendés por qué están donde están también.
我喜欢她说的很少，因为事情就是这样。
I love what she says so little, because that's how it is.
Me encanta lo que dice tan chiquita, porque es así.
有才华的人没有理由羡慕你，相反，相信南方
A guy who has talent has no reason to envy you, on the contrary, trust the south
un tipo que tiene talento no te tiene por qué envidiar, al contrario, confía en el sur
他总是最可爱的。
He always had the cutest.
Siempre tendía el más choto.
真相永远是。
The truth is always.
La verdad que siempre.
我总是，几乎总是，几乎总是与其他艺术家有令人难以置信的经历。
I always, almost always, almost always had incredible experiences with other artists.
Siempre, casi siempre, casi siempre tuve increíbles experiencias con los demás artistas.
事实上，他们都是一种荣誉。
The truth is that they are all an honor.
La verdad que son todos un honor.
人们立刻就爱你，当他们向我展示时我也爱你
People loved you at once and I loved you when they showed me
La gente te amó de una y yo te amé cuando me mostraron
你用照片做的一件事。
one thing you did with a photo.
una cosa que hiciste con una foto.
哦是的！
Oh yes!
¡Ay, sí!
我死了！
I died!
¡Me morí!
附上一张你的照片。
With a photo of you.
Con una foto tuya.
是的，我死了！
Yes, I died!
¡Sí, me morí!
我死了！
I died!
¡Me morí!
我们必须看到它，我不知道我们是否可以在任何地方看到它。
We have to see it, I don't know if we can see it anywhere.
La tenemos que ver, no sé si la podemos ver en algún lado.
但这太棒了，我在……看。
But it's fabulous, I saw it in the... Look.
Pero es fabulosa, yo la vi en el... Mira.
谢谢！
¡Gracias!
当然，多么棒啊！
Of course, how great!
Por supuesto ¡Qué genial!
是的，小手，一切，一切
Yes, the little hand, everything, everything
Sí, la manito, todo, todo
芭芭拉，但是你是怎么想出这个办法的呢？
Barbara, but how did you come up with it?
Bárbara, ¿pero cómo se te ocurrió?
你是一个创造者。
You are a creator.
Sos una creadora.
是的，好吧，一开始我想穿那件衣服。
Yes, well, at first I wanted to come with that dress.
Sí, bueno, en principio yo tenía ganas de venir con ese vestido.
这里是采访。
Here the interview.
Acá la entrevista.
哦，我的爱人！
Oh, my love!
¡Ay, mi amor!
你有没有看到？
Did you see?
¿Viste?
我想这么做。
I wanted to do that.
Tenía ganas de hacer eso.
但是，嘿，没什么，这是一个很大的话题，你明白吗？
But hey, nothing, it was quite a topic, you see?
Pero bueno, nada, era todo un tema, ¿viste?
所以我们说，好吧，对物流和一切来说更好，更好......
So we said, well, better for logistics and everything, better...
Entonces dijimos, bueno, mejor por logística y por todo, mejor...
拍张照片以示致敬。
take the photo in tribute.
hacer la foto en homenaje.
这对我来说似乎是神圣的，对我来说这本书就像是一张面孔的封面。
It seemed divine to me, it seemed to me that the book was a cover of faces.
Me pareció divino, me pareció que el libro era una tapa de caras.
很久以前的事了，但我不知道是5月25日还是类似的日子。
from a long time ago, but I don't know if it's for May 25 or something like that.
de hace mucho tiempo, pero no sé si es para el 25 de mayo o algo así.
当他们向我展示它时，我说我简直不敢相信，我喜欢它，我喜欢它，这是一件很棒的事情。
such a tenderness when they showed it to me that I said I can't believe it, I love it, I love it, it's a great thing.
una ternura cuando me la mostraron que dije no puedo creer, la amo, la amo, es una cosa genial.
谢谢！
¡Gracias!
你什么时候有专辑？
When do you have the album?
¿Cuándo tenés el álbum?
好了，专辑完成了。
Well, the album is done.
Bueno, el álbum ya está.
准备好了。
It's ready.
Ya está listo.
是的，就是这样。
Yes, that's it.
Sí, ya está.
准备好了。
It's ready.
Está listo.
是的，是的。
Yes, yes.
Sí, sí.
好吧，剪辑、单曲都出来了。
And well, the cuts, the singles are coming out there.
Y bueno, están saliendo ahí los cortes, los singles.
是的。
Yeah.
Sí.
但是，嘿，它将于明年初完整发布。
But hey, it will finish coming out in full at the beginning of next year.
Pero bueno, va a terminar de salir completo a principios del año que viene.
当然，因为有声音。
Of course, because there is a voice.
Claro, porque hay una voz.
当然，当然。
Of course, of course.
Claro, claro.
现在我们看到的是如何...
Now what we're seeing is how...
Ahora lo que estamos viendo es cómo...
让每个版本都有不同的工作，视频剪辑，所有的营销......
make each release a different job, the video clip, all the marketing...
hacer cada lanzamiento un trabajo diferente, el videoclip, todo el marketing...
按，就是一切，一切都是一个世界。
press, that is, everything, everything is a world.
de prensa, o sea, todo, todo es un mundo.
所以没什么，我们提前计划好了。
So nothing, we are planning that well in advance.
Entonces nada, estamos planeando eso bien con tiempo.
是的，显然！
Yes, obviously!
¡Sí, obvio!
哦，我的爱人，我爱他！
Oh, my love, I love him!
¡Ay, mi amor, lo amo!
我爱你，我爱你。
I love you, I love you.
Te amo, te amo.
我想知道一件事。
There is one thing I want to know.
Hay una cosa que quiero saber.
伙计们，但我想知道一件事。
Guys, but there is one thing I want to know.
Chicos, pero hay una cosa que quiero saber.
这一点我并没有错。
And I'm not wrong about this.
Y esto no me estoy equivocando.
玛丽亚的梦想是……
Maria's dream was...
El sueño de María era...
曾经成为一名职业足球运动员
be a professional soccer player at one point
ser jugadora de fútbol profesional en un momento
您是否看到我们经历过生命中的时刻？
Did you see that we go through moments in life?
¿Viste que pasamos por momentos en la vida?
足球给了你，当我 13 或 14 岁的时候，它开始或多或少地给了我这样的东西
football gave you and it started to give me more or less when I was 13 or 14 around like that
te dio el fútbol y me dio me empezó a dar más o menos cuando tenía 13 14 por ahí así
是的！
Yeah!
¡Sí!
噢噢，视频！
Oh, oh, video!
¡Ay, ay, video!
¡米拉德，米拉德，米拉德！
¡Mirad, mirad, mirad!
不，他确实这么做了。
No, he really did that.
No, de verdad hacía eso.
哦，上帝，遮住我的脸。
Oh, God, cover my face.
Ay, Dios, tapame la cara.
卢里亚并没有处于最佳状态。
Lurria was not at my best.
Lurria no estaba en mi mejor momento.
我就在那里。
There I am.
Ahí estoy.
事实上，后面有一个精灵。
In fact, an elf back there.
De hecho, un duende ahí atrás.
神圣的。
Divine.
Divino.
但看看你！
But look at you!
¡Pero mira vos!
她很好，她很好！
She was good, she was good!
¡Era buena, era buena!
这很好，我不会否认事实。
And it was good, I'm not going to deny the truth.
Y era buena, no te lo voy a negar la verdad.
不，我去这里尝试了一个月。
No, I went to try out here for the month.
No, yo me fui a probar aquí el mes.
是的。
Yeah.
Sí.
我留在那里，在青年队中担任预备队球员。
And I stayed there, I played the reserve there in the youth teams.
Y quedé ahí, jugaba la reserva ahí en inferiores.
是的，但她很小。
Yes, but she was very small.
Sí, pero era muy chiquita.
但这是残酷的。
But it's brutal.
Pero es brutal.
我想成为一名球员。
I want to be a player.
Quiero ser jugadora.
已经三个了
Three already.
Tres ya.
是的。
Yeah.
Sí.
我的意思是，想象一下，我也想成为一名消防员。
I mean, well, I also wanted to be a firefighter, imagine.
O sea, bueno, también quise ser bombera, imaginate.
是的，激情抓住了我。
Yes, passions grabbed me.
Sí, a mí me agarraban pasiones.
我非常...非常热情，你看到了吗？
I'm very... very effusive, you see?
Yo soy muy... muy efusiva, ¿viste?
突然间，就像一个水族馆，就像……
And, suddenly, like an aquarium, like...
Y, de repente, de acuario, como...
像我这样的！
Like me!
¡Como yo!
我们已经知道我们是如何工作的，你看到我们有这个......
We already know how we work, you saw that we have this...
Ya sabemos como funcionamos, viste que tenemos esta...
这种性格非常爆炸，突然出现。
This very explosive personality, out of nowhere.
Esta personalidad muy explosiva, de la nada.
然后我对某件事感到兴奋，突然我开始喜欢，我不知道，花园，小植物，我已经想开始一个专业的花园了。
Then I get excited about something, suddenly I start to like, I don't know, the garden, the little plants and I already want to start a professional garden.
Entonces me ilusiono con algo, de repente me empieza a gustar, no sé, la huerta, las plantitas y ya quiero armarme una huerta profesional.
是的，当然，一切都在很大程度上。
Yes, of course, everything in a big way.
Sí, claro, todo a lo grande.
一切都在很大程度上，是的，是的。
Everything in a big way, yes, yes.
Todo a lo grande, sí, sí.
我也喜欢你喜欢动物。
And I also love that you like animals.
Y me encanta también que te gusten los animales.
你有什么动物？
What animals do you have?
¿Qué animales tenés?
今天我有五只狗和四只猫。
Today I have five dogs and four cats.
Hoy tengo cinco perros y cuatro gatos.
哦，他们相处得很好。
Oh, and they get along well.
Ah, y se llevan bien.
是的，我的宝贝。
Yes, my baby.
Sí, mi bebé.
我说，猫与狗。
Cats with dogs, I say.
Los gatos con los perros, digo.
是的，事实是……他们从小就长大了，相处得很好。
Yes, the truth is that... They grew up when they were little and they get along well.
Sí, la verdad es que... Se crían de chiquitos y se llevan bien.
但我的很街头，你明白吗？
but mine are very streetwise, you see?
pero los míos son muy callejeros, ¿viste?
即使是这种类型的人也整天出去，他们在外面。
Those from even this type go out all day, they are outside.
Los de hasta estar tipo salen todo el día, están afuera.
还有在房子的屋顶上。
And on the roof of the house.
Y en el techo de la casa.
你有没有看到？
Did you see?
¿Viste?
他们喜欢单独带猫。
They love to take cats alone.
Les encanta tomar sola a los gatos.
哦，是吗？
Oh yeah?
Ah, ¿sí?
他们就这样……上不去了。
They are like this... They can't go up.
Están así... Ellos no pueden subir.
当然，然后它们在那里共存得很好，明白吗？
Of course, then they coexist well there, see?
Claro, entonces ahí conviven bien, ¿viste?
当然，当然。
Of course, of course.
Claro, claro.
哦，多可爱啊。
Oh, how cute.
Ay, qué lindo.
师父，我也养着五只狗。
Master, I also live five dogs.
Amo, también vivo cinco perros.
但我没有猫。
but I don't have cats.
pero no tengo gatos.
你不喜欢吗？
And wouldn't you like it?
¿Y no te gustaría?
我害怕，因为我的狗很大，如果它们追赶它们，如果它们
I'm afraid because my dogs are big and if they chase them, if they
Tengo miedo porque son grandes los perros míos y si los persiguen, si los
这有点危险。
And it's a little dangerous.
Y es un poco peligroso.
我发誓，我全心全意地爱动物。
I love animals with all my soul, I swear.
Yo amo los animales con toda mi alma, lo juro.
嗯，第一个在格莱美颁奖典礼上唱歌的阿根廷人。
Well, the first Argentine to also sing at the Grammys.
Bueno, la primera argentina también en cantar en los Grammys.
伙计们，格莱美奖。
Guys, the Grammys.
Chicos, los Grammys.
非常令人印象深刻
very impressive
muy impresionante
疯了，对吧？
Crazy, right?
Qué locura, ¿no?
那场比赛有多快。
How fast that race.
Qué rápido esa carrera.
一切都很快。
Everything fast.
Todo rápido.
诸如此类的一切，都打在我脸上。
Everything like that, it all hits me in the face.
Todo así, me pega todo en la cara.
我要……显然，我要前进。
And I'm going... I'm going forward, obviously.
Y yo voy... Voy para adelante, obvio.
是的，美丽。
Yes, beautiful.
Sí, hermosa.
谢谢。
Gracias.
是的，事实是……
Yes, the truth is...
Sí, la verdad que...
那个是拉丁格莱美的，你说的另一个是美国格莱美的，当然是美国的。
That one is from the Latin Grammy, the other one that you say is from the American Grammys, American, of course.
Ese es de los Latin Grammy, el otro que vos decís es de los Grammy estadounidenses, americanos, claro.
在那里我和 Shay Balvin 一起唱歌，他邀请我唱歌
and there I sang with Shay Balvin who invited me to sing
y ahí cante con Shay Balvin que me invitó a cantar
但很棒。
But great.
Pero genial.
我们给他一个吻，我爱他。
We send him a kiss, I love him.
Le mandamos un beso, lo amo.
他是一个伟大的人。
He is a great person.
Es una gran persona.
我们有巴尔文。
We had Balvin.
Lo tuvimos a Balvin.
是的。
Yeah.
Sí.
这是拉丁格莱美奖的获奖者。
And that's from the Latin Grammys.
Y eso es de los Latin Grammy.
在那里，我和巴勃罗·阿尔博兰一起唱歌，然后我唱了一首我自己的歌，我独自称之为“ojala”。
There I sang with Pablo Alborán and then I sang a song of mine that I have alone called ojala.
Ahí canté con Pablo Alborán y después canté una canción mía que tengo sola que se llama Ojalá.
就是这样。
And here it is.
Y aquí está.
多么神圣啊。
How divine.
Qué divina.
你写你的歌。
And you write your songs.
Y escribís tus canciones.
是的。
Yeah.
Sí.
谢谢！
¡Gracias!
我爱他们！
I love them!
¡Los amo!
他们是世界上最好的观众，你看到了吗？
They are the best audience in the world, did you see it?
Son el mejor público del mundo, ¿lo viste?
他们是最令人印象深刻的。
They are the most impressive.
Son los más impresionantes.
我已经知道事情会是这样，因为每次有人来......
I already knew it was going to be like this because every time one comes...
Yo ya sabía que iba a ser así porque cada vez que viene una...
如果是超级巨星，他们会疯狂地举着牌子。
If a superstar they go crazy and come with a sign.
si una superestrella se vuelven locos y vienen con un cartel.
事物和旗帜。
things and flag.
cosas y bandera.
他们总是非常有爱，来的观众都是神圣的。
They are always very loving, the audience that comes is divine.
Esos son muy cariños siempre, el público que viene son divinos.
但你几岁了？
But how old are you?
Pero ¿cuántos años tenés?
嘿！
Hey!
¡Olé!
嘿！
Hey!
¡Olé!
嘿！
Hey!
¡Olé!
嘿！
Hey!
¡Olé!
嘿！
Hey!
¡Olé!
嘿！
Hey!
¡Olé!
好吧，我就叫你 Chicho 吧。
Well, I'm going to call you Chicho.
Bueno, te voy a llamar Chicho.
他做了什么？
What did he do?
¿Qué hizo?
那是什么？
What was it?
¿Qué era?
这是一种爱！
It's a love!
¡Es un amor!
好吧，我得问你关于你男朋友 J. Rey 的事。
Well, I have to ask you about your boyfriend, J. Rey.
Bueno, te tengo que preguntar por tu novio, J. Rey.
那么……好吧……
So... well...
Así que... bueno...
确实，他们在希腊订婚了。
It's true that they got engaged in Greece.
Es verdad que se comprometieron en Grecia.
是的，在圣托里尼岛。
Yes, in Santorini.
Sí, en Santorini.
哦，多可爱啊！
Oh, how cute!
¡Ay, qué linda!
哦不，把它拿出来！
Oh no, take it out!
¡Ay, no, saca!
放更好的视频
put better videos
pongan videos mejores
不，但是看看他那样，很奇怪，你在那样的健身房里，而他......
No, but look at him like that, it's strange, you're in a gym like that and he...
No, pero míralo a él así, está raro, vos estás así en una gimnasia y él...
多么美丽的地方，我的天哪！
What a beautiful place, my God!
¡Qué lindo lugar, Dios mío!
是的，我想圣托里尼岛也是如此。
Yes, I think that is also in Santorini.
Sí, eso también creo que es en Santorini.
你怎么说？
How do you say?
¿Cómo se dice?
在一个岛上
On an island
En una isla.
在双体船上。
On a catamaran.
En un catamarán.
我们过得很糟糕。
We had a really bad time.
La pasamos re mal.
我生病了，呕吐了。
Me sick, vomited.
Me mareé, vomité.
太可怕了，是的。
Terrible, yes.
Terrible, sí.
你有一把铲子，它会移动很多。
You have a bit of a shovel for it, it moves a lot.
Le tenés un poco de pala, se mueve mucho.
一般来说不，我们喜欢乘船游览。
In general no, we like to take a boat ride.
En general no, a nosotros nos gusta pasear en lanchita.
是的当然。
Yes of course.
Sí, claro.
我们总是去，但是双体船，你看到它是什么了吗？
And we always go, but the catamaran, did you see what it is?
Y siempre vamos, pero el catamarán, ¿viste qué es?
因为它有两件事。
Because it has two things on the side.
Porque tiene dos cosas al costado.
动得更厉害了！
It moves more!
¡Se mueve más!
我们过得很糟糕。
We had a really bad time.
La pasamos re mal.
两者，两者。
Both, both.
Los dos, los dos.
我们通过了。
We passed it.
La pasamos.
你会这么说的。
You would have said it.
Lo hubieras dicho.
我们去港口吧。
Let's go to the port.
Vamos al puerto.
当然，我们折返了，是的，我们甚至无法享受这段旅程，但是，嘿，它仍然是神圣的。
Of course, we turned back, yes, we couldn't even enjoy the ride, but hey, it was divine all the same.
Claro, nos volvimos, sí, no pudimos ni disfrutar el paseo, pero bueno, fue divino igual.
一切都是神圣的。
Everything was divine.
Fue divino todo.
当他们不乘坐双体船时，你知道。
When they don't take catamarans, you know.
Cuando no tomen catamaranes, ya saben.
订婚。
Got engaged.
Nos comprometimos.
我要求做出承诺。
I asked for a commitment.
Yo le pedí compromiso.
这是戒指。
This is the ring.
Este es el anillo.
我想知道，抱歉，你是如何要求你做出承诺的？
I want to know, sorry, how did you ask for your commitments?
Yo quiero saber, perdón, ¿cómo le pediste vos compromisos?
是的。
Yeah.
Sí.
我发现他有点傻。
And I saw that he was kind of stupid.
Y lo vi que la andaba medio lerdo.
他们没有接受我的暗示，你明白吗？
And they didn't take my hints, you see?
Y no me agarraban mis indirectas, ¿viste?
如果你不问我，我就不得不问。
If you don't ask me, I'll have to ask for it.
Si no me pide lo voy a tener que pedir yo.
听我说。
Listen to me.
Escúchame.
但我已经知道他想要什么了。
But I already knew what he wanted.
Pero yo ya sabía que él quería.
每次我们谈论它时，他都告诉我，是的，我会喜欢它，我不知道什么，我不知道有多喜欢。
Every time we talked about it, he told me, yes, I would love it, I don't know what, I don't know how much.
Cada vez que hablábamos del tema, él me decía, sí, me encantaría, no sé qué, no sé cuánto.
我正要像我告诉过你的那样开始，你看到我是个混蛋。
I was going to start like I told you, you saw that I am all ass.
Iba a empezar como te dije, viste que yo soy todo a todo culo.
对一切。
To everything.
A todo.
所以我打算开始一个珠宝课程来自己制作。
So I was going to start a jewelry course to make it myself.
Entonces iba a empezar un curso de joyería para hacerlo yo misma.
不！
¡No!
这是不可能的！
It just can't be!
¡No puede ser!
她是个天才！
She's a genius!
¡Es una genia!
事情已经开始了，你看到了吗？
It had already started, you see?
Ya había empezado, ¿viste?
一切都很简单，但抽象的珠宝礼服是用它制作的
everything and well everything was simple but the abstract jewelry dresses the one made with
todo y bueno todo era sencillo pero más la joyería abstracta viste la que se hace con
用蜡和一切。
with wax and everything.
con cera y todo.
当我说的时候，我想放一块石头。
When I say, I want to put a stone.
Cuando yo digo, quiero poner una piedra.
啊，不，好吧，你必须学会​​勾引。
Ah, no, well, you have to learn to hook.
Ah, no, bueno, tenés que aprender a enganchar.
那会花费你更长的时间，而我却没有及时赶到。
That's going to take you much longer and I didn't get there in time.
Eso te va a llevar mucho más y yo no llegaba con el tiempo.
所以我说，好吧，我会完成它。
So I said, well, I'll have it done.
Entonces dije, bueno, lo mando a hacer.
我已经完成了，但我考虑了设计和一切。
And I had it done, but I thought about the design and everything.
Y lo mandé a hacer, pero pensé el diseño y todo.
¡爱！
¡Amor!
哦，你放的是……他也有一样的！
Oh, you put the... And he has the same one!
Ay, le pusiste la... ¡Y él tiene el mismo!
是的，显然。
Yes, obviously.
Sí, obvio.
我快死了，我快死了，我快死了。
I'm dying, I'm dying, I'm dying.
Me muero, me muero, me muero.
但说实话，我快要为爱而死了。
But really, I'm dying of love.
Pero de verdad, me muero de amor.
我的一生，我爱他。
My life, I love him.
Mi vida, lo amo.
我送你一个正在注视着我们的吻。
I send you a kiss that is watching us.
Te mando un beso que nos está viendo.
我也送你一个吻。
I send you a kiss too.
Yo también te mando un beso.
他是一名歌手，就是这样。
He's a singer, like that.
Es cantante, así.
是的，是的，显然。
Yes, yes, obviously.
Sí, sí, obvio.
你们有时一起唱歌吗？
Do you sing together sometimes or not?
¿Cantan juntos a veces o no?
不，不，在家里。
No, no, at home there.
No, no, en casa por ahí.
啊，在家里。
Ah, at home.
Ah, en casa.
他是和声的爱好者。
He is a fan of harmonies.
Él es fanático de las armonías.
你看，他真的很喜欢和谐。
You see, he really likes to harmonize.
Viste, le gusta mucho armonizar.
我们在车里听一首歌，他给它配音。
We are in the car listening to a song and he harmonizes it.
Vamos en el auto escuchando una canción y él la armoniza.
和谐是什么感觉？
And what is it like to harmonize?
¿Y cómo es armonizar?
当然，你把它变成第三个、第五个……我的意思是，你看到那首歌就在那里，原来的旋律吗？
Of course, you make it the third, the fifth... I mean, did you see that the song is there, the original melody?
Claro, vos le hacés la tercera, la quinta... O sea, ¿viste que está la canción, la melodía original?
是的。
Yeah.
Sí.
突然你听到背景中有一个小声音发出相同的歌词，相同的旋律，但是......
and suddenly you hear a little voice in the background that is making the same lyrics, the same melody, but...
y de repente vos escuchás de fondo una vocecita que está haciendo la misma letra, la misma melodía, pero...
更严重，你明白吗？更严重。
more acute, you understand?, more serious.
más aguda, ¿entendés?, más grave.
那是一段旋律。
That's a melody.
Eso es una melodía.
我想知道。
I would like to know.
Me gustaría saberlo.
是的，它很漂亮。
Yes, it's beautiful.
Sí, es hermoso.
和谐是美的，那就是和谐。
It is beautiful to harmonize, that is a harmony.
Es hermoso armonizar, eso es una armonía.
他很喜欢，所以有时我会唱一些东西......
And he likes it a lot, so sometimes I sing something...
Y a él le gusta mucho, entonces yo a veces canto algo...
他开始为我协调它。
and he begins to harmonize it for me.
y él me lo empieza a armonizar.
在家里我们一起唱歌。
At home we do sing together.
En casa sí cantamos juntos.
谁弹钢琴，我的生活和你想成为一个母亲。
who plays the piano, my life and you would like to be a mother.
que toca el piano, mi vida y te gustaría ser mamá.
是的，显然。
Yes, obviously.
Sí, obvio.
你有问题。
You had a problem.
Tuviste un problema.
有问题...对吗？
A problem... right?
Un problema... ¿no?
是的，是的。
Yes, yes.
Sí, sí.
我已经是一位母亲了，她告诉我。
I'm already a mother, she tells me.
Ya soy madre, me dice.
是的，是的，是的。
Yes, yes, yes.
Sí, sí, sí.
是的，我不久前发生过宫外孕。
Yes, well I had an ectopic pregnancy a while ago.
Sí, bueno tuve hace un tiempo ya un embarazo ectópico.
但这真是耻辱。
But what a disgrace.
Pero qué desgracia.
是的，是的，是的。
Yes, yes, yes.
Sí, sí, sí.
事实是，这非常困难。
The truth is that it was quite hard.
La verdad que sí fue bastante duro.
嗯，现在仍然如此，看到了吗？
Well, it still is, see?
Bueno, lo sigue siendo, ¿viste?
这是一场决斗。
It's a duel.
Es un duelo.
是的当然。
Yes of course.
Sí, claro.
一个人为另一件事做好心理准备。
One mentally prepares for something else.
Uno se prepara mentalmente para otra cosa.
他们立刻就发现了？
And they discovered it right away?
¿Y te lo descubrieron enseguida?
是的，是的，事实是，相当快。
Yes, yes, the truth is, fairly fast.
Sí, sí, la verdad, medianamente rápido.
就像上周一样，告诉他我发现了什么。
Like last week, tell him what I found out.
Como la semana, ponerle de que me enteré.
好吧，我们当时就在那里，我们要如何告诉家人呢？
And well, we were there, how are we going to tell the family?
Y bueno, estábamos ahí, ¿cómo le vamos a decir a la familia?
你看，我们说，好吧，但是让我们等等，说实话，我想等到我三个月大。
You see, we said, well, but let's wait, I wanted to wait until I was three months old, to be honest.
Viste, decíamos, bueno, pero esperemos, yo quería esperar a tener tres meses, la verdad.
因为我知道，如果你拥有的少，你就会失去它。
Because I know that if you have less, you can lose it.
Porque yo sé que si tenés menos, lo podés perder.
好吧，我很害怕，因为事实是从第一刻起我就感到很痛苦。
And well, I was afraid because the truth is that from the first moment I felt a lot of pain.
Y bueno, yo tenía miedo porque la verdad que desde el primer momento sentí muchos dolores.
是不是已经很痛苦了？
Is it already painful?
¿Hace ya dolor?
是的，很多痛苦。
Yes, a lot of pain.
Sí, muchos dolores.
是的，你过得很糟糕。
Yes, you have a very bad time.
Sí, la pasas muy mal.
非常糟糕。
Very badly.
Muy mal.
我感觉到，你看到了吗？
And I felt, did you see?
Y yo sentía, ¿viste?
我说这对我来说不是正常的怀孕，对我来说我的怀孕不好，你看到了吗？
And I said this is not a normal pregnancy for me, for me my pregnancy is not good, you see?
Y yo decía esto para mí no es un embarazo normal, para mí no está bien mi embarazo, ¿viste?
所以我...
So I...
Entonces yo...
老实说，我很害怕。
I was scared, to be honest.
Tenía miedito, la verdad.
当然，合乎逻辑，亲爱的。
Of course, logical, my love.
Claro, lógico, mi amor.
突然有一天，我正在为一场拉丁美洲活动的演讲排练
and well and suddenly one day I was just rehearsing for a presentation I had for a latingrados event
y bueno y de repente un día estaba justamente ensayando para una presentación que tenía para un evento de los latingrados
对我来说，虽然唱得很好，但在排练过程中我开始感到非常疼痛
to me and while singing well I started to have very bad pain in the middle of the rehearsal
a mí y ahí cantando bueno empecé a tener dolores muy fuerte en el medio del ensayo
你看，后来我接受采访，我的肚子肿得不得不把扣子解开。
You see, later I gave an interview and my belly was so swollen that I had to undo my button.
Viste, después di una entrevista y tenía la panza tan inflamada que me tuve que desabrochar el botón.
我告诉你，好吧，我把扣子解开了，对不起，我说，地方不对，我说，我实在受不了了，我的肚子好疼。
I told you, well, I unbuttoned the button, sorry, I say, it's not the right place, I say, I just can't take it anymore, my belly hurts a lot.
Te dije, bueno, me he desabrochado el botón, perdón, digo, no es de su ubicada, digo, es que no puedo más, me duele mucho la panza.
当然。
Of course.
Claro.
我说完就跑了，我告诉他……治疗师。
I finished and ran away, I told him... The healer.
Terminé y me fui corriendo, le dije... El sanatón.
不。
No.
朱莉在哪里？
Where was Juli?
¿A dónde estaba Juli?
共同做出决定。
To make a decision together.
Para tomar una decisión en conjunto.
什么也没有，我们要去哪里？
And nothing, where are we going?
Y nada, ¿a dónde vamos?
因为我不想去诊所...
Because I didn't want to go to a clinic...
Porque no quería ir a una clínica...
每个人都会发现我怀孕了。
and that everyone would find out that I was pregnant.
y que todo el mundo se fuera a enterar que yo estaba embarazada.
我不知道我有什么。
I didn't know what I had.
Yo no sabía que tenía.
不……然后，好吧，我打电话给一个朋友，我给她一个吻，卡米，我全心全意地爱你，谢谢你。
and no... then, well, I called a friend and I sent her a kiss Kami, I love you with all my heart, thank you.
y no... entonces, bueno, llamé a una amiga que le mando un beso Kami, te amo con todo mi corazón, gracias.
她帮助了我，她在一家诊所工作。
She helped me, she works in a clinic.
Ella me ayudó, trabaja en una clínica.
好吧，我们就去了。
And well, and we went.
Y bueno, y fuimos.
他们在那里对我进行了一项研究，他们告诉我我有内出血。
And there they did a study on me and they told me that I was having internal bleeding.
Y ahí me hicieron un estudio y me dijeron todo que estaba con una hemorragia interna.
这就是为什么它伤害了你。
That's why it hurt you.
Por eso te dolía.
这就是他受苦的原因。
That's why he suffered.
Por eso sufría.
我一生中从未感到如此痛苦。
I have never felt so much pain in my life.
Nunca sentí tanto dolor en mi vida.
是的，我过得很糟糕。
Yes, I had a very bad time.
Sí, la pasé muy mal.
好吧，他们就在那里给我做了手术。
And well, and that, and there they operated on me.
Y bueno, y eso, y ahí me operaron.
但那是最近的事，是最近的事。
But that was recently, it was recently.
Pero eso fue hace poco, fue hace poco.
是的，大约需要20天，对吗？
Yes, it will be 20 days or so, right?
Sí, hará 20 días más o menos, ¿no?
啊，不过已经很完美了。
Ah, but it's already perfect.
Ah, pero ya está perfecto.
我对你来说感觉很陌生。
I feel like new to you.
Ya te como nueva.
我不敢相信，不敢相信，这么快，因为这是一次手术。
I can't believe, I can't believe, so fast, because it's an operation.
No puedo creer, no puedo creer, tan rápido, porque es una operación.
我的意思是……当然是腹腔镜检查。
I mean... Of course, the paroscopy one.
O sea... Claro, la paroscópica.
啊，这是腹腔镜检查。
Ah, it's the paroscopy.
Ah, es la paroscópica.
哦，好吧。
Oh ok.
Ah, bueno.
这并不是说你关心或者……不，感谢上帝。
It's not that you care or... No, thank God.
No es que te importa ni... No, gracias a Dios.
那更快了。
That was faster.
Eso fue más rápido.
当然，当然。
Sure, of course.
Claro, por supuesto.
如果不是受伤的话我不能。
If not with an injury I couldn't.
Si no con una herida no podría.
是的，我今天当然不能来这里。
Yes, I couldn't be here today, of course.
Sí, hoy no podría estar acá, claro.
亲爱的，如果你不看的话我会死的。
Love, I'd die if you weren't looking.
Amor, me muero si no estabas mirando.
是的，事实是我恢复得很好，我很感激。
Yes, the truth is that I recovered well and I am very grateful.
Sí, la verdad que me recuperé re bien y estoy muy agradecida.
与医生同在，也与神同在。
With the doctors, with God too.
Con los médicos, con Dios también.
还有和你男朋友。
And with your boyfriend.
Y con tu novio.
我们走吧！
Let's go!
¡Vámonos!
他们会坚持吗？
Are they going to insist?
¿Van a insistir?
不，显然，是的。
No, obviously, yes.
No, obvio, sí.
我梦想成为一名母亲，他梦想成为一名父亲。
I dream of being a mother, he dreams of being a father.
Yo sueño con ser madre, él sueña con ser padre.
而我们的梦想，就是他是我一生的挚爱。
And we dream, that is, he is the love of my life.
Y soñamos, o sea él es el amor de mi vida.
我总是这么说。
I always say it.
Siempre lo digo.
你们在一起多久了？
How long have you been together?
¿Hace cuánto que están juntos?
两年了。
Two years.
Dos años.
是的，虽然不多，但是……
Yes, it's not much, but...
Sí, no es mucho, pero...
相当多，因为在那个年龄他们还很年轻，可能会发生变化，是或否？
quite a bit because at that age they are very young and it could be that one changes, yes or no?
bastante porque a esa edad son muy jóvenes y puede ser que uno cambie, ¿sí o no?
但你已经决定他是你一生的挚爱，仅此而已。
But you've already decided that he is the love of your life and that's it.
Pero ya decidiste que es el amor de tu vida y ya.
他是我一生的挚爱，我不想和另一个人在一起。
He is the love of my life, I don't want to be with another person.
Es el amor de mi vida, yo no quiero estar con otra persona.
除了他，我对任何人都不感兴趣，我知道对他来说这是一样的，什么也不是。
I am not interested in anyone but him and I know that for him it is the same and nothing, that.
No me interesa nadie más que él y yo sé que para él es lo mismo y nada, eso.
事实是，他是世界上最好的伴侣。
The truth is that he is the best companion in the world.
La verdad que es el mejor compañero del mundo.
你是一个太阳。
You are a sun.
Sos una sol.
那么，他们为什么给我带来这个？
Well, why did they bring me this?
Bueno, ¿para qué me trajeron esto?
玛丽亚是第一位歌唱并充满两条河流的艺术家。
María was the first artist to sing and fill two rivers.
María fue la primera artista de cantar y llenar dos rivers.
我一分钟前就已经说过了。
I already said it a minute ago.
Ya lo dije hace un minuto.
半小时，不过没关系。
half an hour, but it doesn't matter.
media hora, pero no importa.
我们有一个惊喜。
We have a surprise.
Tenemos una sorpresa.
哦，不？
Oh, no?
Ah, ¿no?
关于你在《River》中的表演的时刻。
moment about your performance in River.
momento sobre tu actuación en River.
你的妹妹艾琳·贝塞拉带来了它。
and your sister Aileen Becerra brings it.
y la trae tu hermana Aileen Becerra.
谢谢！
¡Gracias!
加油，塔拉！
Come on, Tara!
¡Vamos, tara!
你好！
Hello!
¡Hola!
唉，我要让自己哭了。
Oh, I'm going to make myself cry.
Ay, me voy a hacer llorar.
哦，就是这样。
Oh, that's it.
Ay, ya va.
河流体育俱乐部。
The River Athletic Club.
El Club Atlético de River.
Dijina María Becerra 是第一位在体育场表演和用餐的阿根廷艺术家。
Dijina María Becerra for being the first Argentine artist to perform and dine at the stadium.
Dijina María Becerra por ser la primera artista argentina en actuar y cenar el estadio.
多好啊！
How nice!
¡Qué lindo!
多好啊！
How nice!
¡Qué lindo!
多么野蛮，多么野蛮。
How barbaric, how barbaric.
Qué bárbaro, qué bárbaro.
现在别开始哭泣。
Don't start crying now.
No se pongan a llorar ahora.
哦，我的爱人。
Oh, my love.
Ay, mi amor.
艾琳，你为什么哭？
Why are you crying, Aileen?
¿Por qué lloras, Aileen?
情感。
The emotion.
La emoción.
是的，显然。
Yes, obviously.
Sí, obvio.
他们相处得很残酷，就像姐妹一样。
They get along brutally, they are like sisters.
Se llevan brutal, son como hermanas.
明显的。
Obvious.
Obvio.
请坐，请坐。
sit down, sit down, please.
siéntense, siéntense, por favor.
现在，它可以改变为音乐剧。
Now, it can be changed for the musical.
Ahora, se puede cambiar para el musical.
现在等我停止哭泣。
Now wait for me to stop crying.
Ahora espera que deje de llorar.
不，两者都有。
No, both.
No, las dos.
谢谢。
Gracias.
爸爸妈妈有这样的绿色吗？
Does mom or dad have green ones like that?
¿El papá o mamá tiene verdes así?
是的。
Yeah.
Sí.
一点一点。
A little and a little.
Un poco y un poco.
他们有一个混合。
They have a mix.
Tienen una mezcla.
笑容非常相似，神圣。
The smile is very similar, divine.
La sonrisa es muy parecida, divina.
是的，我们很相似，小时候他们告诉我们我们是双胞胎。
Yes, we are quite similar, as a child they told us that we were twins.
Sí, somos bastante parecidas, de chica nos decían que éramos gemelas.
哦真的吗？
Oh really?
¿En serio?
笑容与绿色的眼睛很相似。
The smile is very similar to the green eyes.
La sonrisa es muy parecida a los ojos verdes.
不，这是神圣的。
No, it's divine.
No, es divina.
此外，我发现他们相处得非常好。
Besides, I see that they get along fabulously well.
Aparte veo que se llevan fabulosamente bien.
如果没有的话，我真是太大胆了。
If not, it's very bold of me.
Si no es muy atrevido de mi parte.
我的爱是什么。
What my love.
Que amor mio.
我想请你向我阿姨问好。
I wanted to please ask you to say hello to my aunt.
Quería, por favor, pedíte que saludes a mi tía.
阿姨，格拉迪斯爱你。
Aunt, Gladys loves you.
Tía, Gladys te ama.
来吧，阿姨，来吧。
Come, aunt, come.
Vení, tía, vení.
格拉迪斯，来吧。
Gladys, come.
Gladys, vení.
哦，我又要让你兴奋了。
Oh, I'm going to thrill you again.
Ay, te voy a emocionar de nuevo.
那就是他爱你。
It's that he loves you.
Es que te ama.
哦，我的阿姨爱你。
Oh, my aunt loves you.
Ay, mi tía te ama.
哦，不，它杀了我。
Oh, no, it killed me.
Ay, no, me mato.
那是！
That is!
¡Eso es!
那是！
That is!
¡Eso es!
哦！
Oh!
¡Ay!
我爱你，阿姨！
I love you, aunt!
¡Te amo, tía!
是的！
Yeah!
¡Sí!
格拉迪斯·吉萨娜.
Gladys Gisana.
是的，是的，是的。
Yes, yes, yes.
Sí, sí, sí.
她用一生爱你，所以她什么都不想要，谁来迎接她。
She loves you with her life, that's why she wanted nothing, who greets her.
Ella te ama con su vida, por eso quería nada, que la saluda.
是的，是的。
Yes, yes.
Sí, sí.
哦，是的，我知道，你已经喜欢经常这样做了。
Oh yes, I know, you already love doing it often.
Ay sí, ya sé, ya se te ama hacerlo seguida.
好吧，现在你必须拨打0900，对吧？
Well, now you have to call 0900, right?
Bueno, ahora tenés que llamar el 0900, ¿no?
哦，九，九。
Oh, nine, nine.
Ay, nueve, nueve.
哦，九，九。
Oh, nine, nine.
Ay, nueve, nueve.
如果你猜得出来，那就是一百套。
If you can guess, it's a hundred suits.
Si llegas a adivinar son cien palos.
就是这样。
That's it.
Ya está.
哦，伙计。
Oh, man.
Ay, tío.
我的爱人，我的爱人。
My love, my love.
Mi amor, mi amor.
谢谢你，格拉迪斯，他们很可爱。
Thank you, Gladys, they are cute.
Gracias, Gladys, son tiernas.
她哭了。
And she cries all over.
Y llorona toda.
是的，是的，这是家族遗传的。
Yes, yes, it runs in the family.
Sí, sí, ya viene de familia la cosa.
你知道什么是超级明星吗？
And did you see what a superstar is?
¿Y viste lo que es una superestrella?
哦，我的爱人。
Oh, my love.
Ay, mi amor.
亲爱的，我只是不想见到格拉迪斯姨妈，不可能。
Love, I just don't want to see Aunt Gladys, it can't be.
Amor, es que yo no quiero ver a la tía Gladys, no puede ser.
现在...哦，没错，我们把麦克风放在上面...是的，麦克风所以什么都没有，现在我们要把它放在上面。
And now... Oh, that's right, we put the microphone on it to... Yes, the microphone so that nothing, now we are going to put it on.
Y ahora... Ah, es cierto, le ponemos el micrófono para... Sí, el micrófono para que nada, ahora la vamos a poner.
我向你致以问候。
I send you greetings.
Te mando un saludo.
我们爱你，我们爱你。
We love you, we love you.
Te queremos, te queremos.
向所有的钱问好。
Greetings to all the money.
Saludos a toda la plata.
走吧，走吧！
Let's go, let's go!
¡Vamos, vamos!
现在是女孩的音乐剧。
Now comes the girl's musical.
Ahora viene el musical de la nena.
阿根廷的法律。
of the law in Argentina.
de la ley en la Argentina.
你要改变吗？
Are you going to change?
¿Vas a cambiarte?
你会改变的，我的爱人。
You're going to change, my love.
Vas a cambiarte, mi amor.
再见，再见。
Bye, see you.
Chao, nos vemos.
亲爱的。
My love.
Mi amor.
赵，谢谢艾琳。
Chao, gracias Aline.
Chao, gracias Ailín.
谢谢，谢谢。
Thank you, thank you.
Gracias, gracias.
啊，我还是这么想的。
Ah, I was still with this.
Ah, yo seguía con esto.
哦，好吧，我现在就去改变。
Oh well, I'm going to change now.
Ah, bueno, ya me voy a cambiar.
你会改变，因为……是的。
You're going to change because... Yes.
Te vas a cambiar porque... Sí.
我想见你，我想见你……给自己点时间！
I want to see you, I want to see you... Give yourself time!
Yo quiero verte, quiero verte... ¡Date tiempo!
讲很多所以你给我时间！
Talk a lot so you give me time!
¡Habla mucho así me das tiempo!
我说了很多，我说了很多，亲爱的！
I talk a lot, I talk a lot, my love!
¡Hablo mucho, hablo mucho, mi amor!
现在它来了，现在它来了。
Now it comes, now it comes.
Ahora viene, ahora viene.
是的，要成为...
Yes, to be...
Sí, para ser...
当一切准备就绪后，请告诉我。
When everything is ready, let me know.
Cuando esté todo listo me avisan.
我已经介绍过了。
I had already presented it.
Yo ya lo había presentado.
他们是多么有爱啊！
How loving they are!
¡Qué amorosas que son!
天哪，阿格拉达姨妈杀了我。
Oh my God, Aunt Aglada kills me.
Dios mío, la tía Aglada y me mata.
能？
Can?
¿Puedo?
号码列出来了吗？
Is the number listed?
¿Está lista o no?
是的？
Yeah?
¿Sí?
它在名单上吗？
Is it on the list?
¿Está lista?
好吧，现在正如我们所期望的那样。
Well, now what we all expected.
Bueno, ahora lo que todos esperábamos.
玛丽亚·贝塞拉！
Maria Becerra!
¡María Becerra!
这将是！
It will be!
¡Serrá!
现在
and now
y ahora
我要补充，我会永远等你
I want to replenish, I will wait for you forever
Quiera reponer, te esperaré por siempre
我在想你 如果你原谅我
I'm thinking about you and if you forgive me
Estoy pensando en ti Y si tú me perdonas
你原谅我，你不再爱我了
You forgive me you don't love me anymore
Me perdonas Ya no me quieres
再看一次
and see again
y volver a ver
我想知道你们现在在哪里见面，但我想我知道今晚已经五点二了，我只知道
I wonder where you met now, but I think I know Tonight it's been five two and I just know
Me pregunto donde ahora conociste, pero creo que sé Esta noche ha pasado de cinco dos y perco sé
我接到你的电话，想象着最坏的情况，我不知道该怎么办。
I had a call from you. Imagining the worst, I didn't know what to do.
Tenía llamada tuya Imaginando lo peor ya no sabía qué hacer
我不知道我是否了解得很清楚，但是我，我不喜欢什么......
I don't know if I know well, but I, I didn't like what...
No sé si sé bien, pero ya me, no me gustó lo que...
我听到的，我想和你谈谈
what I heard, I wanted to talk to you
lo que escuché, yo quería hablar con vos
佩佩你的破布告诉我不要再为他兴奋了
Pepe your rag told me not to get excited about him anymore
Pepe tu trapo me dijo que no te ilusiones más con él
因为它不会回来 切断电话并摔倒
Because it won't come back cut off the phone and fall
Porque ya no va a volver Cortar el teléfono y caer
你让我的心空了
you left my heart empty
Me dejaste el corazón vacío
现在我又热又冷，真是迷惑了。
And now I'm getting hot and I'm dying of cold, how deluded.
Y ya me da calor y yo muero de frío, que ilusa.
快点！
Come on!
¡Vamos!
我
i
宝贝，见不到你就别发疯
Baby, and don't go crazy without seeing you
Baby, y no te pongas loco sin verte
靠在墙上和另一个人一起大笑你和我拥有它而你让它失去了而我想要
Laughing with another against the wall That you and I had it and you let it lose And that I want
Riendo con otro contra la pared Que tú y yo lo tuviste y lo dejaste perder Y que quiero
我
i
我们继续前进，尽管我们走在纯净中，但我们还是离开了。
We continue and although we walk in the pure, we leave.
Seguimos y aunque caminamos en lo puro, salimos.
你缺乏勇气，而我有承诺，这让我无法站起来。
You lacked courage and I had commitment, it stopped me from the floor.
Te faltó valor y yo tuve compromiso, me para del piso.
我
me
a mí
我听到的并不是所有的事情我都想和你谈谈，但我哭着告诉他
Not everything I heard I wanted to talk to you, but I rag and tell him that
No todo lo que escuché Yo quería hablar con vos, pero trapo y le digo que
我们不要对他抱有希望，因为他不会回来了。
Let's not get your hopes up about him because he's not going to come back.
No te ilusionemos con él porque ya no va a volver
电话那头，你让我的心空空如也
On the phone go up and you left my heart empty
Por teléfono sube y me dejaste corazón vacío
音乐...
Music...
Música...
小心！
Take care!
¡Taduro!
这是你皮肤的颜色，你的嘴唇是焦糖色，看你的地面，看天空
This is the color of your skin, your lips are caramel See your ground for the sky
Esto es color de tu piel, tu labios son caramelo Ver tu suelo para el cielo
这个皮质不是拥有我的模型，这就是为什么如果你碰我，我会打电话给我自己。
This cortico is not the model that has me, that's why if you touch me I'll call myself.
Este cortico no es modelo que me tiene, por eso si me tocas yo me llamo.
我喜欢你的毒药，它看起来越来越好，把它扔到我这里，拿走我喜欢的一切，是的，我喜欢它
I enjoy your poison and it looks better and better, throw it at me here, take everything I like, yes I love it
yo me disfruto tu veneno y cada vez se ve mas bueno echamelo aquí tome todo mi que me gusta si me encanta
现在
and now
y ya
音乐 音乐
Music Music
Música Música
我
i
所以
so
de modo
我
i
那是一段美好的时光，顶转，我喜欢它
It was a great time, top turn and I loved it
Fue un ma-de-ser, turno de top y me lo ma-de-ser
只有我们两个人，几个月后，几个月后，我就要杀死 Dímelo que sé tu forma
Just the two of us, in months, in months, I'm about to kill Dímelo que sé tu forma
我我
i i
只有想法才是最重要的
Just the thought that counts
我我
i i
太感谢了。
Thank you so much.
Muchas gracias.
神圣的，神圣的。
Divine, divine.
Divina, divina.
绝对神圣。
Absolutely divine.
Absolutamente divina.
我喜欢它，我喜欢它，事实是我喜欢它。
I love it, I love it, the truth is that I loved it.
Me encanta, me encanta, la verdad que me encantó.
太棒了，太棒了。
Fabulous, fabulous.
Fabulosa, fabulosa.
嗯，我想让他们...
Well, I want to make them...
Bueno, les quiero hacer...
在继续之前我想先告诉你们。
I want to tell you guys now before continuing.
Les quiero hacer chicos ahora antes de seguir.
在继续之前我要特别感谢你......
Before continuing I want to thank you very especially...
Antes de seguir quiero agradecerle muy especialmente...
致莱昂内尔·梅西 (Lionel Messi)，他在美国为我录制了视频。
to Lionel Messi, who was in the United States and recorded me.
a Lionel Messi, que estaba en Estados Unidos y me grabó.
那个神圣的东西。
that divine thing to be.
esa cosa divina para estar.
梅西，我爱你。
Messi, I love you.
Messi, te amo.
我打电话给梅西的母亲西莉亚。
I call Celia, Messi's mother.
Llamo a Celia, la mamá de Messi.
她是另一个梅西，是那个抚养他长大的人，是那个让他变得如此谦虚、神圣的人。
that she is another Messi, the one who raised him, the one who made him like this, humble, divine.
que es otra Messi, la que lo crió, la que lo hizo así, humilde, divino.
有礼貌，嗯，对整个梅西家族，我们爱你们，我们非常爱你们。
polite, well, to the entire Messi family, we love you, we love you very much.
educado, bueno, a toda la familia Messi que los amamos, los amamos mucho.
现在我要感谢你送给我的礼物和信息。
And now I want to thank you for the gifts and messages you sent me.
Y ahora quiero agradecer los regalos y mensajes que me mandaron.
快跑吧，我要看花。
Run, I want to see the flowers.
Correte que quiero ver las flores.
这些是米尔塔·勒格朗和家人的。
These are those of Mirta Legrand and family.
Estas son las de Mirta Legrand y familia.
非常感谢你们，我爱你们，小孩子们。
Thank you very much, I love you little ones.
Muchas gracias, te amo chiquis.
达里奥·图罗维尔斯基、彭迪诺、费德里科·莱布里诺。
Darío Turowelski, Pendino, Federico Lebrino.
Santiago Pernicioli，收入团队，Olga。
Santiago Pernicioli, Revenues team, Olga.
Santiago Pernicioli, equipo de Revenues, Olga.
奥尔加！
¡Olga!
玛丽亚·贝塞拉也给我送了花！
María Becerra also sent me flowers!
¡María Becerra me mandó también flores!
玛丽亚的是什么？
What are Maria's?
¿Cuáles son las de María?
让我看看玛丽亚的。
Show me Maria's.
Mostrame las de María.
好吧，嘿，Leandro Paredes 给我送来了 Vinos mi Victoria。
Well, hey, Leandro Paredes sent me Vinos mi Victoria.
Bueno, eh, Leandro Paredes me mandó Vinos mi Victoria.
哦，他向我收费是因为他赢了。
Oh, he's charging me because he won.
Ah, me está cargando porque ganó.
当然！
Of course!
¡Claro!
咬一口多好啊！
What a bite!
¡Qué picado!
看看多么神圣！
Look how divine!
¡Mira qué divino!
谢谢你，爱莱安德罗！
Thank you, loving Leandro!
¡Gracias, Leandro amoroso!
就跟嘲讽一样。
Just like mocking.
Igual que se burle.
哦，查理·加西亚，我爱你，查理。
Oh, Charly García, I love you, Charly.
Ay, Charly García, te amo, Charly.
Juan del Music，Cae 博士的家人。
Juan del Music, family of Dr. Cae.
Juan del Music, familia del Dr. Cae.
我全心全意地爱他。
I loved him with all my soul.
Lo amé con toda mi alma.
他是全家人的医生，但他离开了。
He was the doctor for the whole family and he left.
fue el médico de toda la familia y se fue.
大约四天前，但我从未见过你忘记，所以我把它放进去了……
about four days ago, but I never saw you forget and I put it in...
hace unos cuatro días, pero nunca te vi olvidar y se lo puse en...
到处。
everywhere.
en todos lados.
我永远不会忘记你，卡埃博士。
I will never forget you, Dr. Caé.
Nunca te voy a olvidar, doctor Caé.
胡安·伊格纳西奥·阿布奇特 (Juan Ignacio Abuchit)，A 组主席……不。
Juan Ignacio Abuchit, president of Group A... No.
Juan Ignacio Abuchit, presidente del Grupo A... No.
I、E、B. Antoniaz y Jewelers，La Peña de Morfi，Bodegas López。
I, E, B. Antoniaz y Jewelers, La Peña de Morfi, Bodegas López.
I, E, B. Antoniaz y Joyeros, La Peña de Morfi, Bodegas López.
当然，西尔瓦娜，一半的西尔瓦娜。
Silvana, half Silvana, of course.
Silvana, media Silvana, por supuesto.
毛里西奥和伊丽莎白·西尔凯。
Mauricio and Elizabeth Silkei.
Mauricio y Elizabeth Silkei.
世界、Silkei 世界、Polo Martínez 和家人、La Sieven、哈维尔·阿雷纳、诺拉和帕科。
world, Silkei world, Polo Martínez and family, La Sieven, Javier Arena, Nora and Paco.
mundial, Silkei mundial, Polo Martínez y familia, La Sieven, Javier Arena, Nora y Paco.
鲜花
the flowers
las flores
这。
This.
Esto.
哦。
Oh.
Ay.
好，好！
Good, good!
¡Bien, bien!
谢谢！
¡Gracias!
哦！
Oh!
¡Ay!
猜拳！
¡Mora!
但春天快乐！
But happy spring!
¡Pero feliz primavera!
我的花不见了！
My flowers were missing!
¡Faltaban mis flores!
你说得对，莫拉！
You're right, Mora!
¡Tenés razón, Mora!
雏菊！
The daisies!
¡Las margaritas!
首映快乐！
Happy premiere!
¡Feliz estreno!
谢谢你，但你是...
Thank you, but you are...
¡Gracias, pero vos sos...
玛格丽塔。
Margarita.
我是玛格丽特。
I am Margaret.
Yo soy Margarita.
该系列的主角。
The protagonist of the series.
La protagonista de la serie.
完全相同
The very same
La mismísima.
明天晚上九点十五分
tomorrow nine fifteen at night
mañana nueve y cuarto de la noche
出色的！
Excellent!
¡Qué bueno!
我的爱人，谢谢你！
My love, thank you!
Amor mío, ¡gracias!
谢谢你。
Thanks to you.
Gracias a vos.
我非常爱他们，玛格丽塔。
I loved them so well, Margarita.
Me encantaron así bien, Margarita.
谢谢。
Gracias.
它会杀人的。
It's going to kill.
Va a matar.
这就是克里斯所做的，克里斯莫雷纳创造的。
It's what Chris does, what Chris Morena produced.
Es lo que hace Chris, lo que produjo Chris Morena.
精确的。
Exact.
Exacto.
专门做这种事的。
Specialist for that kind of thing.
Especialista para ese tipo de cosas.
赞成，真是一个奇迹。
In favor, a wonder.
A favor, una maravilla.
我希望他们打破它。
I hope they break it.
Espero que la rompan.
我们走吧！
Let's go!
¡Vámonos!
我们也去吧！
Let's go too!
¡Vamos igualmente!
快点！
Come on!
¡Vamos!
我已经不得不告别这令人难以置信的一天了。
I already have to say goodbye to this incredible day.
Ya me tengo que despedir de este día increíble.
直到下周日，上帝保佑。
Until next Sunday, God willing.
Hasta el domingo que viene, si Dios quiere.
感谢一切。
Thanks for everything.
Gracias por todo.
谢谢你们！
Thanks guys!
¡Gracias chicos!
谢谢大众，大神！
Thank you public, divine!
¡Gracias público, divino!
苏珊娜，苏珊娜，我来找你
Susana, Susana, I'm coming to you
Susana, Susana ya te voy